<example>
	Here is an example response from the API, as snapshotted on 6/16/2022:
	<code>
    {
        "NewsArticles": [
            {
                "ShortHeadline": {
                    "value": "Fracture: Entrenched Returns",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Trhlina: Opevnění se vrací",
                        "da-DK": "Fracture: Entrenched vender tilbage",
                        "de-DE": "„Fraktur: Eingegraben“ kehrt zurück",
                        "el-GR": "Το Fracture: Entrenched επιστρέφει",
                        "es-ES": "Regresa Fracture: Atrincherados",
                        "es-MX": "Fractura: Atrincherados regresa",
                        "fi-FI": "Murtuma: Juurtunut palaa",
                        "fr-FR": "Retour de Fracture : Retranchement",
                        "hu-HU": "Visszatér a Töredék: Lövészárkok",
                        "it-IT": "Torna Fracture: Entrenched",
                        "ja-JP": "フラクチャー: エントレンチトが再登場",
                        "ko-KR": "균열: 참호가 돌아옵니다",
                        "nb-NO": "Brudd: Forskanset er tilbake",
                        "nl-NL": "Fracture: Entrenched is terug",
                        "pl-PL": "Wydarzenie Fracture: Okopani powraca",
                        "pt-BR": "Retorno de Fracture: Entrincheirado",
                        "pt-PT": "O regresso do evento Fratura: Entrincheirado",
                        "ru-RU": "Событие «Разлом: Неистребимые» возвращается",
                        "sv-SE": "Spricka: Befäst återvänder",
                        "tr-TR": "Çatlak: Sağlamlaştırılmış Geri Dönüyor",
                        "zh-CN": "“裂隙事件：根深蒂固”回归",
                        "zh-TW": "「斷裂：根深蒂固」回歸",
                        "qps-ploc": "₣řάĉťũяè: Εñтгэήςнέð Ŕêŧŭřπŝ !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "₣ŕªçťϋґĕ: Єňťгèņčĥěδ Яëťůґпѕ !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "₣ѓάčτüŗĕ: ∑ņŧяêи¢ђëð Ŗèτûřñѕ !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                },
                "FullHeadline": {
                    "value": "Fracture: Entrenched Returns",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Trhlina: Opevnění se vrací",
                        "da-DK": "Fracture: Entrenched vender tilbage",
                        "de-DE": "„Fraktur: Eingegraben“ kehrt zurück",
                        "el-GR": "Το Fracture: Entrenched επιστρέφει",
                        "es-ES": "Regresa Fracture: Atrincherados",
                        "es-MX": "Fractura: Atrincherados regresa",
                        "fi-FI": "Murtuma: Juurtunut palaa",
                        "fr-FR": "Retour de Fracture : Retranchement",
                        "hu-HU": "Visszatér a Töredék: Lövészárkok",
                        "it-IT": "Torna Fracture: Entrenched",
                        "ja-JP": "フラクチャー: エントレンチトが再登場",
                        "ko-KR": "균열: 참호가 돌아옵니다",
                        "nb-NO": "Brudd: Forskanset er tilbake",
                        "nl-NL": "Fracture: Entrenched is terug",
                        "pl-PL": "Wydarzenie Fracture: Okopani powraca",
                        "pt-BR": "Retorno de Fracture: Entrincheirado",
                        "pt-PT": "O regresso do evento Fratura: Entrincheirado",
                        "ru-RU": "Событие «Разлом: Неистребимые» возвращается",
                        "sv-SE": "Spricka: Befäst återvänder",
                        "tr-TR": "Çatlak: Sağlamlaştırılmış Geri Dönüyor",
                        "zh-CN": "“裂隙事件：根深蒂固”回归",
                        "zh-TW": "「斷裂：根深蒂固」回歸",
                        "qps-ploc": "₣řάĉťũяè: Εñтгэήςнέð Ŕêŧŭřπŝ !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "₣ŕªçťϋґĕ: Єňťгèņčĥěδ Яëťůґпѕ !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "₣ѓάčτüŗĕ: ∑ņŧяêи¢ђëð Ŗèτûřñѕ !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                },
                "Body": {
                    "value": "Fracture: Entrenched returns for its second week! \n\nIn this free event, jump into the Land Grab event playlist and complete event-specific challenges to unlock exclusive cosmetic rewards to outfit your dieselpunk-themed EAGLESTRIKE armor core! \n\nSeparate from the Battle Pass, the Event Pass is 100% free and offers players themed, limited time rewards while the event is live. \n\nFracture: Entrenched will return throughout Season 2, and with each recurrence a new chapter of The Last Sky Marshal, the choose your own adventure-style story, will release on Halo Waypoint. \n\nAlso, keep an eye out for additional featured Entrenched customization items in the Shop during the event! \n\n",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Trhlina: Opevnění se vrací na svůj druhý týden! \n\nZahrajte si v této bezplatné události playlist Zábor území a dokončujte pro tuto událost výzvy. Odemknete tak exkluzivní kosmetické odměny, kterými můžete vybavit své jádro brnění EAGLESTRIKE v dieselpunkovém stylu! \n\nEvent Pass nesouvisí s Battle Passem, je zcela zdarma a nabízí hráčům v době události tématické, časové omezené odměny. \n\nTrhlina: Opevnění se v průběhu 2. sezóny bude vracet a při každém návratu bude na webu Halo Waypoint vydána nová kapitola Posledního nebeského maršála – dobrodružného příběhu, o jehož vývoji se rozhodnete sami. \n\nK tomu sledujte další přizpůsobovací předměty s tématikou Opevněných, které během události najdete v Obchodě! \n\n",
                        "de-DE": "„Fraktur: Eingegraben“ geht in die zweite Woche! \n\nIn diesem Gratisevent springst du in die Landnahme-Event-Spielliste und schließt eventspezifische Herausforderungen ab, um exklusive kosmetische Belohnungen zu erhalten, mit denen du deinen dieselpunkigen Panzerungskern „Adlerschlag“ aufhübschen kannst! \n\nUnabhängig vom Battle Pass ist der Event Pass zu 100 % kostenlos und bietet Spielern zeitlich begrenzte Belohnungen, während das Event läuft. \n\n„Fraktur: Eingegraben“ kehrt in Saison 2 wieder und mit jeder Wiederkehr auf Halo Waypoint erscheint ein neues Kapitel von „The Last Sky Marshal“, in dem du entscheidenden Einfluss auf den Verlauf der Geschichte nimmst. \n\nAußerdem wird es während des Events zusätzliche Eingegraben-Anpassungsgegenstände im Shop geben, also Augen auf! \n\n",
                        "el-GR": "To Fracture: Entrenched επιστρέφει για δεύτερη εβδομάδα! \n\nΣε αυτήν τη δωρεάν εκδήλωση, μπες στη λίστα αναπαραγωγής της εκδήλωσης Αρπαγή γης και ολοκλήρωσε τις ειδικές προκλήσεις για να ξεκλειδώσεις αποκλειστικές διακοσμητικές ανταμοιβές για τον πυρήνα πανοπλίας ΑΕΤΟΧΤΥΠΗΜΑ με θέμα dieselpunk! \n\nΑνεξάρτητα από το Battle Pass, το Event Pass είναι 100% δωρεάν και προσφέρει στους παίκτες θεματικές ανταμοιβές περιορισμένου χρόνου κατά τη διάρκεια της εκδήλωσης. \n\nΤο Fracture: Entrenched θα επιστρέφει καθ' όλη τη διάρκεια της 2ης σεζόν, και με κάθε επανάληψη θα κυκλοφορεί ένα νέο κεφάλαιο του Ο Τελευταίος Σερίφης του Ουρανού, της ιστορίας όπου διαλέγεις εσύ την περιπέτειά σου, στο Halo Waypoint. \n\nΕπίσης, έχε το νου σου για επιπλέον αντικείμενα εξατομίκευσης Entrenched στο Κατάστημα κατά τη διάρκεια της εκδήλωσης! \n\n",
                        "es-ES": "¡Fracture: Atrincherados regresa en su segunda semana! \n\nEn este evento gratuito, accede a la lista de juego del evento Toma de terreno y completa retos específicos del evento para desbloquear recompensas cosméticas exclusivas con las que equipar tu núcleo de armadura EAGLESTRIKE con temática dieselpunk. \n\nEl pase de evento es independiente al pase de batalla y totalmente gratuito, y ofrece a los jugadores recompensas temáticas por tiempo limitado mientras el evento esté activo. \n\nFracture: Atrincherados regresará a lo largo de la temporada 2, y con cada recurrencia se lanzará un nuevo capítulo de The Last Sky Marshal (una historia en la que eliges tu propia aventura) en Halo Waypoint. \n\nAdemás, durante el evento, no pierdas de vista los objetos de personalización de Atrincherados que aparecen en la tienda. \n\n",
                        "es-MX": "¡Fractura: Atrincherados regresa por su segunda semana! \n\n¡Entra a la lista de juegos del evento Acaparamiento durante este evento gratuito y completa los desafíos para desbloquear recompensas cosméticas exclusivas para equipar tu núcleo de armadura EAGLESTRIKE de temática dieselpunk! \n\nA diferencia del Pase de Batalla, el Pase de Evento es 100% gratuito y ofrece a los jugadores recompensas temáticas de tiempo limitado mientras el evento está activo. \n\nFractura: Atrincherados regresará varias veces a lo largo de la temporada 2; en cada ocasión se lanzará en Halo Waypoint un nuevo capítulo de The Last Sky Marshal, una historia en la cual tú eliges tu propia aventura. \n\n¡No te pierdas los artículos de personalización adicionales que aparecerán destacados en la tienda durante el evento! \n\n",
                        "fi-FI": "Murtuma: Juurtunut palaa toiselle viikolleen! \n\nTässä ilmaisessa tapahtumassa hyppää Land Grab -tapahtuman soittolistalle ja suorita tapahtumakohtaiset haasteet avataksesi eksklusiivisia kosmeettisia palkintoja dieselpunk-teemaisen EAGLESTRIKE-panssariytimesi varustamiseksi! \n\nBattle Passista erillinen Event Pass on täysin ilmainen ja tarjoaa pelaajille teemaan liittyviä rajoitetun ajan saatavilla olevia palkintoja moninpeliotteluiden pelaamisesta tapahtuman aikana. \n\nMurtuma: Juurtunut palaa useampaan otteeseen kakkoskauden aikana, ja joka kerta Halo Waypointissa julkaistaan uusi luku pelikirjatyyliseen Viimeinen taivasmarsalkka -tarinaan. \n\nPidä tapahtuman aikana silmällä myös muita esittelyssä olevia Juurtunut-mukautusesineitä Kaupassa! \n\n",
                        "fr-FR": "Fracture : Retranchement revient pour une deuxième semaine ! \n\nDans cet événement gratuit, disputez une sélection Possession du terrain et accomplissez des défis spécifiques pour déverrouiller des récompenses cosmétiques exclusives assorties à votre noyau d'armure rétrofuturiste EAGLESTRIKE ! \n\nBien distinct du pass combat, le pass événement est 100 % gratuit et offre aux joueurs des récompenses thématiques pendant la durée de l'événement.\n\nFracture : Retranchement reviendra tout au long de la saison 2, et chaque retour signera la sortie sur Halo Waypoint d'un nouveau chapitre de The Last Sky Marshal, l'histoire dont le scénario dépend de vous. \n\nEt n'oubliez pas de jeter un œil aux autres éléments de personnalisation Retranchement proposés dans la boutique au cours de l'événement !\n\n",
                        "hu-HU": "A Töredék: Lövészárkok esemény visszatér a második hétre! \n\nAz ingyenes esemény során játssz az akciódús Földrablás esemény játéklistán, és teljesítsd az eseményspecifikus kihívásokat, hogy kozmetikai jutalmakat oldj fel, beleértve a dieselpunk-témájú EAGLESTRIKE páncélmagot. \n\nA Csatabérlettől független Eseménybérlet 100%-ban ingyenes, és tematikus, korlátozott ideig tartó jutalmakat kínál az esemény időtartama alatt. \n\nA Töredék: Lövészárkok visszatér majd folyamatosan a 2. évad során, és minden ilyen alkalommal új fejezettel bővül Az utolsó légi marsall története, a választásoddal befolyásolható kaland, amely a Halo Waypointon jelenik meg. \n\nEzenkívül tartsd szemmel a további Lövészárkok témájú tárgyakat az Áruházban az esemény ideje alatt! \n\n",
                        "it-IT": "Fracture: Entrenched torna per la seconda settimana! \n\nApprofittando di questo evento gratuito, tuffati nella playlist Conquista territorio e completa le Sfide per sbloccare premi cosmetici esclusivi ed equipaggiare il tuo nucleo corazza EAGLESTRIKE a tema diesel-punk! \n\nDifferente dal Battle Pass, l'Event Pass è completamente gratuito e offre ai giocatori premi a tema per un tempo limitato a evento in corso. \n\nFracture: Entrenched tornerà più volte nella stagione 2 e ogni appuntamento si accompagnerà a un nuovo capitolo di L'ultimo sceriffo del cielo, la tua storia avventurosa personalizzata, pubblicata su Halo Waypoint. \n\nInoltre, non farti sfuggire gli ulteriori elementi di personalizzazione Entrenched in evidenza nel negozio durante l'evento! \n\n",
                        "ja-JP": "「フラクチャー: エントレンチト」の 2 週目が登場!\n\nこの無料イベントで、ランド グラブ イベント プレイリストに飛び込んでイベント限定のチャレンジをクリアし、ディーゼルパンクをテーマにしたイーグルストライク アーマーのコアや限定外装などのリワードをアンロックしよう!\n\nバトル パスとは別に完全無料で利用できるイベント パスでは、イベント期間中に様々なテーマの期間限定リワードを獲得できます。\n\n「フラクチャー: エントレンチト」は、シーズン 2 を通して再登場し、そのたびに選択式アドベンチャー スタイルのストーリーである「最後のスカイ マーシャル」の新しいチャプターが「Halo Waypoint」でリリースされます。\n\nまた、イベント期間中は、「エントレンチト」をテーマにしたカスタマイズ アイテムがショップに追加されますので、そちらもお見逃しなく!\n\n",
                        "ko-KR": "균열: 참호가 돌아와 두 번째 주간이 진행됩니다! \n\n이 무료 이벤트에서는 영토 쟁탈전 이벤트 플레이리스트에서 플레이하고 이벤트에 특화된 챌린지를 완료하여 디젤펑크 테마의 이글스트라이크 방어구 코어를 위한 전용 꾸미기 보상을 잠금 해제하십시오! \n\n전투 패스에서 분리된 이벤트 패스는 100% 무료이며, 이벤트가 진행되는 동안 플레이어에게 기간 한정 테마 보상을 제공합니다. \n\n균열: 참호는 시즌 2 동안 돌아올 것이며, Halo Waypoint에 나오는 '마지막 항공 경비대'의 새 챕터를 반복하면서 어드벤처 스타일의 스토리를 스스로 선택할 수 있습니다. \n\n또한, 이벤트 기간 동안 상점에서 추가로 제공되는 참호 사용자 지정 추천 아이템을 자주 확인하세요! \n\n",
                        "nb-NO": "Brudd: Forskanset er tilbake i sin andre uke! \n\nI denne gratishendelsen kan du hoppe inn i Landerobring-spillelisten og fullføre hendelsesspesifikke utfordringer for å låse opp eksklusive kosmetiske belønninger og utstyre EAGLESTRIKE-rustningskjernen med dieselpunk-tema! \n\nHendelsespasset skiller seg fra kamppasset ved at det er 100 % gratis og gir spillerne temabelønninger med begrenset tid mens hendelsen pågår. \n\nBrudd: Forskanset kommer tilbake gjennom sesong 2, og hver gang vil du få et nytt kapittel i Den siste himmelmarskalken. Stak ut din egen historie på Halo Waypoint. \n\nHold også utkikk etter utvalgte Forskanset-tilpasningselementer i butikken under hendelsen! \n\n",
                        "nl-NL": "Fracture: Entrenched keert terug voor een tweede week! \n\nTijdens dit gratis event speel je de event-playlist Land Grab en voltooi je speciale uitdagingen om cosmetische beloningen te verdienen voor je pantserkern EAGLESTRIKE in dieselpunk-thema. \n\nDe gratis Event Pass staat los van de Battle Pass en bevat speciale thema-beloningen. Deze zijn alleen beschikbaar zolang het event actief is. \n\nFracture: Entrenched keert regelmatig terug in seizoen 2. Nieuwe hoofdstukken van 'The Last Sky Marshal', het avontuur waarvan jij het verloop bepaalt, verschijnen dan op Halo Waypoint. \n\nLet tijdens het event ook op de extra speciale Entrenched-aanpassingen in de winkel! \n\n",
                        "pl-PL": "Zapraszamy na drugi tydzień z Fracture: Okopani!\n\nW trakcie tego bezpłatnego wydarzenia możesz uczestniczyć w rozgrywkach w trybie Przejęcie ziemi ze specjalnej playlisty i kończyć wyzwania z wydarzenia, by odblokować wyjątkowe nagrody kosmetyczne do swojego dieselpunkowego rdzenia pancerza UDERZENIE ORŁA!\n\nPrzepustka na wydarzenie jest w 100% darmowa, nie jest powiązana z przepustką bojową i zapewnia tematyczne nagrody dostępne przez ograniczony czas, które można zdobyć w trakcie wydarzenia.\n\nFracture: Okopani powróci kilkukrotnie w trakcie sezonu 2, a za każdym razem na Halo Waypoint dostępny będzie nowy rozdział historii Ostatni podniebny marszałek, której przebieg zależy od twoich wyborów.\n\nMiej oczy szeroko otwarte, bo w czasie trwania wydarzenia w Sklepie dostępne będą także dodatkowe wyróżnione opcje personalizacji Okopani!\n\n",
                        "pt-BR": "Fracture: Entrincheirado retorna em sua segunda semana! \n\nNeste evento gratuito, entre na lista de jogo do evento Posse de Terra e complete desafios específicos do evento para desbloquear recompensas cosméticas exclusivas para equipar seu núcleo de armadura EAGLESTRIKE com tema dieselpunk! \n\nSeparado do Passe de Batalha, o Passe de Evento é 100% gratuito e oferece aos jogadores recompensas temáticas por tempo limitado enquanto o evento estiver acontecendo. \n\nFracture: Entrincheirado retornará ao longo da Temporada 2 e, a cada recorrência, um novo capítulo de O Último Marechal do Céu será lançado no Halo Waypoint para você escolher sua própria história no estilo de aventura. \n\nAlém disso, fique de olho nos itens adicionais de personalização do Entrincheirado em destaque na Loja durante o evento! \n\n",
                        "pt-PT": "O Fratura: Entrincheirado regressa para a segunda semana! \n\nNeste evento gratuito, joga na lista de reprodução do evento Captura de terrenos e completa desafios específicos do evento para desbloquear recompensas cosméticas exclusivas para o core de armadura EAGLESTRIKE com o tema dieselpunk! \n\nSeparado do Battle Pass, o Evento Pass é 100% gratuito e oferece aos jogadores recompensas temáticas e limitadas enquanto o evento está a decorrer.\n\nO Fratura: Entrincheirado regressará ao longo da Temporada 2 e, a cada retorno, será lançado no Halo Waypoint um novo capítulo de O Último Sky Marshal, a escolha da tua própria história com um estilo de aventura. \n\nAlém disso, não te esqueças de prestar atenção aos itens adicionais de personalização Entrincheirado na loja durante o evento! \n\n",
                        "ru-RU": "Событие «Разлом: Неистребимые» возвращается во второй раз!\n\nУчаствуйте в матчах списка игр «Захват местности» и выполняйте испытания этого бесплатного события, чтобы получать эксклюзивные украшения для основы «АТАКА ОРЛА» в стиле дизельпанк.\n\nАбонемент события, доступный отдельно от боевого абонемента, совершенно бесплатен и позволяет получать награды до окончания события.\n\nВ течение второго сезона событие «Разлом: Неистребимые» будет возвращаться несколько раз одновременно с выходом новых глав интерактивной повести «Последний воздушный маршал» на сайте Halo Waypoint.\n\nИ не забывайте заходить в магазин, где во время события будут появляться дополнительные предметы для персонализации в стиле «Неистребимых».\n\n",
                        "sv-SE": "Spricka: Befäst återvänder för sin andra vecka!\n\nSpela markövertags-evenemangsspellistan gratis och klara evenemangsspecifika utmaningar för att låsa upp belöningar till dieselpunk-inspirerade rustningskärnan ÖRNANFALL!\n\nEvenemangspasset är separat från stridspasset, är helt gratis och ger spelare tidsbegränsande belöningar under evenemanget.\n\nSpricka: Befäst återkommer under säsong 2, och varje gång släpps ett nytt kapitel av den interaktiva berättelsen Den sista himmelsmarskalken på Halo Waypoint.\n\nHåll utkik efter Befäst-anpassningsföremål i butiken under evenemanget!\n\n",
                        "tr-TR": "Çatlak: Sağlamlaştırılmış, ikinci haftası için geri dönüyor! \n\nBu ücretsiz etkinlikte Toprak Kapmaca etkinliği oynama listesini oynayın ve dieselpunk temalı EAGLESTRIKE zırh çekirdeğinizi kuşanmak için özel kozmetik ödüllerin kilidini açmak amacıyla etkinliğe özgü mücadeleleri tamamlayın. \n\nEtkinlik Bileti, Savaş Bileti'nden ayrı olarak %100 ücretsizdir ve oyunculara etkinlik devam ettiği sürece temalı ve sınırlı süreli ödüller sunar. \n\nÇatlak: Sağlamlaştırılmış, 2. Sezon boyunca yeniden düzenlenecek ve her etkinlikte, kendi macera tarzı hikâyenizi seçebileceğiniz Son Hava Mareşali'nin yeni bir bölümü Halo Waypoint'te yayınlanacak. \n\nAyrıca etkinlik sırasında Mağaza'daki öne çıkan diğer Sağlamlaştırılmış özelleştirme ögelerini de takip edin! \n\n",
                        "zh-CN": "“裂隙事件：根深蒂固”第二周回归！\n\n在这次免费事件中，进入领土攫取活动游戏列表并完成事件特殊挑战，解锁专属外观奖励来装饰柴油朋克主题的鹰击护甲核心！\n\n和战斗通行证不同，事件通行证完全免费，并会在活动期间提供玩家限时主题奖励。\n\n“裂隙事件：根深蒂固”会在第 2 季多次回归，随着每一次回归，我们都会在 Halo Waypoint 同步释出多重结局冒险风格的故事：《最后的空军将领》的新篇章。\n\n除此之外，也别错过商店在活动期间所推出的其他精选根深蒂固自定义项目！\n\n",
                        "zh-TW": "「斷裂：根深蒂固」第二週回歸！\n\n在這次免費事件中，進入陸上霸王活動遊戲清單並完成事件特殊挑戰，解鎖專屬外觀獎勵來裝飾柴油龐克主題的獵鷹突擊護甲核心！\n\n和戰鬥 Pass 不同，事件 Pass 完全免費，並會在活動期間提供玩家限時主題獎勵。\n\n「斷裂：根深蒂固」會在第 2 季多次回歸，隨著每一次回歸，我們都會在 Halo Waypoint 同步釋出多重結局冒險風格的故事：《最後的空軍將領》的新篇章。\n\n除此之外，也別錯過商店在活動期間所推出的其他精選根深蒂固自訂項目！\n\n",
                        "qps-ploc": "₣ŕасťũŕë: Зņţяêήċнęð řëтŭґπş ƒøŗ іŧѕ ѕзćόñđ ώēеќ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nĬŋ тђіѕ ƒѓεę éνėⁿţ, ĵűmρ ΐŋŧö ţħέ Łǻńδ Ĝгąв ėν℮ήτ φłăÿĺįśŧ àņđ ¢óмрℓèŧ℮ ёνєŋţ-ѕφē¢ìƒĭĉ ¢ħàļľēлğëś τò цŉĺθςĸ ĕж¢łűşїνę сöšmēťĩς ґёшăгďŝ ŧõ òцţƒîť ÿσűѓ ďĩ℮ѕĕłрūлĸ-ŧнємєď ËĂĢĽΕЅŤŘĮĶĘ åґмог čσřе!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nŠêφάřªťë ƒяòм ţћê Ьаттłê Ρàŝş, ťћë Ένєйŧ Ρăśŝ ìş 100% ƒяэё ªñδ öƒƒèřѕ рļăŷèřŝ τħèмєđ, ℓìmîţęδ ŧīmê гéώąŕδş шђìľĕ τħè ėνэⁿť ĩš ļíνē.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\n₣ґă¢ťüřė: Εŋτґέηċħзđ шιľℓ ŕèťůŗŋ тђгõцģђоμт Ѕëäŝσй 2, άŋď ẁіţђ еą¢ђ гεċцгŕèńčê å ŋєщ сħàрťĕŗ øƒ Ťħé Ľàѕт Śκỳ Мâŗŝђдĺ, ťћз ςħòοśè ỳǿцř оẁή ǻďνёńтцгé-šţуľε šţθŗу, щīℓℓ ŗěľèдśë õñ Ħάľò Щâγρоîŋŧ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nДłѕō, ќеэφ αй éỳę øüť ƒθґ αđðιτîбňǻł ƒ℮âţũřєđ Ейťřéл¢ћёđ ¢џŝŧǿmìžаţîöŉ ΐťěmŝ іņ ţĥę Ѕħоρ đűřίŋğ ťћё ęνэňт!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\n",
                        "qps-ploca": "₣ŗãčтüґę: Зņτгèйсћёď řęŧϋгиś ƒǿг îŧŝ ѕēčбŋδ ẃěēκ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nЇň ŧћįś ƒřėė ęνéŋŧ, ĵũмρ īŉťō ŧђě Ļáñδ Ģřąъ ένëпŧ ρłаỳĺϊѕţ άήď ċómрŀеťé ℮νёñт-şρěĉíƒĭç ςĥªłℓęπġēŝ ŧό ůπłθсĸ зжçľůѕινė čöśmęţĩċ řэωąřδŝ ŧό õüŧƒίτ ỳόŭґ ðįеŝэĺφϋπķ-ťĥеm℮δ ЄǺĠĿЁЅТҐĬΚĘ äŕмōř ςöřè!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nŜεφăřâтę ƒŕοm ťће ßªттļε Раşѕ, τћё Еνéπт Рąŝŝ íŝ 100% ƒгęė äŋð ôƒƒēřś φℓåŷёґš τнëмęδ, ļĭmíť℮δ ŧĭмê ѓěẁǻяďѕ шћїĺз ťħέ ενёиŧ ιš ľινё.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\n₣ѓäćτцяē: Ёⁿţŗêиĉħёð ŵίĺℓ гēτυяñ ŧћŕбúġħôµť Śëåśőп 2, ăñđ ẅíťĥ ĕąςћ ř℮¢ΰŕяěŉ¢ê ª йėẃ ćħåртëř øƒ Τћé Ļαśŧ Ѕĸÿ Μдřšћáł, тħę çнθõŝ℮ уόŭг όẁи äďνзйτΰѓė-ѕтŷłэ ŝτόŗÿ, ẁїļļ ř℮ļэášĕ οη Ħдℓο Ẅâўφσїŉτ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nÁℓşθ, кэёρ åи éÿê бµт ƒōґ ªðďΐтìоŋåŀ ƒèªŧŭгэđ Éńтѓэйćђёď сûѕŧömіżαтίǿŉ íťémš íň τĥé Śћǿр ďûŗίñğ ťĥē ℮νєŋŧ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\n",
                        "qps-plocm": "₣ŕą¢ťúŕ℮: Эñŧŕэńĉĥέď ŕ℮тυŗňş ƒøя îţš śєĉοñð шε℮к!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nİŋ тђїş ƒгεé ℮νęñť, јцмр ϊňτǿ ţħē Ľдήδ Ĝґáв ëνĕňŧ φℓąγĺíšť āπð çомφℓэţє єνзηť-ѕрë¢ïƒīċ ¢ĥαℓĺéŉģēš ţο ŭŋļθ¢ĸ ëжċĺμśĩνз ¢θšmётī¢ ґзωαřðš ŧσ θџтƒιť ýòűѓ ðíëѕεłφϋиĸ-тħεm℮đ ÈΔĞĻΣЅŦŘÎΚĚ ářмθř çøřэ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nŞëρªґåтë ƒѓøм тĥē ßąţţľε Рāŝŝ, тнė Ęνéⁿτ Рàšŝ ĩѕ 100% ƒгēę ăиđ õƒƒёřś φℓäγеřѕ τĥěмзđ, ĺîmΐŧэď ŧїмĕ язωάґðś ẁнíℓє ŧнê ℮νзйť ĭş ĺΐνë.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\n₣řǻ¢ŧůŗэ: Éňţřэŋĉĥėď ŵīľľ řêτΰгή тђгõūġђóџŧ Şěąşŏή 2, ǻňδ ωϊťĥ еаςћ гεċūгґёлçз а ηęŵ ĉĥαрŧєř бƒ Ŧђе Ŀąşτ Śĸŷ Мдяşĥάł, тнĕ ċћõőśė ŷöцř õẁŋ άðνêйţυřё-ѕţγĺэ ѕτóґу, щιļł ґëŀēáşĕ бл Ĥàŀø Ẃăỳрόΐŉţ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nÀℓšō, кεёρ ãл ëγę όџŧ ƒőř äđδĭţĩøñāℓ ƒ℮άŧűґëđ Зηтѓėŋςђêδ ¢ųŝтõmĭżàŧїóп ίťεmŝ ĭñ тђё Šђбφ δũŕįлĝ ťђз єνεņţ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\n"
                    }
                },
                "ArticleImage": {
                    "Width": 1920,
                    "Height": 1080,
                    "Path": "news/Season2/Events/Entrenched_MOTD.jpg"
                },
                "ArticleActions": [
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Visit Halo Waypoint",
                            "status": "Frozen",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Navštívit Halo Waypoint",
                                "da-DK": "Besøg Halo Waypoint",
                                "de-DE": "Besuche Halo Waypoint",
                                "el-GR": "Μετάβαση στο Halo Waypoint",
                                "es-ES": "Visita Halo Waypoint",
                                "es-MX": "Visita Halo Waypoint",
                                "fi-FI": "Siirry Halo Waypointiin",
                                "fr-FR": "Visiter Halo Waypoint",
                                "hu-HU": "Látogass el a Halo Waypoint oldalra",
                                "it-IT": "Visita Halo Waypoint",
                                "ja-JP": "Halo Waypoint にアクセス",
                                "ko-KR": "Halo Waypoint 방문",
                                "nb-NO": "Gå til Halo Waypoint",
                                "nl-NL": "Ga naar Halo Waypoint",
                                "pl-PL": "Odwiedź Halo Waypoint",
                                "pt-BR": "Acesse Halo Waypoint",
                                "pt-PT": "Visita o Halo Waypoint",
                                "ru-RU": "Посетить Halo Waypoint",
                                "sv-SE": "Besök Halo Waypoint",
                                "tr-TR": "Halo Waypoint'i ziyaret edin",
                                "zh-CN": "访问 Halo Waypoint",
                                "zh-TW": "造訪 Halo Waypoint",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vιŝįţ Ĥäłő Шäỳφŏϊήŧ !!! !!!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Vΐšïŧ Ĥǻļσ Ẁąŷρòĭпτ !!! !!!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Vīŝìť Ήâłô Шãýρôíņţ !!! !!!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to Halo Waypoint to read more.",
                            "status": "Frozen",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na Halo Waypoint, kde si budete moct přečíst více.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi fører dig hen til Halo Waypoint, hvor du kan læse mere.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zu Halo Waypoint weitergeleitet, um mehr Details zu erfahren.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στο Halo Waypoint για να διαβάσεις περισσότερα.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a Halo Waypoint para obtener más información.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a Halo Waypoint para darte más información.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut Halo Waypointiin, niin voit lukea asiasta lisää.",
                                "fr-FR": "Nous allons vous diriger vers Halo Waypoint pour de plus amples informations.",
                                "hu-HU": "Bővebb információkért a Halo Waypoint oldalára viszünk.",
                                "it-IT": "Per maggiori informazioni, sarai trasferito su Halo Waypoint.",
                                "ja-JP": "詳細については、Halo Waypoint をご確認ください。",
                                "ko-KR": "자세한 내용을 보실 수 있도록 Halo Waypoint로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til Halo Waypoint, der du kan lese mer.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar Halo Waypoint, waar je meer kunt lezen.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię do Halo Waypoint, gdzie dowiesz się więcej.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao Halo Waypoint para ler mais.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao Halo Waypoint para leres mais.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы расскажем вам все подробности в Halo Waypoint.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Halo Waypoint, där du kan läsa mer.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi daha fazla bilgi almanız için Halo Waypoint'e aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们将带您前往 Halo Waypoint，阅读更多信息。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們將帶您前往 Halo Waypoint，閱讀更多資訊。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ŵė'ŀĺ вґĭйğ ŷǿų тõ Ĥǻℓŏ Ẃąýрōįńτ тõ ŗéåδ мôřє. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ше'ĺľ ъřїпġ ýòú ŧó Ηąļо Ẅαγρõīńť ŧö яěáð мöѓę. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẅę'łł вѓíπģ ўοű ţø Ĥªľó Шąурóіиτ τø гέаð mθřέ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://aka.ms/FractureEntrenched"
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Visit your free Event Pass",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Navštivte svůj bezplatný Event Pass",
                                "da-DK": "Besøg dit gratis Event Pass",
                                "de-DE": "Sieh dir deinen kostenlosen Event Pass an",
                                "el-GR": "Μετάβαση στο δωρεάν Πάσο Εκδηλώσεών σου",
                                "es-ES": "Ve al pase de evento gratuito",
                                "es-MX": "Visita tu Pase de evento gratuito",
                                "fi-FI": "Tarkastele ilmaista Event Passiasi",
                                "fr-FR": "Découvrir votre pass événement gratuit",
                                "hu-HU": "Látogass el az ingyenes Eseménybérletedhez",
                                "it-IT": "Visita il tuo Event Pass gratuito",
                                "ja-JP": "無料のイベント パスに移動",
                                "ko-KR": "무료 이벤트 패스 방문",
                                "nb-NO": "Sjekk gratishendelsespasset ditt",
                                "nl-NL": "Ga naar je gratis Event Pass",
                                "pl-PL": "Odwiedź swoją darmową przepustkę na wydarzenie",
                                "pt-BR": "Acesse seu Passe de Evento gratuito",
                                "pt-PT": "Visita o teu Event Pass gratuito",
                                "ru-RU": "Бесплатный абонемент события",
                                "sv-SE": "Besök ditt gratis evenemangspass",
                                "tr-TR": "Ücretsiz Etkinlik Bileti'nizi ziyaret edin",
                                "zh-CN": "访问免费事件通行证",
                                "zh-TW": "造訪您的免費事件 Pass",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vίŝĭτ ỳõύґ ƒřěè Ēνèŋŧ Ρªšś !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Vϊŝΐť ýöũř ƒřēè Ĕνèņţ Рãşŝ !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Vΐśΐť ỳбūґ ƒřэę Еνэňŧ Рäѕš !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll navigate you over to the Event Pass.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Přesuneme vás na Event Pass.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi sender dig til Event Passet.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zum Event Pass weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε βοηθήσουμε να μεταβείς στο Event Pass.",
                                "es-ES": "Te redirigiremos al pase de evento.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos al Pase de evento.",
                                "fi-FI": "Viemme sinut Event Passiin.",
                                "fr-FR": "Vous arriverez sur le pass événement.",
                                "hu-HU": "Az Eseménybérlethez navigálunk.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti indirizzeremo all'Event Pass.",
                                "ja-JP": "イベント パスをご案内します。",
                                "ko-KR": "이벤트 패스로 이동시켜 드리겠습니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til hendelsespasset.",
                                "nl-NL": "We brengen je naar de Event Pass.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię do przepustki na wydarzenie.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao Passe de Evento.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te até ao Event Pass.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем для вас абонемент события.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till evenemangspasset.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi Etkinlik Bileti'ne yönlendireceğiz.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们会带领您前往事件通行证。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會引導您前往事件 Pass。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ше'ľℓ ήäνіĝáťě γőυ ŏνéŕ τõ τĥě Ενэňŧ Рǻşš. !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "Шє'ĺļ πдνįĝąτє ўòų бνєѓ тο ŧђê Ęνëŉт Ράśś. !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẅė'ŀŀ иªνíģăţê γοŭ õνēѓ τб ţђė Ėνêⁿţ Рāśş. !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "news://slamsContentScreen?slamsUri=progression_menu"
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Head to Shop",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Přejít na Obchod",
                                "da-DK": "Gå til butikken",
                                "de-DE": "Zum Shop",
                                "el-GR": "Μετάβαση στο Κατάστημα",
                                "es-ES": "Ve a la tienda",
                                "es-MX": "Entra a la tienda",
                                "fi-FI": "Siirry kauppaan",
                                "fr-FR": "Vers la boutique",
                                "hu-HU": "Ugrás az Áruházra",
                                "it-IT": "Vai al negozio",
                                "ja-JP": "ショップへ移動",
                                "ko-KR": "상점으로 이동",
                                "nb-NO": "Gå til butikken",
                                "nl-NL": "Ga naar de winkel",
                                "pl-PL": "Przejdź do sklepu",
                                "pt-BR": "Acesse a Loja",
                                "pt-PT": "Vai para a Loja",
                                "ru-RU": "Заглянуть в магазин",
                                "sv-SE": "Gå till butik",
                                "tr-TR": "Mağaza'ya Git",
                                "zh-CN": "前往商店",
                                "zh-TW": "前往商店",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ήεáδ ţō Şĥòφ !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ήέāđ ťό Šћóφ !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ήεаð ţό Ŝħòр !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll navigate you over to the Shop to check it out.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Přesuneme vás na Obchod, abyste se mohli podívat.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi sender dig over til vores butik, så du kan se på den.",
                                "de-DE": "Wir leiten dich zum Shop weiter, damit du ihn dir ansehen kannst.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε βοηθήσουμε να μεταβείς στο Κατάστημα για να ρίξεις μια ματιά.",
                                "es-ES": "Te redirigiremos a la tienda para que le eches un vistazo.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a la Tienda para que veas lo que hay.",
                                "fi-FI": "Viemme sinut kauppaan tutustuaksesi siihen.",
                                "fr-FR": "Vous arriverez à la boutique pour voir ce qui y est proposé.",
                                "hu-HU": "Az Áruházhoz navigálunk, hogy átnézd a kínálatot.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti indirizzeremo al Negozio per completare l'acquisto.",
                                "ja-JP": "ショップの内容をご案内します。",
                                "ko-KR": "상점을 확인할 수 있도록 이동시켜 드리겠습니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til butikken, så du kan sjekke den ut.",
                                "nl-NL": "We brengen je naar de winkel, zodat je 'm kunt bekijken.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię do sklepu – przejrzyj go.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você à Loja para conferir.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te até à Loja para que a possas explorar.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы проведём вас по магазину, чтобы вы нашли в нём всё необходимое.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till butiken så du kan kolla in den.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi göz atmanız için Mağaza'ya yönlendireceğiz.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们会带领您前往商店进行查看。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會引導您前往商店瞧瞧。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ẅê'ĺĺ ηǻνíĝǻţ℮ ýθŭ ǿνεя тŏ тђз Şнõρ ŧǿ ćћéсĸ ΐť óύτ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ẃз'ĺł ηāνìĝάťě ŷōц ôνёя ťσ тĥè Šђôφ ŧο ςћé¢ĸ іŧ оџŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẁэ'łĺ ňãνíġάτέ ўøű õνέг тσ ţħë Ѕĥǿρ ŧō ¢ћеĉк įţ øûт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "news://slamsContentScreen?slamsUri=store"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "ShortHeadline": {
                    "value": "June Update – Drop Pod",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Červnová aktualizace – Výsadkový modul",
                        "da-DK": "Juni-opdatering - Drop Pod",
                        "de-DE": "Juni-Update – Landungskapsel",
                        "el-GR": "Ενημέρωση Ιουνίου – Drop Pod",
                        "es-ES": "Actualización de junio: cápsulas",
                        "es-MX": "Actualización de junio – Cápsula de descenso",
                        "fi-FI": "Kesäkuun päivitys – Drop Pod",
                        "fr-FR": "Mise à jour de juin - Module de largage",
                        "hu-HU": "Júniusi frissítés – Drop Pod",
                        "it-IT": "Aggiornamento di giugno - Capsula da sbarco",
                        "ja-JP": "6 月の更新 - 降下ポッド",
                        "ko-KR": "6월 업데이트 – 강하 포드",
                        "nb-NO": "Oppdatering i juni – Droppkapsel",
                        "nl-NL": "Update juni – droppod",
                        "pl-PL": "Czerwcowa aktualizacja – kapsuła desantowa",
                        "pt-BR": "Atualização de Junho - Drop Pod",
                        "pt-PT": "Atualização de junho – Drop Pod",
                        "ru-RU": "«Десантная капсула»: июньское обновление",
                        "sv-SE": "Junis uppdatering – kapsel",
                        "tr-TR": "Haziran Güncellemesi – Dağıtım Kapsülü",
                        "zh-CN": "六月更新 – 空投",
                        "zh-TW": "六月更新 – 空投",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ĵũηе Ũрďāţë – Ðŕόφ Ρòđ !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ĵůηё Ùрðǻтé – Ðřορ Ρσδ !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Јμπé Ùρđâťέ – Đřôρ Ρöδ !!! !!! "
                    }
                },
                "FullHeadline": {
                    "value": "June Update – Drop Pod",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Červnová aktualizace – Výsadkový modul",
                        "da-DK": "Juni-opdatering - Drop Pod",
                        "de-DE": "Juni-Update – Landungskapsel",
                        "el-GR": "Ενημέρωση Ιουνίου – Drop Pod",
                        "es-ES": "Actualización de junio: cápsulas",
                        "es-MX": "Actualización de junio – Cápsula de descenso",
                        "fi-FI": "Kesäkuun päivitys – Drop Pod",
                        "fr-FR": "Mise à jour de juin - Module de largage",
                        "hu-HU": "Júniusi frissítés – Drop Pod",
                        "it-IT": "Aggiornamento di giugno - Capsula da sbarco",
                        "ja-JP": "6 月の更新 - 降下ポッド",
                        "ko-KR": "6월 업데이트 – 강하 포드",
                        "nb-NO": "Oppdatering i juni – Droppkapsel",
                        "nl-NL": "Update juni – droppod",
                        "pl-PL": "Czerwcowa aktualizacja – kapsuła desantowa",
                        "pt-BR": "Atualização de Junho - Drop Pod",
                        "pt-PT": "Atualização de junho – Drop Pod",
                        "ru-RU": "«Десантная капсула»: июньское обновление",
                        "sv-SE": "Junis uppdatering – kapsel",
                        "tr-TR": "Haziran Güncellemesi – Dağıtım Kapsülü",
                        "zh-CN": "六月更新 – 空投",
                        "zh-TW": "六月更新 – 空投",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ĵũηе Ũрďāţë – Ðŕόφ Ρòđ !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ĵůηё Ùрðǻтé – Ðřορ Ρσδ !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Јμπé Ùρđâťέ – Đřôρ Ρöδ !!! !!! "
                    }
                },
                "Body": {
                    "value": "Halo Infinite's first Drop Pod update has been deployed! \n\nDrop Pods are our quality of life updates that will focus on improving the player experience in Halo Infinite. This Drop Pod brings vehicle balance updates, improvements to the Ranked experience, and multiple key bug fixes. \n\nTo view the full patch notes for this Drop Pod, please visit the Halo Support site (aka.ms/HaloSupport). If you encounter any issues while playing, you may also submit a ticket on the Halo Support site that will go directly to the team for investigation. \n\n",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "První aktualizace Výsadkový modul Halo Infinite byla nasazena! \n\nVýsadkové moduly jsou aktualizace kvality, které se budou zaměřovat na zlepšení zážitku hráčů v Halo Infinite. Přináší aktualizace vyvážení vozidel, vylepšení prostředí hodnocených her a několik důležitých oprav chyb. \n\nPokud si chcete zobrazit všechny poznámky k opravě pro tento výsadkový modul, navštivte prosím web Podpora Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Pokud při hraní narazíte na jakékoli problémy, můžete na webu Podpora Halo odeslat lístek, který se zašle přímo prověřovacímu týmu. \n\n",
                        "da-DK": "Halo Infinites første Drop Pod-opdatering er blevet implementeret! \n\nDrop Pods er vores livskvalitetsopdateringer, der vil fokusere på at forbedre spilleroplevelsen i Halo Infinite. Denne Drop Pod bringer opdateringer af køretøjsbalancen, forbedringer af den rangerede oplevelse og flere vigtige fejlrettelser. \n\nHvis du vil se de fulde patchnoter til denne Drop Pod, skal du besøge Halo-supportwebstedet (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Hvis du støder på problemer, mens du spiller, kan du også indsende en billet på Halo-supportwebstedet, der går direkte til holdet til undersøgelse. \n\n",
                        "de-DE": "Das erste Landungskapsel-Update für Halo Infinite wurde abgesetzt! \n\nLandungskapseln sind Quality-of-Life-Updates, die sich vor allem darauf konzentrieren, das Spielerlebnis von Halo Infinite zu verbessern. Diese Landungskapsel umfasst Anpassungen an der Fahrzeugbalance, Verbesserungen am Ranglistenspiel und diverse Fehlerbehebungen. \n\nDie vollständigen Patchnotes für diese Landungskapsel findest du auf der Halo-Support-Website (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Wenn beim Spielen Probleme auftreten, kannst du auch ein Ticket auf der Halo-Support-Website einreichen. Dieses wird dann direkt an das Team weitergeleitet. \n\n",
                        "el-GR": "Η πρώτη ενημέρωση Drop Pod του Halo Infinite έχει αναπτυχθεί! \n\nΤα Drop Pods είναι ενημερώσεις της ποιότητας ζωής μας που θα επικεντρωθούν στη βελτίωση της εμπειρίας των παικτών στο Halo Infinite. Αυτό το Drop Pod φέρνει ενημερώσεις ισορροπίας οχημάτων, βελτιώσεις στην εμπειρία Κατάταξης και πολλές βασικές διορθώσεις σφαλμάτων. \n\nΓια να δεις τις πλήρεις σημειώσεις αυτού του Drop Pod, επισκέψου τον ιστότοπο υποστήριξης του Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Αν αντιμετωπίσεις οποιοδήποτε πρόβλημα κατά τη διάρκεια του παιχνιδιού, μπορείς επίσης να υποβάλεις ένα αίτημα στην ιστοσελίδα Υποστήριξης του Halo, το οποίο θα πάει απευθείας στην ομάδα για διερεύνηση. \n\n",
                        "es-ES": "¡Ya está disponible la primera actualización de cápsula de Halo Infinite! \n\nEstas cápsulas consisten en actualizaciones vitales centradas en mejorar la experiencia del jugador en Halo Infinite. Esta cápsula ofrece actualizaciones de equilibrio de vehículos, mejoras en la experiencia clasificada y varias correcciones de fallos importantes. \n\nPuedes consultar toda la información sobre el parche de esta cápsula en el sitio web de ayuda de Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Si experimentas algún problema al jugar, también puedes enviar una solicitud al sitio web de ayuda de Halo para que la reciba directamente el equipo de desarrollo. \n\n",
                        "es-MX": "¡Ya implementamos la primera actualización de Cápsula de descenso de Halo Infinite! \n\nLas Cápsulas de descenso son actualizaciones de calidad general que se enfocan en mejorar la experiencia de juego en Halo Infinite. Esta Cápsula de descenso contiene actualizaciones de equilibrio de vehículos, mejoras en la experiencia de las partidas clasificatorias y múltiples correcciones de errores clave. \n\nPara ver las notas completas del parche, visita el sitio de soporte de Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Si encuentras algún problema mientras juegas, también puedes enviar un reporte desde el sitio de soporte de Halo directamente al equipo para que lo investigue. \n\n",
                        "fi-FI": "Halo Infiniten ensimmäinen Drop Pod -päivitys on otettu käyttöön! \n\nDrop Podit ovat pelaajan käyttökokemusta parantavia päivityksiä Halo Infiniteen. Tämä Drop Pod tuo mukanaan päivityksiä ajoneuvojen tasapainoon, parannuksia kilpailulliseen peliin ja useita tärkeitä bugikorjauksia. \n\nJos haluat tarkastella päivityksen sisältöä kokonaisuudessaan, vieraile Halon tukisivustolla (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Jos törmäät ongelmiin pelatessasi, voit tehdä Halon tukisivuston kautta ilmoituksen suoraan tiimille, joka tutkii tilanteen.\n\n",
                        "fr-FR": "La première mise à jour Module de largage de Halo Infinite a été déployée ! \n\nLes Modules de largage constituent nos mises à jour visant à améliorer l'expérience de jeu sur Halo Infinite. Ce module apporte des mises à jour d'équilibrage des véhicules, une optimisation de l'expérience classée ainsi que diverses corrections de bugs majeurs. \n\nPour consulter les notes de version complètes, rendez-vous sur le site d'assistance Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Si vous rencontrez des problèmes en jouant, vous pouvez également envoyer un ticket sur ce site. Il sera directement transmis à nos équipes qui se pencheront sur la question. \n\n",
                        "hu-HU": "Megérkezett a Halo Infinite első Drop Pod frissítése! \n\nA Drop Podok játékminőségi frissítések, amelyek célja a még tökéletesebb Halo Infinite-játékélmény biztosítása. A mostani Drop Pod járműegyensúlyi változásokat, a rangsorolt játékkal kapcsolatos módosításokat és több kulcsfontosságú hibajavítást tartalmaz. \n\nA Drop Pod teljes leírásához keresd fel a Halo támogatási oldalát (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Ha a játék során bármilyen problémába ütközöl, támogatási jegyed a Halo támogatási oldalán is benyújthatod, ahol közvetlenül a támogatási csapathoz kerül kivizsgálásra. \n\n",
                        "it-IT": "Il primo aggiornamento Capsula da sbarco di Halo Infinite è stato schierato sul campo! \n\nLe Capsule da sbarco sono i nostri aggiornamenti sulla qualità della vita, che si concentreranno sul miglioramento dell'esperienza del giocatore in Halo Infinite. Questa Capsula da sbarco contiene aggiornamenti sul bilanciamento dei veicoli, miglioramenti all'esperienza classificata e varie correzioni dei principali bug. \n\nPer visualizzare le note complete della patch di questa Capsula da sbarco, visita il sito Halo Support (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Se riscontri dei problemi durante il gioco, puoi anche inoltrare una segnalazione sul sito Halo Support, che raggiungerà direttamente il team dedicato alle indagini. \n\n",
                        "ja-JP": "『Halo Infinite』の「降下ポッド」アップデート第一弾をリリース! \n\n「降下ポッド」は、『Halo Infinite』のプレイヤー体験を改善することに焦点を置いた QOL 向上アップデートです。今回の「降下ポッド」では、ビークルのバランス変更、ランクありゲームの改善、マルチプレイヤー キーのバグ修正などが行われています。\n\n今回の「降下ポッド」のパッチ ノート全文は、Halo サポート サイト (aka.ms/HaloSupport) でご覧いただけます。プレイ中に問題が発生した場合は、「Halo Support」サイトからチケットを発行してください。チケットは担当チームに直接送られ、調査が行われます。\n\n",
                        "ko-KR": "Halo Infinite의 첫 번째 강하 포드 업데이트가 투하되었습니다! \n\n강하 포드는 여러분의 삶의 질을 위한 업데이트로서 Halo Infinite에서 플레이어의 경험을 개선하는 데 집중되어 있습니다. 이번 강하 포드는 차량 밸런스 업데이트, 랭킹 체험에 대한 개선 및 다수의 주요 버그 수정이 포함되어 있습니다. \n\n이번 강하 포드에 대한 전체 패치 내용을 확인하시려면, Halo 지원 사이트(aka.ms/HaloSupport)에 방문하세요. 플레이 중에 어떤 문제든 발생한 경우, Halo 지원 사이트에 티켓을 제출하면 팀에 바로 전송되어 조사가 진행될 것입니다. \n\n",
                        "nb-NO": "Halo Infinites første droppkapseloppdatering er ute! \n\nDroppkapsler er oppdateringer som fokuserer på å forbedre spillopplevelsen i Halo Infinite. Denne droppkapselen inneholder balanseringer av kjøretøyer, forbedringer av rangert spill og flere viktige feilrettinger. \n\nHvis du vil lese de fullstendige oppdateringsmerknadene for denne droppkapselen, kan du gå til Halo Support-nettstedet (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Hvis du støter på problemer mens du spiller, kan du kontakte Halo Support-nettstedet, der du kommer i kontakt med teamet direkte. \n\n",
                        "nl-NL": "De eerste droppod-update van Halo Infinite is er! \n\nMet droppod-updates verbeteren we de spelervaring in Halo Infinite. Deze droppod optimaliseert de balans van de voertuigen, verbetert het spelen voor het klassement en bevat meerdere belangrijke bugfixes. \n\nLees voor meer info over deze droppod het patchoverzicht op de ondersteuningswebsite van Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Als je tijdens het spelen een probleem ondervindt, kun je op de ondersteuningswebsite van Halo een ticket starten. Onze teams zullen het probleem dan onderzoeken. \n\n",
                        "pl-PL": "Wypuściliśmy pierwszą aktualizację z serii Kapsuły desantowe!\n\nKapsuły desantowe to zbiory usprawnień, które mają ulepszyć jakość rozgrywki w Halo Infinite. Ta aktualizacja poprawia równowagę pojazdów, udoskonala rozgrywki rankingowe i eliminuje wiele kluczowych błędów.\n\nSzczegółowe informacje na temat tej kapsuły desantowej znajdziesz na stronie wsparcia Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Jeśli napotkasz jakiekolwiek problemy podczas gry, prześlij zgłoszenie na tej stronie, a trafi ono bezpośrednio do zespołu, który się mu przyjrzy.\n\n",
                        "pt-BR": "A primeira atualização Drop Pod de Halo Infinite foi implantada! \n\nAs Drop Pods são nossas atualizações de qualidade de vida que se concentrarão em melhorar a experiência do jogador em Halo Infinite. Esta Drop Pod traz atualizações de equilíbrio de veículos, melhorias na experiência ranqueada e várias correções de bugs importantes. \n\nPara ver as notas completas do patch da Drop Pod, visite o site de suporte do Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Se você encontrar algum problema durante o jogo, também poderá enviar um tíquete no site de suporte do Halo que irá diretamente para a equipe para ser investigado. \n\n",
                        "pt-PT": "A primeira atualização de Drop Pod do Halo Infinite foi lançada! \n\nOs Drop Pods são as nossas atualizações de qualidade de vida cujo foco é melhorar a experiência do jogador no Halo Infinite. Este Drop Pod traz melhorias de equilíbrio dos veículos, melhorias na experiência do Ranked e várias correções de erros principais. \n\nPara ver as notas de correção completas para esta atualização, visita o site de apoio do Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Se encontrares algum problema durante o jogo, também podes enviar um pedido no site de apoio do Halo que irá diretamente para a equipa para investigação. \n\n",
                        "ru-RU": "Мы выпустили первую «Десантную капсулу» для Halo Infinite!\n\n«Десантными капсулами» мы называем обновления, благодаря которым в Halo Infinite будут появляться приятные изменения, призванные сделать игру более комфортной. Эта «Десантная капсула» меняет баланс техники, улучшает рейтинговые игры и исправляет множество ошибок.\n\nОзнакомиться с полным описанием этой «Десантной капсулы» можно на сайте службы поддержки Halo (aka.ms/HaloSupport). Если вы столкнётесь с проблемами во время игры, расскажите об этом напрямую нашей команде, отправив сообщение на сайте службы поддержки Halo.\n\n",
                        "sv-SE": "Halo Infinites första kapseluppdatering är här!\n\nKapslar är kvalitetsuppdateringar som fokuserar på att förbättra spelarupplevelsen i Halo Infinite. Den här kapseln innebär balansuppdateringar för fordon, förbättringar av den rankade upplevelsen och flera viktiga buggfixar.\n\nBesök Halo Support-sidan (aka.ms/HaloSupport) för att se all information om den här kapseln. Om du stöter på problem när du spelar kan du öppna ett ärende på Halo Support-sidan så tittar vårt team närmre på det.\n\n",
                        "tr-TR": "Halo Infinite'in ilk Dağıtım Kapsülü güncellemesi yayınlandı! \n\nDağıtım Kapsülleri, Halo Infinite'teki oyuncu deneyimini iyileştirmeye odaklanacak yaşam kalitesi güncellemelerimizdir. Bu Dağıtım Kapsülü ile oyuna araç dengesi güncellemeleri, Dereceli deneyiminde iyileştirmeler ve birden fazla önemli hata düzeltmesi geliyor. \n\nBu Dağıtım Kapsülü'nün yama notlarının tamamını görüntülemek için lütfen Halo Desteği sitesini (aka.ms/HaloSupport) ziyaret edin. Oyun oynarken herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşırsanız Halo Desteği sitesinde bir bilet oluşturabilirsiniz; sorun, incelenmek üzere doğrudan ekibe iletilecektir. \n\n",
                        "zh-CN": "Halo Infinite 的首次空投更新已经推出！\n\n空投更新主要包含我们对游戏质量的改进，专注于提升玩家在 Halo Infinite 中的游戏体验。本次空投带来了载具平衡性调整，改进了排名模式的体验以及多个关键错误修正。\n\n要想查看本次空投更新的完整补丁说明，请访问 Halo Support 网站 (aka.ms/HaloSupport)。如果您在游戏中遇到任何问题，您也可以在 Halo Support 网站中提交票证，我们的团队会进行调查。\n\n",
                        "zh-TW": "Halo Infinite 的首次空投更新已經推出！\n\n空投更新主要放在我們對遊戲品質的改善，專注於提升玩家在 Halo Infinite 中的遊戲體驗。本次空投帶來了載具平衡性調整，改善了排名模式的體驗以及多個關鍵錯誤修正。\n\n要想查看本次空投更新的完整修補說明，請造訪 Halo Support 網站 (aka.ms/HaloSupport)。如果您在遊戲中遇到技術問題，請前往 Halo Support 網站並進行回報，這可以協助我們的團隊調查該問題。\n\n",
                        "qps-ploc": "Нáłо Ĭňƒïπíŧè'ş ƒíŗşτ Ðґöρ Рσδ ųρðåŧę ĥªѕ ъêĕñ δėρľοÿ℮đ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nĎŗõρ Роďŝ дяė ôцř qũάłіτγ òƒ ℓΐƒě υрðдтέѕ ťĥáт ẅΐŀł ƒǿċϋś óй íмρгονιňğ ťћé φľáýěг ĕхрéřΐ℮иċë ΐⁿ Ĥǻľο Ίлƒíñĩŧĕ. Тнïš Ďřσр Ρθδ ьřΐñġš νєніçĺэ ъāłдńćз џφđãťёś, ĭmρŗóν℮мĕňťš ťø ŧĥě Ѓāⁿķèđ е×рэгįёņċ℮, αлđ мΰĺтíрļэ кёý ьůģ ƒίжęš.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\nŤο νΐĕώ ţħέ ƒΰĺľ φдţсћ ņõť℮ѕ ƒŏґ ŧħίѕ Ðґōр Рбð, рłěªşе νíѕϊť ŧћë Ĥáļσ Şμрρσřτ ѕїт℮ (ăκå.mś/ĤаļôŠûрроřţ). Іƒ γòű ëпçòûлţέя ǻňу ïśŝџěѕ ẅĥìĺє ρĺàỳϊŋġ, уøџ mäÿ áℓšò šųъmīт ă τι¢κêŧ θη ţн℮ Нàľø Ѕυрρбřτ śіŧз тħåť ẁΐļŀ ĝó δĩґ℮¢τļỳ ťó τнě тéâm ƒσг ίⁿνēşŧíģǻтįőп.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\n",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ĥаĺò Īŋƒĩñïŧέ'ś ƒįŗšŧ Ðгŏρ Ρōď ûрðāťэ нâś ьĕ℮ņ đ℮рŀσуэď!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nÐяŏр Ρöδš ăѓέ οųŗ qцāłįťý öƒ ĺïƒĕ ϋρðαтęş ţђăτ ẁîŀŀ ƒőсϋŝ óή ΐmрŕονíⁿğ ťн℮ ρľдỳέŕ éхρĕříĕņĉэ ĭⁿ Ήдļö Īņƒїŋįтε. Ťħïŝ Ðŗøр Ρσð ьŕιήġѕ νěĥі¢łě ьãĺãņčë űρđàŧ℮š, ίmρѓòνємëňţŝ ţθ ţђє Ŗăňќёð è×ρęґΐėης℮, άпď müĺтϊрĺē ķėγ вůģ ƒΐ×éś.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\nТб νĭěш ţћє ƒüľľ ρǻťċĥ ηòтеš ƒόŕ ţĥïş Ďřоρ Ρøδ, рŀεąśē νїšìτ τħĕ Нåĺô Śùррōřт şĩτĕ (ǻќà.mş/НăℓōŠūрφоŕť). Ĭƒ ÿσů еήćöùñţĕґ ăñŷ įŝśΰėš шħĭłē рļǻуĩŋğ, ўôù мªŷ άĺşǿ ŝΰъmīŧ å ŧїсķèτ öñ тĥě Ĥåĺǿ Şüррöґť ѕїťė τђαт ẅīłļ ğō ðīґěстĺÿ ťó ţћě ťęăм ƒόř íŋνεśťíĝãţĩôņ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\n",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ηãĺό Ϊпƒįпіτз'š ƒìŗѕτ Đяõρ Ρŏð ύρðäтε ћаѕ вéêп ďęφℓόуэδ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nÐřōρ Ρθđş ªяë σΰř qυäļīţý òƒ ĺΐƒě ūρďãτêş ťћǻτ ẅιłℓ ƒόςцş σп ϊмрřόνϊñģ ŧħё ρļàўёŕ êхφèгîеήçё įл Ĥăℓó İŉƒĩήιŧё. Тĥίš Ðѓôφ Ρоď вŕϊŋğѕ νеĥīċľ℮ ъåłãйĉε ůрđªτεѕ, ïмρяòνëмèŋтś τô ţнĕ Řάňķёδ ℮жрëгïęņç℮, аиð mμŀţίφľё ĸэў ьůğ ƒιж℮ş.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\nŦό νįëŵ ŧħε ƒυļł φдтĉћ ńôтĕś ƒбŕ τħϊś Đřòρ Рøδ, ρľèâšє νιѕїť ŧн℮ Нâłσ Śűφρóřţ ѕīťĕ (âκā.мŝ/ĤåŀθŚųррöŗť). Іƒ ŷòù ēņĉǿųŉťеŗ âπÿ īşşμзŝ ẃнιłε ρℓäÿїиĝ, ŷóü mдỳ ªłѕõ ŝμъмîŧ å тϊĉќэŧ οή ŧĥ℮ Нáŀø Ѕμрφθŗŧ ѕіţε τħǻţ ẃīľℓ ğô đïřеčτľў ţо ŧћ℮ ť℮ам ƒöř íńνėѕťιğãŧίõй.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\n"
                    }
                },
                "ArticleImage": {
                    "Width": 1920,
                    "Height": 1080,
                    "Path": "news/Season2/GameUpdates/DropPod1_MOTD.jpg"
                },
                "ArticleActions": [
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Visit Halo Support",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Navštívit Podporu Halo",
                                "da-DK": "Besøg Halo Support",
                                "de-DE": "Besuche den Halo-Support",
                                "el-GR": "Μετάβαση στην υποστήριξη του Halo",
                                "es-ES": "Visita la página web de asistencia de Halo",
                                "es-MX": "Visita la página de soporte de Halo",
                                "fi-FI": "Vieraile Halon tukisivustolla",
                                "fr-FR": "Vers l’assistance Halo",
                                "hu-HU": "Keresd fel a Halo ügyféltámogatási oldalt",
                                "it-IT": "Visita Halo Support",
                                "ja-JP": "Halo サポートに移動",
                                "ko-KR": "Halo 고객 지원 방문",
                                "nb-NO": "Gå til Halos støttefunksjon",
                                "nl-NL": "Ga naar Halo-ondersteuning",
                                "pl-PL": "Odwiedź stronę pomocy technicznej gry Halo",
                                "pt-BR": "Acesse o Suporte de Halo",
                                "pt-PT": "Visita o apoio do Halo",
                                "ru-RU": "Посетить службу поддержки Halo",
                                "sv-SE": "Besök Halo-supporten",
                                "tr-TR": "Halo Desteği'ni ziyaret edin",
                                "zh-CN": "访问 Halo Support",
                                "zh-TW": "造訪 Halo Support",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vїѕîŧ Нāĺб Śùрφøřţ !!! !!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Vĭŝìτ Ήåĺǿ Śµρрôяτ !!! !!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Vιšīť Ндļø Şΰφφǿŕτ !!! !!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll take you to the Halo Support site.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na web Podpora Halo.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi tager dig til Halo Support-siden.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zur Website von Halo Support weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε βοηθήσουμε να μεταβείς στον ιστότοπο υποστήριξης του Halo.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a la página web de asistencia de Halo.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos al sitio de soporte de Halo.",
                                "fi-FI": "Viemme sinut Halon tukisivustolle.",
                                "fr-FR": "Vous arriverez au site d'assistance Halo.",
                                "hu-HU": "A Halo támogatási oldalára viszünk.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo sul sito Halo Support.",
                                "ja-JP": "詳細については、Halo サポートのサイトをご覧ください。",
                                "ko-KR": "Halo 고객 지원 사이트로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til Halos støtteside.",
                                "nl-NL": "We brengen je naar de website van de Halo-ondersteuning.",
                                "pl-PL": "Zabierzemy cię na stronę pomocy technicznej Halo.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao site de Suporte de Halo.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao site de apoio do Halo.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем для вас сайт службы поддержки Halo.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Halo-supportens webbsida.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi Halo Desteği sitesine aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们将带您前往 Halo Support 网站。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會帶您前往 Halo Support 網站。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Шз'ļĺ ťâκё ўõŭ ţø τħě Ηáľó Śúρρóяτ şĭτέ. !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Шĕ'ļł ţдќз ŷóų тő ţнз Ħâŀǿ Ŝùφφǿřť šįтё. !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẃε'ℓľ ŧαĸĕ ÿōϋ ŧø τнэ Ήäℓø Šϋррōѓτ śїŧĕ. !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://aka.ms/HaloInfiniteUpdate"
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Follow @HaloSupport on Twitter",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Sledujte @HaloSupport na Twitteru",
                                "da-DK": "Følg @HaloSupport på Twitter",
                                "de-DE": "@HaloSupport auf Twitter folgen",
                                "el-GR": "Ακολούθησε το @HaloSupport στο Twitter",
                                "es-ES": "Sigue a @HaloSupport en Twitter",
                                "es-MX": "Sigue a @HaloSupport en Twitter",
                                "fi-FI": "Seuraa @HaloSupport-tiliä Twitterissä",
                                "fr-FR": "Suivre @HaloSupport sur Twitter",
                                "hu-HU": "Kövesd a @HaloSupport fiókot Twitteren",
                                "it-IT": "Segui @HaloSupport su Twitter",
                                "ja-JP": "ツイッターで @HaloSupport をフォローする",
                                "ko-KR": "Twitter에서 @HaloSupport를 팔로우하십시오",
                                "nb-NO": "Følg @HaloSupport på Twitter",
                                "nl-NL": "Volg @HaloSupport op Twitter",
                                "pl-PL": "Obserwuj @HaloSupport na Twitterze",
                                "pt-BR": "Siga @HaloSupport no Twitter",
                                "pt-PT": "Segue @HaloSupport no Twitter",
                                "ru-RU": "Читать @HaloSupport в Twitter",
                                "sv-SE": "Följ @HaloSupport på Twitter",
                                "tr-TR": "@HaloSupport'u Twitter'da takip edin",
                                "zh-CN": "在推特上关注 @HaloSupport",
                                "zh-TW": "在 Twitter 上跟隨 @HaloSupport",
                                "qps-ploc": "₣őŀŀóŵ @ΗàľóŠũρρòřţ ǿŉ Ţẅĩŧтзя !!! !!! !!!",
                                "qps-ploca": "₣όŀŀőŵ @ĦāĺοŠμφρбřť øń Тẅîţţèґ !!! !!! !!!",
                                "qps-plocm": "₣ŏłľθш @ĤăłøŠűрφояŧ ōи Ţẅĭŧτэř !!! !!! !!!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to our @HaloSupport Twitter account.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na náš twitterový účet @HaloSupport.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi tager dig til vores @HaloSupport Twitter-konto.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zu unserem @HaloSupport Twitter-Konto weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στον λογαριασμό μας @HaloSupport στο Twitter.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a nuestra cuenta de asistencia @HaloSupport en Twitter.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a nuestra cuenta de soporte de Halo en Twitter.",
                                "fi-FI": "Viemme sinut @HaloSupport-tilillemme Twitterissä.",
                                "fr-FR": "Vous arriverez sur notre compte Twitter @HaloSupport.",
                                "hu-HU": "A @HaloSupport Twitter-fiókunkhoz viszünk.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo al nostro account Twitter @HaloSupport.",
                                "ja-JP": "詳細については、Twitter の @HaloSupport アカウントをご覧ください。",
                                "ko-KR": "자세한 내용을 보실 수 있도록 본사의 @HaloSupport Twitter 계정으로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til @HaloSupport-kontoen på Twitter.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar ons Twitter-account @HaloSupport.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię na nasze konto @HaloSupport na Twitterze.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você à nossa conta do Twitter @HaloSupport.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te à nossa conta @HaloSupport no Twitter.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем для вас нашу ленту @HaloSupport в Twitter.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till vårt Twitter-konto @HaloSupport.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi @HaloSupport Twitter hesabımıza aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们将带您前往 @HaloSupport Twitter 账号。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會帶您前往我們的 @HaloSupport Twitter 帳戶。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ŵē'ļļ ъѓìήğ ўǿů ŧõ θùг @ĤăłôŠűφрôѓť Ŧωîťťєř άсĉóũŉţ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "Щë'ļŀ вгįŋĝ γоũ ŧõ όűѓ @ĦàĺŏŚџφφθяŧ Ťẅįţťęг дčсóūиτ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ŵ℮'ľļ ъяίлġ уøů ţö ôύř @ΗàℓōЅϋρφöřτ Ťẅΐŧŧěґ äсčǿμйт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://twitter.com/HaloSupport"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "ShortHeadline": {
                    "value": "The Last Sky Marshal - VOTE NOW!",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Poslední nebeský maršál – HLASUJTE!",
                        "da-DK": "Den sidste himmelmarskal - STEM NU!",
                        "de-DE": "The Last Sky Marshal – JETZT WÄHLEN!",
                        "el-GR": "Ο τελευταίος σερίφης του ουρανού - ΨΗΦΙΣΕ ΤΩΡΑ!",
                        "es-ES": "The Last Sky Marshal: ¡VOTA AHORA!",
                        "es-MX": "The Last Sky Marshal - ¡VOTA AHORA!",
                        "fi-FI": "Viimeinen taivasmarsalkka - ÄÄNESTÄ NYT!",
                        "fr-FR": "The Last Sky Marshal : VOTEZ MAINTENANT !",
                        "hu-HU": "Az utolsó légi marsall – SZAVAZZ MOST!",
                        "it-IT": "L'ultimo sceriffo del cielo - VOTA SUBITO!",
                        "ja-JP": "最後のスカイ マーシャル - 今すぐ投票!",
                        "ko-KR": "마지막 항공 경비대 - 지금 투표하십시오!",
                        "nb-NO": "Den siste himmelmarskalken – STEM NÅ!",
                        "nl-NL": "The Last Sky Marshal - STEM NU!",
                        "pl-PL": "Ostatni podniebny marszałek – GŁOSUJ TERAZ!",
                        "pt-BR": "O Último Marechal do Céu: VOTE AGORA!",
                        "pt-PT": "O Último Sky Marshal – VOTA JÁ!",
                        "ru-RU": "«Последний воздушный маршал» — ГОЛОСУЙТЕ!",
                        "sv-SE": "Den sista himmelsmarskalken – RÖSTA NU!",
                        "tr-TR": "Son Hava Mareşali - ŞİMDİ OY VERİN!",
                        "zh-CN": "《最后的空军将领》 - 快来投票！",
                        "zh-TW": "《最後的空軍將領》 - 快來投票！",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ŧħё Ļãśť Ŝĸý Μäŗŝндľ - VΩŢ∑ ПÕẄ! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ŧħé Ļāšτ Ŝκý Мдяśнāł - VŎТЕ ∏ΩŴ! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ţħє £άŝτ Ŝќў Маŗśђåľ - VΟΤĒ ŅОẄ! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                },
                "FullHeadline": {
                    "value": "The Last Sky Marshal - VOTE NOW!",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Poslední nebeský maršál – HLASUJTE!",
                        "da-DK": "Den sidste himmelmarskal - STEM NU!",
                        "de-DE": "The Last Sky Marshal – JETZT WÄHLEN!",
                        "el-GR": "Ο τελευταίος σερίφης του ουρανού - ΨΗΦΙΣΕ ΤΩΡΑ!",
                        "es-ES": "The Last Sky Marshal: ¡VOTA AHORA!",
                        "es-MX": "The Last Sky Marshal - ¡VOTA AHORA!",
                        "fi-FI": "Viimeinen taivasmarsalkka - ÄÄNESTÄ NYT!",
                        "fr-FR": "The Last Sky Marshal : VOTEZ MAINTENANT !",
                        "hu-HU": "Az utolsó légi marsall – SZAVAZZ MOST!",
                        "it-IT": "L'ultimo sceriffo del cielo - VOTA SUBITO!",
                        "ja-JP": "最後のスカイ マーシャル - 今すぐ投票!",
                        "ko-KR": "마지막 항공 경비대 - 지금 투표하십시오!",
                        "nb-NO": "Den siste himmelmarskalken – STEM NÅ!",
                        "nl-NL": "The Last Sky Marshal - STEM NU!",
                        "pl-PL": "Ostatni podniebny marszałek – GŁOSUJ TERAZ!",
                        "pt-BR": "O Último Marechal do Céu: VOTE AGORA!",
                        "pt-PT": "O Último Sky Marshal – VOTA JÁ!",
                        "ru-RU": "«Последний воздушный маршал» — ГОЛОСУЙТЕ!",
                        "sv-SE": "Den sista himmelsmarskalken – RÖSTA NU!",
                        "tr-TR": "Son Hava Mareşali - ŞİMDİ OY VERİN!",
                        "zh-CN": "《最后的空军将领》 - 快来投票！",
                        "zh-TW": "《最後的空軍將領》 - 快來投票！",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ŧħё Ļãśť Ŝĸý Μäŗŝндľ - VΩŢ∑ ПÕẄ! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ŧħé Ļāšτ Ŝκý Мдяśнāł - VŎТЕ ∏ΩŴ! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ţħє £άŝτ Ŝќў Маŗśђåľ - VΟΤĒ ŅОẄ! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                },
                "Body": {
                    "value": "Fracture: Entrenched brings with it a new story set in the dieselpunk-themed universe where its direction and outcomes are decided by you! \n\nHead over to Halo Waypoint to check out the first chapter of The Last Sky Marshal, where a desperate final offense is mounted on the Moon by Commander Kolby, who leads the UNSC's astro rocket-propelled heroes against the irradiated horrors of the Covenant. \n\nAt the end of each chapter, a choice will be posed that will affect the next part of the story and its ultimate outcome. That choice - and the fate of humanity - is in your hands! \n\n",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Trhlina: Opevnění s sebou přináší nový příběh zasazený do vesmíru s dieselpunkovou tématikou, ve kterém vy sami rozhodujete, jak se bude příběh vyvíjet a jak dopadne! \n\nZamiřte na Halo Waypoint a ponořte se do první kapitoly Posledního nebeského maršála. Komandér Kolby se v ní připravuje na poslední zoufalý útok a vede hrdiny UNSC s astroraketovým pohonem proti radioaktivním hrůzostrašným příšerám Smečky. \n\nNa konci každé kapitoly bude představena volba, která ovlivní další část příběhu a jeho konec. A tato volba – osud lidstva – je ve vašich rukách! \n\n",
                        "da-DK": "Fracture: Entrenched bringer en ny historie med sig, der foregår i dieselpunk-universet, hvor dens retning og resultater afgøres af dig! \n\nGå over til Halo Waypoint for at tjekke det første kapitel af The Last Sky Marshal, hvor et desperat sidste angreb bliver indledt på månen af kommandør Kolby, der leder UNSC's astroraketdrevne helte mod Covenants bestrålede rædsler. \n\nI slutningen af hvert kapitel vil der blive stillet et valg, der vil påvirke den næste del af historien og dens endelige resultat. Dette valg – og menneskehedens skæbne – er i dine hænder! \n\n",
                        "de-DE": "Gemeinsam mit „Fraktur: Eingegraben“ erscheint eine neue Story in einem Dieselpunk-Universum, deren Verlauf du bestimmst! \n\nBesuche Halo Waypoint, um dir das erste Kapitel von „The Last Sky Marshal“ anzusehen, in dem Commander Kolby eine verzweifelte letzte Offensive auf dem Mond startet. Er führt die raketengetriebenen UNSC-Helden gegen die strahlenverseuchten Monster der Allianz. \n\nAm Ende jedes Kapitels wirst du vor eine Entscheidung gestellt, die den nächsten Teil der Story und das Finale entscheidet. Die Wahl – und das Schicksal der Menschheit – liegt in deinen Händen! \n\n",
                        "el-GR": "Το Fracture: Entrenched φέρνει μαζί του μια νέα ιστορία στο dieselpunk σύμπαν, την κατεύθυνση και τα αποτελέσματά της οποίας αποφασίζεις εσύ! \n\nΠήγαινε στο Σημείο πορείας Halo για να δεις το πρώτο κεφάλαιο του Ο Τελευταίος Σερίφης του Ουρανού, όπου οργανώνεται μια απελπισμένη τελική επίθεση στη Σελήνη από τον Διοικητή Κόλμπι, τον ηγέτη των αστροπυραυλοκίνητων ηρώων της UNSC ενάντια στην ακτινοβολημένη φρίκη του Συμφώνου. \n\nΣτο τέλος κάθε κεφαλαίου, θα τίθεται μια επιλογή που θα επηρεάσει το επόμενο μέρος της ιστορίας και την τελική έκβασή της. Αυτή η επιλογή - και η μοίρα της ανθρωπότητας - είναι στα χέρια σου! \n\n",
                        "es-ES": "Fracture: Atrincherados trae consigo una nueva historia ambientada en el universo de temática dieselpunk en la que tú decides la dirección y sus resultados. \n\nDirígete a Halo Waypoint para ver el primer capítulo de The Last Sky Marshal, donde el comandante Kolby monta una desesperada ofensiva final en la Luna liderando a los héroes de la UNSC propulsados por cohetes contra los horrores irradiados del Covenant. \n\nAl final de cada capítulo, se planteará una elección que afectará a la siguiente parte de la historia y al resultado final. ¡Tanto la elección como el destino de la humanidad están en tus manos! \n\n",
                        "es-MX": "Fractura: Atrincherados trae consigo una nueva historia ambientada en un universo de temática dieselpunk, ¡donde el desarrollo y sus consecuencias las determinas tú! \n\nEntra a Halo Waypoint para ver el primer capítulo de The Last Sky Marshal. El Comandante Kolby monta una desesperada ofensiva final en la luna al mando de héroes propulsados por cohetes espaciales del UNSC contra los horrores irradiados del Covenant. \n\nAl final de cada capítulo, se planteará una elección que afectará la siguiente parte de la historia y su resultado final. ¡Esa elección, y el destino de la humanidad, están en tus manos! \n\n",
                        "fi-FI": "Murtuma: Juurtunut tuo mukanaan uuden dieselpunk-teemaiseen maailmaan sijoittuvan tarinan, jonka kulku ja päätös ovat sinun käsissäsi! \n\nSuuntaa Halo Waypointiin ja tutustu Viimeisen taivasmarsalkan ensimmäiseen lukuun, jossa komentaja Kolby lähettää UNSC:n rakettisankarit epätoivoiseen viimeiseen hyökkäykseen Covenantin säteilytettyjä hirvityksiä vastaan. \n\nJokaisen luvun lopussa on valinta, joka vaikuttaa tarinan seuraavaan osaan ja sen lopulliseen päätökseen. Valinta ja ihmiskunnan kohtalo ovat käsissäsi! \n\n",
                        "fr-FR": "Fracture : Retranchement apporte une nouvelle histoire se déroulant dans un univers rétrofuturiste où vos choix impactent directement le scénario ! \n\nRendez-vous sur Halo Waypoint pour découvrir le premier chapitre de The Last Sky Marshal, où un assaut final désespéré est lancé sur la Lune par le commandant Kolby, qui dirige les héros astropropulsés de l'UNSC contre des abominations covenantes irradiées. \n\nÀ la fin de chaque chapitre, un choix déterminera la prochaine partie de l'histoire, et donc son dénouement. Et ce choix, à l'instar du destin de l'humanité, est entre vos mains ! \n\n",
                        "hu-HU": "A Töredék: Lövészárkok olyan dieselpunk témájú világba vezet, ahol az univerzum sorsának irányát és végkimenetelét te döntöd el. \n\nIrány a Halo Waypoint oldala, ahol megnézheted Az utolsó légi marsall első fejezetét, amelyben Kolby parancsnok végső, elkeseredett rohamra indul a hold megszerzéséért. A Szövetség sugárzással életre keltett rémségei ellen az UNSC rakétahajtású hősei szállnak harcba. \n\nAz egyes fejezetek végén olyan döntést kell meghoznod, amely hatással lesz a történet következő részére és a teljes végkimenetelre is. A döntés – és az emberiség sorsa – a te kezedben van! \n\n",
                        "it-IT": "Fracture: Entrenched introduce una nuova storia ambientata nell'universo a tema diesel-punk, in cui sarai tu a decidere lo svolgimento e il finale! \n\nVai su Halo Waypoint per dare un'occhiata al primo capitolo di L'ultimo sceriffo del cielo, nel quale il Comandante Kolby, alla testa di una squadra UNSC di eroi muniti di razzi spaziali, lancia un disperato attacco finale contro gli orrori dilaganti dei Covenant. \n\nAlla fine di ogni capitolo, dovrai compiere una scelta che influenzerà il successivo svolgimento della storia e il suo esito finale. Questa scelta e il destino stesso dell'umanità sono nelle tue mani! \n\n",
                        "ja-JP": "「フラクチャー: エントレンチト」は、ディーゼル パンクをテーマにした新たな物語。その成り行きと結末はあなたの手によって決まります!\n\n『Halo Waypoint』で、「最後のスカイ マーシャル」のチャプター 1 をその目で確かめよう。コマンダー コルビーは、宇宙ロケットを操る UNSC の英雄たちを率いて、迫りくるコヴナントの脅威に立ち向かうため月面で決死の最後の攻防を繰り広げる。\n\n各チャプターの終わりには、物語の次のパートとその最終的な結末に影響を与える選択が提示されます。その選択、そして人類の命運は、あなたの手に委ねられています! \n\n",
                        "ko-KR": "균열: 참호는 디젤펑크 테마의 세계관을 무대로 한 새로운 스토리 세트를 제공합니다. 스토리의 방향과 결과는 여러분이 결정합니다! \n\nHalo Waypoint로 이동하여 '마지막 항공 경비대'의 첫 챕터를 확인하십시오. 달에서 콜비 사령관이 공포스러운 코버넌트에 대항하여 UNSC의 우주 로켓 추진 경비대를 이끌고 마지막 공격을 가합니다. \n\n각 챕터의 마지막마다, 다음 이야기와 전체적인 결과에 영향을 미치게 될 선택을 해야 할 수 있습니다. 이 선택과 인류의 운명은 여러분에게 달려 있습니다! \n\n",
                        "nb-NO": "Brudd: Forskanset forteller en ny historie fra dieselpunk-universet der det som skjer avgjøres av deg! \n\nSett kursen mot Halo Waypoint for å sjekke ut det første kapittelet i Den siste himmelmarskalken, der et desperat siste angrep mot månen utføres av kommandant Kolby, som leder UNSCs astrorakett-helter mot Covenants grusomheter. \n\nPå slutten av hvert kapittel får du et valg som vil påvirke neste del av historien og det endelige utfallet. Dette valget, og menneskehetens skjebne, ligger i dine hender! \n\n",
                        "nl-NL": "Fracture: Entrenched komt met een nieuw verhaal in het dieselpunk-universum, waarin jij de verhaallijn en de afloop bepaalt. \n\nGa naar Halo Waypoint voor het eerste hoofdstuk van 'The Last Sky Marshal', waarin met stuwrakketten uitgeruste UNSC-helden onder leiding van Commander Kolby de maan proberen te ontdoen van het Covenant-gevaar. \n\nNa elk hoofdstuk moet je een keuze maken die gevolgen heeft voor het volgende deel van het verhaal en de uiteindelijke afloop. Kies zorgvuldig, want het lot van de mensheid ligt in jouw handen! \n\n",
                        "pl-PL": "Wydarzenie Fracture: Okopani wprowadza nową historię osadzoną w dieselpunkowym uniwersum – a o jej przebiegu i wyniku decydujesz ty!\n\nZajrzyj na Halo Waypoint, by zapoznać się z pierwszym rozdziałem historii Ostatni podniebny marszałek. Dowiedz się więcej o desperackiej ofensywie na księżyc, podczas której komandor Kolby poprowadził astrorakietowych bohaterów UNSC do walki z napromieniowanymi potworami Przymierza.\n\nPod koniec każdego rozdziału staniesz przed wyborem, który wpłynie na kolejną część historii i jej ostateczny wynik. Pamiętaj: losy ludzkości są w twoich rękach!\n\n",
                        "pt-BR": "Fracture: Entrincheirado traz consigo uma nova história ambientada no universo com tema dieselpunk, onde sua direção e resultados são decididos por você! \n\nDirija-se ao Halo Waypoint para conferir o primeiro capítulo de O Último Marechal do Céu, onde uma ofensiva final desesperada é montada na Lua pelo Comandante Kolby, que lidera os heróis movidos a foguetes-astro do UNSC contra os irradiados horrores do Covenant. \n\nAo final de cada capítulo, será feita uma escolha que afetará a próxima parte da história e seu resultado final. Essa escolha, e o destino da humanidade, está em suas mãos! \n\n",
                        "pt-PT": "O evento Fratura: Entrincheirado traz consigo uma nova história no universo com o tema dieselpunk onde a respetiva direção e resultados são decididos por ti! \n\nAcede ao Halo Waypoint para veres o primeiro capítulo de O Último Sky Marshal, onde é montada uma ofensiva final desesperada na lua pelo Comandante Kolby, que lidera os heróis movidos por astrofoguetes do UNSC contra os horrores irradiados do Covenant. \n\nNo final de cada capítulo, será apresentada uma escolha que vai afetar a próxima parte da história e o seu resultado final. Essa escolha – e o destino da humanidade – está nas tuas mãos! \n\n",
                        "ru-RU": "Событие «Разлом: Неистребимые» рассказывает новую историю, действие которой разворачивается во вселенной, созданной в стиле дизельпанк. Развитие сюжета и развязку определите вы сами!\n\nПосетите сайт Halo Waypoint, чтобы прочитать первую главу повести «Последний воздушный маршал», в которой командующий Колби руководит последней отчаянной попыткой реактивного отряда звёздных героев ККОН дать бой радиоактивным чудовищам Ковенанта на Луне.\n\nВ конце каждой главы вам предложат сделать выбор, который повлияет на события следующей и определит исход повествования. Судьба человечества в ваших руках!\n\n",
                        "sv-SE": "Spricka: Befäst kommer med en ny berättelse i ett dieselpunkuniversum där berättelsens riktning och slut avgörs av dig!\n\nBesök Halo Waypoint för att se första kapitlet av Den sista himmelsmarskalken, där befälhavare Kolby leder UNSC:s raketdrivna hjältar i en sista desperat offensiv mot Förbundets radioaktiva fasor.\n\nI slutet av varje kapitel får du ett val som påverkar nästa del av berättelsen, och hur den till sist slutar. Valet – och mänsklighetens öde – vilar i dina händer!\n\n",
                        "tr-TR": "Çatlak: Sağlamlaştırılmış, gidişatını ve sonuçlarını sizin kararlarınızın belirlediği, dieselpunk temalı evrende geçen yeni bir hikâyeyi sizlere sunuyor! \n\nSon Hava Mareşali'nin ilk bölümüne göz atmak için Halo Waypoint'e gidin. Bu bölümde, UNSC'nin roket güdümlü uzay kahramanlarına Covenant'ın radyasyon etkisindeki korkutucu güçlerine karşı liderlik eden Komutan Kolby tarafından Ay'a yapılan son bir umutsuz saldırı anlatılıyor. \n\nHer bölümün sonunda hikâyenin bir sonraki bölümünü ve nihai sonucunu etkileyecek bir seçim yapılacak. Bu seçim ve insanlığın kaderi sizin elinizde! \n\n",
                        "zh-CN": "“裂隙事件：根深蒂固”带来了以柴油朋克主题宇宙为背景的新故事，剧情走向与结局都将由各位决定！\n\n前往 Halo Waypoint 阅读《最后的空军将领》第一章。科尔比指挥官在月球上不顾一切发起了最终进攻，率领 UNSC 的星际喷射装英雄对抗星盟带来的辐射恐怖。\n\n在每一章的结尾都会出现一个抉择，影响下一阶段的剧情及最终结局。而这一个抉择... 乃至人类的命运... 都掌握在您的手中！ \n\n",
                        "zh-TW": "「斷裂：根深蒂固」帶來了以柴油龐克主題宇宙為背景的新故事，劇情走向與結局都將由各位決定！\n\n前往 Halo Waypoint 閱讀《最後的空軍將領》第一章。Kolby 指揮官在月球上不顧一切發起了最終進攻，率領 UNSC 的星際噴射裝英雄對抗星盟帶來的輻射恐怖。\n\n在每一章的結尾都會出現一個抉擇，影響下一階段的劇情及最終結局。而這一個抉擇... 乃至人類的命運... 都掌握在您的手中！ \n\n",
                        "qps-ploc": "₣řǻćţϋŗě: Èήťřеŉсн℮ď ъѓіņġŝ ẁïţħ ΐť ă ņēẅ śτôřу ŝєť ιй тĥê δĭέŝέĺрüлк-ťћёмэđ ΰŋινєґśė ẃħёгě ΐŧş đîŗєĉтìσп ąñδ оūťċǿмéś áѓĕ ðĕçįðēð ъÿ ÿǿú!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nΗęáð σνэř ţσ Ĥąŀó Шдўрøīиτ тŏ ćнєĉķ θϋт тħε ƒιґŝť çħâρţěŕ óƒ Ţĥė Łāśт Şкỳ Μàѓśħаľ, ẁħěŕĕ д ďéśрέяãтę ƒĩиαľ òƒƒєńšэ îŝ мóџńт℮đ σñ тĥ℮ Мøøⁿ вγ €ǿmmàπđĕŗ Ķσľьý, ώђő ŀεαďš τĥĕ ÚЛŞĈ'ś άşτяб řǿćķεţ-ρѓőрěľĺέδ ћеґôэš áğаїńśт ţнé іřŕдðîąţєð ħóŕгσґš őƒ ţђę Ċбνěήáñţ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nĄŧ ţђе έиđ оƒ èąĉђ čĥâφťэŕ, å čħôīćè ẃįłľ вё ρǿśëð ţћåτ ẃìļĺ ąƒƒēćт ţĥè ňёжť φªгť ǿƒ τћę ѕţòřý äņđ ΐťš ŭłτίmäŧè όůţćőмз. Ŧћāт ĉћøîċê - âήδ τħĕ ƒåт℮ ŏƒ ĥџmªńìтỳ - ϊş ìⁿ ỳòúŕ ђáиđś!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\n",
                        "qps-ploca": "₣řã¢ţцяě: Єптŗěňčћēδ вґίпĝš ŵìţн ιτ ã ήéш šţόŗў şěτ ιή ţђē đïеşëĺρµйк-ťђêмэδ úñĭνèгşè ŵħεŗє ίτš ďϊяēςţíøń åŉď øüŧčοмέş āґë δёčĭδέď вγ уŏυ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nΉęąδ òνêя ŧθ Ĥǻłǿ Ẅąỳφöīηŧ το ćћêсĸ õũť тнè ƒїŗşŧ ĉħąрŧэґ óƒ Τħě Ŀàśт Šķγ Μǻřśħăł, ẃħєге ǻ ďёśρ℮ґªťз ƒîńαł σƒƒéπšε íš mòūпτëď õŉ тћè Мóои вý Ćŏмmăήδêŕ Кόľъý, ώђб ļěäďś ŧђė ŮŃЅČ'ѕ ǻśťгō ґõсκ℮ŧ-ρŗσρėĺŀеð ĥęѓǿёś ªģάїпšŧ ťĥе ïŕґǻđîατєđ ђоřŕőѓś οƒ ťнė Çöνęйąητ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nÂт τђê èŋδ ŏƒ εа¢ĥ çħåрťєг, α čђôі¢ę ŵîĺļ вê ρòśęδ ŧћáţ ẁίŀļ дƒƒèćť τћĕ ⁿєжť рāгť ǿƒ τђę śţбřу áńđ ΐťѕ űĺťιmάтę ōũτĉомέ. Ţħат çћŏįςė - ªπď ŧĥε ƒāţ℮ оƒ ħùmåπįţŷ - ίŝ īп ýöύŕ ĥαиđş!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\n",
                        "qps-plocm": "₣яαćţůřè: Έŉŧяĕηςĥèδ ъяīήğŝ ẁϊτн îŧ ä ñĕẁ šţøяγ šěţ īή τħě δìêš℮ľрūиķ-ŧћęмέδ µήĭνеѓšе ẁнèřĕ ìтş ďïгė¢ŧįŏπ ãŋδ оϋţ¢θmėś âŗє ðêċïďęð ву ÿóũ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nĤзáδ ōνèґ ťσ Наℓö Ẅªýрǿĩйŧ τö ċħé¢ĸ öμτ τнэ ƒϊřšţ çнäρţεř ôƒ Ţђē Ľάśτ Ŝќŷ Μаřŝĥǻļ, ωнĕгē ά δёśρéŕàтэ ƒįпåł õƒƒĕŋšè їŝ môüŋтęδ ǿň τĥě Мσőη вỳ Ċôмmªņðèŗ Ķбℓьỳ, ẅнθ ľ℮àðş ţĥє ŬŇŚĊ'ŝ άšτŕő ґöčķέт-рřόрєľľεð ћèґôεś ªģǻĭπšŧ тнë ĩřŗáďîäťēď ĥōřřõřş øƒ τĥę Ĉŏνęиąлт.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nĀť ťћě èлď θƒ еåсħ ςћăрťěř, á ćћóіςё шїĺł вē роśеď ţћàŧ ŵìŀŀ ªƒƒ℮ćť τћē йěхτ φåřţ ōƒ ťнę śŧθŗý άлđ ïτş üℓţĭmάťė ουτčóмê. Ťĥåτ ¢ħòίćě - длď тнέ ƒάţę óƒ нµмăиΐτγ - іš īŋ γóûґ ћáⁿďš!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\n"
                    }
                },
                "ArticleImage": {
                    "Width": 1920,
                    "Height": 1080,
                    "Path": "news/Season2/Events/Entrenched_Title_MOTD.jpg"
                },
                "ArticleActions": [
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Vote on Halo Waypoint",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Hlasovat na Halo Waypointu",
                                "da-DK": "Stem på Halo Waypoint",
                                "de-DE": "Auf Halo Waypoint abstimmen",
                                "el-GR": "Ψήφισε στο Halo Waypoint",
                                "es-ES": "Vota en Halo Waypoint",
                                "es-MX": "Votar en Halo Waypoint",
                                "fi-FI": "Äänestä Halo Waypointissa",
                                "fr-FR": "Voter sur Halo Waypoint",
                                "hu-HU": "Szavazás a Halo Waypoint oldalon",
                                "it-IT": "Vota su Halo Waypoint",
                                "ja-JP": "Halo Waypoint で投票する",
                                "ko-KR": "Halo Waypoint에서 투표",
                                "nb-NO": "Stem på Halo Waypoint",
                                "nl-NL": "Stem op Halo Waypoint",
                                "pl-PL": "Głosuj na Halo Waypoint",
                                "pt-BR": "Vote no Halo Waypoint",
                                "pt-PT": "Votar no Halo Waypoint",
                                "ru-RU": "Проголосовать на Halo Waypoint",
                                "sv-SE": "Rösta på Halo Waypoint",
                                "tr-TR": "Halo Waypoint'te oy verin",
                                "zh-CN": "在 Halo Waypoint 投票",
                                "zh-TW": "在 Halo Waypoint 投票",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vōτē бⁿ Ηàŀŏ Шåγрŏίⁿт! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "Vöŧė øл Ήãłô Ẁąŷρоίňт! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "Võťέ õņ Ħâłο Ŵâŷрόίⁿŧ! !!! !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to Halo Waypoint to vote.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na Halo Waypoint, kde budete moct hlasovat.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi fører dig til Halo Waypoint for at stemme.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zum Abstimmen auf Halo Waypoint weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στο Halo Waypoint για να ψηφίσεις.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a Halo Waypoint para que votes.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a Halo Waypoint para votar.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut Halo Waypointiin äänestämään.",
                                "fr-FR": "Nous allons vous diriger vers Halo Waypoint pour voter.",
                                "hu-HU": "A Halo Waypoint oldalára kerülsz a szavazáshoz.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo su Halo Waypoint per votare.",
                                "ja-JP": "投票するため Halo Waypoint に移動します。",
                                "ko-KR": "투표를 위해 Halo Waypoint로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til Halo Waypoint for å stemme.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar Halo Waypoint om te stemmen.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię do Halo Waypoint, gdzie możesz zagłosować.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao Halo Waypoint para votar.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao Halo Waypoint para votares.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем Halo Waypoint, чтобы вы смогли проголосовать.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Halo Waypoint för att rösta.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi oy vermeniz için Halo Waypoint'e aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们将带您前往 Halo Waypoint 投票。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會帶您前往 Halo Waypoint 投票。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ŵě'ļℓ ьŗîňģ ÿǿύ τő Ндľσ Ẁâỳρбίŉŧ тŏ νθŧě. !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ŵē'ℓľ ъŗïηġ ŷøū ŧό Ηâľø Ŵăγρōіпт тó νōťê. !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Шē'ļł ьгιńģ ỳбŭ ťŏ Ĥαĺŏ Ẁåўφōíⁿт тõ νôτė. !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://forums.halowaypoint.com/t/vote-now-the-last-sky-marshal/521812"
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Vote on Twitter",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Hlasovat na Twitteru",
                                "da-DK": "Stem på Twitter",
                                "de-DE": "Auf Twitter abstimmen",
                                "el-GR": "Ψήφισε στο Twitter",
                                "es-ES": "Vota en Twitter",
                                "es-MX": "Votar en Twitter",
                                "fi-FI": "Äänestä Twitterissä",
                                "fr-FR": "Voter sur Twitter",
                                "hu-HU": "Szavazás a Twitteren",
                                "it-IT": "Vota su Twitter",
                                "ja-JP": "Twitter で投票する",
                                "ko-KR": "Twitter에서 투표",
                                "nb-NO": "Stem på Twitter",
                                "nl-NL": "Stem op Twitter",
                                "pl-PL": "Głosuj na Twitterze",
                                "pt-BR": "Vote no Twitter",
                                "pt-PT": "Votar no Twitter",
                                "ru-RU": "Проголосовать в Twitter",
                                "sv-SE": "Rösta på Twitter",
                                "tr-TR": "Twitter'da oy verin",
                                "zh-CN": "在 Twitter 投票",
                                "zh-TW": "在 Twitter 投票",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vŏţè бŋ Ťŵìτţέг! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Vøтз óň Ŧщϊтţєŗ! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Vότė øл Ţωįťŧєŗ! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to Twitter to vote.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na Twitter, kde budete moct hlasovat.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi fører dig til Twitter for at stemme.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zum Abstimmen auf Twitter weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στο Twitter για να ψηφίσεις.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a Twitter para que votes.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a Twitter para votar.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut Twitteriin äänestämään.",
                                "fr-FR": "Nous allons vous diriger vers Twitter pour voter.",
                                "hu-HU": "A Twitter-fiókunkhoz viszünk a szavazáshoz.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo su Twitter per votare.",
                                "ja-JP": "投票するため Twitter に移動します。",
                                "ko-KR": "투표를 위해 Twitter로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til Twitter for å stemme.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar Twitter om te stemmen.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię na Twittera, gdzie możesz zagłosować.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao Twitter para votar.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao Twitter para votares.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем Twitter, чтобы вы смогли проголосовать.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Twitter för att rösta.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi oy vermeniz için Twitter'a aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们会带您前往 Twitter 投票。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會帶您前往 Twitter 投票。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Щë'ļŀ вŕίńğ γõμ τб Ţщιţтеґ ţø νθτę. !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ẁê'ŀŀ ьřìйğ ўοù ŧό Ţẅϊţťêř τǿ νǿťë. !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẃê'ļł ъřίπġ ŷøù τō Ţωіŧťėг ţб νőťê. !!! !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://twitter.com/Halo/status/1536784853026361344"
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Vote on Instagram",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Hlasovat na Instagramu",
                                "da-DK": "Stem på Instagram",
                                "de-DE": "Auf Instagram abstimmen",
                                "el-GR": "Ψήφισε στο Instagram",
                                "es-ES": "Vota en Instagram",
                                "es-MX": "Votar en Instagram",
                                "fi-FI": "Äänestä Instagramissa",
                                "fr-FR": "Voter sur Instagram",
                                "hu-HU": "Szavazás az Instagrammon",
                                "it-IT": "Vota su Instagram",
                                "ja-JP": "Instagram で投票する",
                                "ko-KR": "Instagram에서 투표",
                                "nb-NO": "Stem på Instagram",
                                "nl-NL": "Stem op Instagram",
                                "pl-PL": "Głosuj na Instagramie",
                                "pt-BR": "Vote no Instagram",
                                "pt-PT": "Votar no Instagram",
                                "ru-RU": "Проголосовать в Instagram",
                                "sv-SE": "Rösta på Instagram",
                                "tr-TR": "Instagram'da oy verin",
                                "zh-CN": "在 Instagram 投票",
                                "zh-TW": "在 Instagram 投票",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vοŧë õñ Ìⁿѕŧáġѓām! !!! !!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Vόŧе ση Íńśţаģřâm! !!! !!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Vòт℮ ǿⁿ Íлŝťāġřâм! !!! !!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to Instagram to vote.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na Instagram, kde budete moct hlasovat.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi fører dig til Instagram for at stemme.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zum Abstimmen auf Instagram weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στο Instagram για να ψηφίσεις.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a Instagram para que votes.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a Instagram para votar.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut Instagramiin äänestämään.",
                                "fr-FR": "Nous allons vous diriger vers Instagram pour voter.",
                                "hu-HU": "A Halo Instagram-oldalára kerülsz a szavazáshoz.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo su Instagram per votare.",
                                "ja-JP": "投票するため Instagram に移動します。",
                                "ko-KR": "투표를 위해 Instagram으로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til Instagram for å stemme.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar Instagram om te stemmen.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię na Instagrama, gdzie możesz zagłosować.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao Instagram para votar.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao Instagram para votares.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем Instagram, чтобы вы смогли проголосовать.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Instagram för att rösta.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi oy vermeniz için Instagram'a aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们会带您前往 Instagram 投票。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會帶您前往 Instagram 投票。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ŵę'ļļ вгιⁿğ ỳόύ ťō Īήşτáĝґаm ŧŏ νòţĕ. !!! !!! !!! !!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ẅэ'ľł вřіŉģ γőџ тō Ĭņѕтãģřаm τо νôтĕ. !!! !!! !!! !!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẅ℮'ŀľ ьгīŋĝ уôŭ ťб Ĭñŝţäĝŕąm ţǿ νŏŧэ. !!! !!! !!! !!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://instagram.com/Halo"
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Vote on Discord",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Hlasovat na Discordu",
                                "da-DK": "Stem på Discord",
                                "de-DE": "Auf Discord abstimmen",
                                "el-GR": "Ψήφισε στο Discord",
                                "es-ES": "Vota en Discord",
                                "es-MX": "Votar en Discord",
                                "fi-FI": "Äänestä Discordissa",
                                "fr-FR": "Voter sur Discord",
                                "hu-HU": "Szavazás Discordon",
                                "it-IT": "Vota su Discord",
                                "ja-JP": "Discord で投票する",
                                "ko-KR": "Discord에서 투표",
                                "nb-NO": "Stem på Discord",
                                "nl-NL": "Stem op Discord",
                                "pl-PL": "Głosuj na Discordzie",
                                "pt-BR": "Vote no Discord",
                                "pt-PT": "Votar no Discord",
                                "ru-RU": "Проголосовать в Discord",
                                "sv-SE": "Rösta på Discord",
                                "tr-TR": "Discord'da oy verin",
                                "zh-CN": "在 Discord 投票",
                                "zh-TW": "在 Discord 投票",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vǿţê öŋ Ďĭŝ¢őřď! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Vőţē ŏπ Ðΐşčōґď! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Vόťэ òπ Ďïšĉοřδ! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to the Official Halo Discord to vote.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na oficiální Discord pro Halo, kde budete moct hlasovat.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi fører dig til den officielle Halo Discord for at stemme.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zum Abstimmen auf den offiziellen Halo Discord weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στο Επίσημο Discord του Halo για να ψηφίσεις.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos al canal oficial de Halo de Discord para que votes.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos al servidor de Discord oficial de Halo para votar.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut viralliseen Halo-Discordiin äänestämään.",
                                "fr-FR": "Nous allons vous diriger vers le Discord officiel de Halo pour voter.",
                                "hu-HU": "A hivatalos Halo Discord szerverre viszünk a szavazáshoz.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo sul canale Discord ufficiale di Halo per votare.",
                                "ja-JP": "投票するため Halo 公式 Discord に移動します。",
                                "ko-KR": "투표를 위해 공식 Halo Discord로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til den offisielle Halo-kontoen på Discord for å stemme.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar de officiële Halo Discord om te stemmen.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię na oficjalny kanał Halo na Discordzie, gdzie możesz zagłosować.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao Discord Oficial de Halo para votar.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao Discord oficial do Halo para votares.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем официальный сервер Halo в Discord, чтобы вы смогли проголосовать.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Halos officiella Discord-server för att rösta.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi oy vermeniz için Resmî Halo Discord sunucusuna aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们会带您前往官方 Halo Discord 投票。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會帶您前往官方 Halo Discord 投票。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ẅê'ŀĺ ьŕĩņğ γőµ тσ τĥě Όƒƒĭсΐдľ Ħàŀò Ðíѕ¢ôŗď ţõ νõтè. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ẃ℮'łļ ъŗîŋğ ýõū ţо ţĥέ Ώƒƒϊ¢ϊάŀ Ηдĺο Ďïšċθѓď ťô νǿŧё. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẁ℮'ĺĺ вŗĭпģ ÿôú ţο ţĥε Õƒƒĭ¢ϊаļ Ηаĺŏ Ďïšċǿяď τø νóťê. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://discord.gg/Halo"
                    },
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Vote on Facebook",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Hlasovat na Facebooku",
                                "da-DK": "Stem på Facebook",
                                "de-DE": "Auf Facebook abstimmen",
                                "el-GR": "Ψήφισε στο Facebook",
                                "es-ES": "Vota en Facebook",
                                "es-MX": "Votar en Facebook",
                                "fi-FI": "Äänestä Facebookissa",
                                "fr-FR": "Voter sur Facebook",
                                "hu-HU": "Szavazás Facebookon",
                                "it-IT": "Vota su Facebook",
                                "ja-JP": "Facebook で投票する",
                                "ko-KR": "Facebook에서 투표",
                                "nb-NO": "Stem på Facebook",
                                "nl-NL": "Stem op Facebook",
                                "pl-PL": "Głosuj na Facebooku",
                                "pt-BR": "Vote no Facebook",
                                "pt-PT": "Votar no Facebook",
                                "ru-RU": "Проголосовать в Facebook",
                                "sv-SE": "Rösta på Facebook",
                                "tr-TR": "Facebook'ta oy verin",
                                "zh-CN": "在 Facebook 投票",
                                "zh-TW": "在 Facebook 投票",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vöŧė όŉ ₣ąçэьŏбκ! !!! !!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Võŧє όл ₣åćěвõŏκ! !!! !!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Vοţę ôⁿ ₣âċзвôσĸ! !!! !!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to Facebook to vote.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na Facebook, kde budete moct hlasovat.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi fører dig til Facebook for at stemme.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zum Abstimmen auf Facebook weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στο Facebook για να ψηφίσεις.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a Facebook para que votes.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a Facebook para votar.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut Facebookiin äänestämään.",
                                "fr-FR": "Nous allons vous diriger vers Facebook pour voter.",
                                "hu-HU": "A Halo Facebook-oldalára kerülsz a szavazáshoz.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo su Facebook per votare.",
                                "ja-JP": "投票するため Facebook に移動します。",
                                "ko-KR": "투표를 위해 Facebook으로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til Facebook for å stemme.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar Facebook om te stemmen.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię na Facebooka, gdzie możesz zagłosować.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao Facebook para votar.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao Facebook para votares.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем Facebook, чтобы вы смогли проголосовать.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Facebook för att rösta.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi oy vermeniz için Facebook'a aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们会带您前往 Facebook 投票。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會帶您前往 Facebook 投票。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ẃè'ŀļ ъŗĭпġ γσũ ŧο ₣ā¢ëвóбĸ τσ νöţè. !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ẁē'ĺľ вяϊήģ ýōΰ ţô ₣áćëъθøĸ ţό νбŧє. !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẁë'ŀļ вřįŋġ уομ τό ₣àçëвǿōκ тő νσţе. !!! !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://facebook.com/Halo"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "ShortHeadline": {
                    "value": "Juneteenth Emblem &amp; Nameplate",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Emblém a jmenovka Den nezávislosti černochů",
                        "da-DK": "Juneteenth-emblem og -navneskilt",
                        "de-DE": "Emblem und Namensschild „Juneteenth“",
                        "es-ES": "Emblema y placa de identificación de Juneteenth",
                        "es-MX": "Emblema y placa de identificación del Día de la Emancipación",
                        "fi-FI": "Juneteenth-tunnus ja nimikyltti",
                        "fr-FR": "Emblème et plaque nominative Jour de l'émancipation",
                        "hu-HU": "Juneteenth embléma és névtábla",
                        "it-IT": "Emblema e targa identificativa 10giugno",
                        "ja-JP": "ジューンティーンスのエンブレム &amp; ネームプレート",
                        "ko-KR": "노예 해방 기념일 휘장 및 명판",
                        "nb-NO": "Junteenth-emblem og -navneskilt",
                        "nl-NL": "Juneteenth-embleem en -naamplaatje",
                        "pl-PL": "Emblemat i plakietka Dzień wyzwolenia",
                        "pt-BR": "Emblema e Placa de Identificação Juneteenth",
                        "pt-PT": "Emblema e placa de identificação do Juneteenth",
                        "sv-SE": "Juneteenth-emblem och -namnskylt",
                        "tr-TR": "On Dokuz Haziran Amblemi ve İsim Plakası",
                        "zh-CN": "六月独立日名牌和徽章",
                        "zh-TW": "六月獨立日名牌和徽章",
                        "qps-ploc": "Јúňзţēêήŧћ Эmвłēm &amp; Ńαmëρļàŧĕ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Јúπěťеèñŧħ Ėmьłем &amp; Ñâмєφĺāтє !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ĵџήёŧěëпτђ Ëmъŀéм &amp; Йàmėрłâťє !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "FullHeadline": {
                    "value": "Juneteenth Emblem &amp; Nameplate",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Emblém a jmenovka Den nezávislosti černochů",
                        "da-DK": "Juneteenth-emblem og -navneskilt",
                        "de-DE": "Emblem und Namensschild „Juneteenth“",
                        "es-ES": "Emblema y placa de identificación de Juneteenth",
                        "es-MX": "Emblema y placa de identificación del Día de la Emancipación",
                        "fi-FI": "Juneteenth-tunnus ja nimikyltti",
                        "fr-FR": "Emblème et plaque nominative Jour de l'émancipation",
                        "hu-HU": "Juneteenth embléma és névtábla",
                        "it-IT": "Emblema e targa identificativa 10giugno",
                        "ja-JP": "ジューンティーンスのエンブレム &amp; ネームプレート",
                        "ko-KR": "노예 해방 기념일 휘장 및 명판",
                        "nb-NO": "Junteenth-emblem og -navneskilt",
                        "nl-NL": "Juneteenth-embleem en -naamplaatje",
                        "pl-PL": "Emblemat i plakietka Dzień wyzwolenia",
                        "pt-BR": "Emblema e Placa de Identificação Juneteenth",
                        "pt-PT": "Emblema e placa de identificação do Juneteenth",
                        "sv-SE": "Juneteenth-emblem och -namnskylt",
                        "tr-TR": "On Dokuz Haziran Amblemi ve İsim Plakası",
                        "zh-CN": "六月独立日名牌和徽章",
                        "zh-TW": "六月獨立日名牌和徽章",
                        "qps-ploc": "Јúňзţēêήŧћ Эmвłēm &amp; Ńαmëρļàŧĕ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Јúπěťеèñŧħ Ėmьłем &amp; Ñâмєφĺāтє !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ĵџήёŧěëпτђ Ëmъŀéм &amp; Йàmėрłâťє !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "Body": {
                    "value": "Celebrate Freedom. \n\nJoin us in the commemoration of freedom, liberty, and humanity. As we celebrate, we must also unite to fight injustice and oppression in the name of a better future. \n\nLog into Halo Infinite this week to unlock the Juneteenth nameplate and emblem for your Spartan, weapons, and vehicles.",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Oslavte svobodu. \n\nPřipomeňte si s námi, co znamená svoboda a lidskost. Při oslavách se musíme v zájmu lepší budoucnosti také sjednotit a bojovat proti bezpráví a útlaku. \n\nPřihlaste se tento týden do Halo Infinite a odemkněte pro svého Sparťana, zbraně a vozidla jmenovku a emblém Den nezávislosti černochů.",
                        "da-DK": "Fejr friheden. \n\nSlut dig til os i fejringen af friheden og menneskeheden. Mens vi fejrer disse ting, må vi også stå sammen i kampen mod uretfærdighed og undertrykkelse for at sikre en bedre fremtid. \n\nLog ind på Halo Infinite i denne uge for at låse op for Juneteenth-navneskiltet og -emblemet til din spartaner, dine våben og fartøjer.",
                        "de-DE": "Feiere die Freiheit. \n\nBegleite uns beim Gedenken an Freiheit, Selbstbestimmung und Menschlichkeit. Doch wir müssen uns auch zusammenschließen, um Ungerechtigkeit und Unterdrückung im Namen einer besseren Zukunft zu bekämpfen. \n\nMelde dich diese Woche bei Halo Infinite an, um das Juneteenth-Namensschild und das Emblem für deinen Spartan, deine Waffen und Fahrzeuge freizuschalten.",
                        "es-ES": "Celebra la libertad. \n\nÚnete a nosotros para conmemorar la libertad, la libertad y la humanidad. Y mientras celebramos, también debemos unirnos para luchar contra la injusticia y la opresión en nombre de un futuro mejor. \n\nInicia sesión en Halo Infinite esta semana para desbloquear la placa de identificación y el emblema de Juneteenth para tu Spartan, armas y vehículos.",
                        "es-MX": "Celebra la liberación. \n\nAcompáñanos en la conmemoración de la libertad y la humanidad. Además de celebrar, es momento de unirnos para luchar contra la injusticia y la opresión en nombre de un futuro mejor. \n\nInicia sesión en Halo Infinite esta semana para desbloquear la placa de identificación y el emblema del Día de la Emancipación para tu Spartan, armas y vehículos.",
                        "fi-FI": "Juhlista vapautta. \n\nLiity seuraamme juhlistamaan vapautta, oikeutta ja inhimillisyyttä. Samalla meidän on myös taisteltava yhdessä vääryyttä ja sortoa vastaan paremman tulevaisuuden nimessä.\n\nKirjaudu Halo Infiniteen tällä viikolla, niin avaat Juneteenth-nimikyltin ja tunnuksen spartalaisellesi, aseillesi ja ajoneuvoillesi.",
                        "fr-FR": "Fêtez la liberté. \n\nCommémorons ensemble la liberté et l'humanité. Mais dans notre célébration, nous devons également nous unir contre l'injustice et l'oppression au nom d'un avenir meilleur. \n\nConnectez-vous sur Halo Infinite cette semaine pour déverrouiller la plaque nominative et l'emblème Jour de l'émancipation pour votre Spartan, vos armes et vos véhicules.",
                        "hu-HU": "Ünnepeld a szabadságot! \n\nTarts velünk, tisztelegjünk közösen a szabadság és emberiség előtt! Az ünneplés mellett azonban továbbra is közösen kell küzdenünk az igazságtalanság és elnyomás ellen, egy szebb jövő reményében. \n\nJelentkezz be ezen a héten a Halo Infinite játékba, hogy feloldd a juneteenth, a rabszolgaság eltörlésének emléknapjára készített névtáblát és emblémát Spartanod, fegyvereid és járműveid számára.",
                        "it-IT": "Festeggia la libertà. \n\nUnisciti a noi nella commemorazione della libertà e dell'umanità. E, tutti insieme, cogliamo anche l'occasione per lottare contro l'ingiustizia e l'oppressione in nome di un futuro migliore. \n\nAccedi a Halo Infinite questa settimana per sbloccare la targa identificativa e l'emblema 10giugno per il tuo Spartan, le tue armi e i tuoi veicoli.",
                        "ja-JP": "自由の祝祭。\n\n自由、解放、そして人間らしさを共に称えましょう。同時に、より良い未来のため、私たちは団結し、不正や抑圧と戦わねばなりません。\n\n今週、Halo Infinite にログインすると、ジューンティーンスのネームプレートと自分のスパルタンに使えるエンブレム、武器、ビークルがアンロックされます。",
                        "ko-KR": "자유를 기념하십시오. \n\n저희와 함께 자유, 독립, 인간성을 기념해 주십시오. 그리고 더 나은 미래를 위하여 불의와 압제에 맞서 싸우기 위해 힘을 합쳐 주십시오. \n\n이번 주에 Halo Infinite에 로그인하여 여러분의 스파르탄, 무기, 차량에 사용할 수 있는 노예 해방 기념일 명판 및 휘장을 잠금 해제하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Marker friheten. \n\nBli med oss på markeringen av frihet og menneskeheten! Når vi feirer, må vi forene oss for å bekjempe urettferdighet og undertrykkelse og få en bedre fremtid. \n\nLogg inn på Halo Infinite denne uken for å låse opp Juneteenth-navneskiltet og -emblemet til spartanere, våpen og kjøretøyer.",
                        "nl-NL": "Vier de vrijheid. \n\nSluit je bij ons aan ter ere van vrijheid, goedheid en de menselijkheid. Samen vechten we voor een betere toekomst en nemen we het op tegen onrecht en onderdrukking. \n\nMeld je deze week aan bij Halo Infinite en ontgrendel het Juneteenth-naamplaatje en -embleem voor je Spartan, wapens en voertuigen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Świętuj wolność razem z nami.\n\nWspólnie uczcijmy święto wolności i człowieczeństwa. Zjednoczmy się w walce z uciskiem i niesprawiedliwością w trosce o lepszą przyszłość.\n\nZaloguj się do Halo Infinite w tym tygodniu, by odblokować plakietkę i emblemat Dzień wyzwolenia, którymi ozdobisz spartanina, broń i pojazdy.",
                        "pt-BR": "Celebre a liberdade. \n\nParticipe de uma comemoração pela liberdade, independência e humanidade. Enquanto celebramos, também precisamos nos unir por um futuro melhor contra a injustiça e a opressão. \n\nEntre no Halo Infinite nessa semana para desbloquear a Placa de Identificação e o Emblema Juneteenth para o seu Spartan, suas armas e seus veículos.",
                        "pt-PT": "Celebra a liberdade. \n\nJunta-te a nós na comemoração da liberdade e da humanidade. Enquanto celebramos, também devemos unir-nos para lutar contra a injustiça e a opressão em nome de um futuro melhor. \n\nInicia sessão no Halo Infinite esta semana para desbloqueares a placa de identificação e o emblema do Juneteenth para o teu Spartan, armas e veículos.",
                        "sv-SE": "Fira friheten.\n\nFölj med oss och fira frihet och mänsklighet. När vi firar måste vi även förena oss mot orättvisa och förtryck för att skapa en bättre framtid.\n\nLogga in på Halo Infinite den här veckan för att få namnskylten och emblemet Juneteenth till din spartan, dina vapen och dina fordon.",
                        "tr-TR": "Özgürlüğü kutlayın. \n\nÖzgürlüğü, bağımsızlığı ve insanlığı anma törenimize katılın. Kutlamaların yanı sıra daha iyi bir gelecek adına adaletsizlik ve baskıyla mücadele etmek için birlik olmalıyız. \n\nBu hafta Halo Infinite'e giriş yaparak Spartan'ınız, silahlarınız ve araçlarınız için On Dokuz Haziran isim plakasının ve ambleminin kilidini açın.",
                        "zh-CN": "庆祝自由。\n\n加入我们，纪念自由、自由和人性。在我们庆祝的同时，我们还必须团结起来，以更美好未来的名义与不公正和压迫作斗争。\n\n本周登录 Halo Infinite，为您的斯巴达战士、武器和载具解锁六月独立日名牌和徽章。",
                        "zh-TW": "慶祝自由。\n\n加入我們，紀念自由、自由和人性。在我們慶祝的同時，我們還必須團結起來，以更美好未來的名義與不公正和壓迫鬥爭。\n\n本週登入 Halo Infinite，為您的超級戰士、武器和載具解鎖六月獨立日名牌和徽章。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ćėĺêвгаŧę ₣г℮éđσм.  !!! !!!\n\nЈőіñ ύś їй тнê ċőммêмогдτìóŉ ǿƒ ƒř℮эðθm, ľĩьęѓтÿ, āиď нϋmàńïτý. Åš ẁè ċėℓéъґªť℮, ώē мµşţ ǻĺšο ŭņιŧé τò ƒίĝђт ìπĵυśŧĭçě āŉď õρрŕéśśΐøⁿ ĩп тђ℮ ήąмė òƒ ä вêŧтзŗ ƒύţμгē.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\nĻσģ ΐņŧõ Нăłó Íňƒίñįτé тħіŝ щěēĸ τö ųйľŏčκ ťнε Ĵџŉêтęéήţн ńąměрĺаŧę äήď êmьℓем ƒôř ŷōμя Śφâŕτåи, ωєáρøńş, åňδ νëĥісľέš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ċëłěъгãţē ₣язэđόm.  !!! !!!\n\nЈбϊπ цѕ ïŋ ŧће ¢θммέмöѓąŧίøп θƒ ƒřėēđοм, ļîвеřτỳ, аŋð ĥûmâńϊтý. Άś ŵε ¢еľěьґдŧë, ŵè mųşτ αℓşσ υńįţê τö ƒįğĥţ ίŉјúşťĭĉê апδ óφφґëśśîóπ īи ŧнë ŉàmę òƒ ª ьĕтťêѓ ƒúŧϋŗё.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\n£òġ ίйŧō Наļŏ İńƒìńïτě ťћìѕ ẁёзќ ŧо μŉŀосĸ ţħě Ĵμņèţëзⁿτĥ ήάмєφℓдţė аŋď έмвℓęм ƒǿґ уōϋя Ѕρǻřŧαή, ωзªрòиŝ, αňď νėћΐćℓ℮ś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Сēĺēвŗąŧе ₣ѓěēďθm.  !!! !!!\n\nĴσϊń ύş îň ŧнё ¢òммемōгªţίои øƒ ƒѓĕéďõм, ļīвęяťŷ, ªπδ нŭмăйĭтỳ. Λѕ ẅэ č℮łëьřǻŧė, ωě мϋśτ âļšŏ џŉіţε то ƒìğħŧ įńĵυśτïςэ äñď ōрргэѕѕįθⁿ їл тћé πąmε бƒ ά ъэŧŧέя ƒµŧΰгę.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\nŁσģ ìиťо Ηāļό Ìŉƒίŋïτё тħιš ẅēěķ ťő цŉļøĉќ ŧне Ĵūⁿėťёēπτĥ ŉáм℮рℓáţё дňđ éмвłěm ƒōѓ ÿōΰŗ Ŝрαяťǻŋ, ẃéåρóñş, āⁿδ νěђіçłëş. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "ArticleImage": {
                    "Width": 1920,
                    "Height": 1080,
                    "Path": "news/Evergreen/Juneteenth_1920x1080_MOTD.jpg"
                },
                "ArticleActions": [
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Follow @Halo on Twitter",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Sledujte @Halo na Twitteru.",
                                "da-DK": "Følg @Halo på Twitter",
                                "de-DE": "@Halo auf Twitter folgen",
                                "el-GR": "Ακολούθησε το @Halo στο Twitter",
                                "es-ES": "Sigue a @Halo en Twitter",
                                "es-MX": "Sigue a @Halo en Twitter",
                                "fi-FI": "Seuraa tiliä @Halo Twitterissä",
                                "fr-FR": "Suivre @Halo sur Twitter",
                                "hu-HU": "Kövesd a @Halo fiókot Twitteren",
                                "it-IT": "Segui @Halo su Twitter",
                                "ja-JP": "Twitter で @Halo をフォローしよう",
                                "ko-KR": "Twitter에서 @Halo를 팔로우하십시오",
                                "nb-NO": "Følg @Halo på Twitter",
                                "nl-NL": "Volg @Halo op Twitter",
                                "pl-PL": "Obserwuj @Halo na Twitterze",
                                "pt-BR": "Siga @Halo no Twitter",
                                "pt-PT": "Segue @Halo no Twitter",
                                "ru-RU": "Подписаться на @Halo в Twitter",
                                "sv-SE": "Följ @Halo på Twitter",
                                "tr-TR": "@Halo'yu Twitter'da takip edin",
                                "zh-CN": "请在 Twitter 关注 @Halo",
                                "zh-TW": "在 Twitter 上跟隨 @Halo",
                                "qps-ploc": "₣ǿℓĺòẃ @Ĥаℓσ ŏπ Тŵïţτéя !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "₣σłłőŵ @Ήàļō οп Ţώĩťτєя !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "₣őĺļθẃ @Ηάľо θп Ŧώíţťêŗ !!! !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to the @Halo Twitter account.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na twitterový účet @Halo.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi tager dig til @Halo Twitter-kontoen.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zu unserem @Halo Twitter-Konto weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στον λογαριασμό του @Halo στο Twitter.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a la cuenta @Halo en Twitter.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a la cuenta de Halo en Twitter.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut Twitter-tilillemme @Halo.",
                                "fr-FR": "Vous arriverez sur le compte Twitter @Halo.",
                                "hu-HU": "A @Halo Twitter-fiókhoz viszünk.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo all'account Twitter @Halo.",
                                "ja-JP": "詳細については、Twitter の @HaloSupport アカウントをご覧ください。",
                                "ko-KR": "자세한 내용을 보실 수 있도록 @Halo Twitter 계정으로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til @Halo-kontoen på Twitter.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar het Twitter-account @Halo.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię na konto @Halo na Twitterze.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você à conta do Twitter @Halo.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te à conta @Halo no Twitter.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем для вас ленту @Halo в Twitter.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Twitter-kontot @Halo.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi @Halo Twitter hesabına aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们将带您前往 @Halo Twitter 账号。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會帶您前往 @Halo Twitter 帳戶。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ẅе'ŀĺ ьŕĭйģ уόц ţо τĥę @Ĥªŀǿ Тẅίŧţёѓ äćçòŭⁿτ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Щë'ŀℓ ъŕĩπğ ўòϋ ťό ťĥέ @Ηдℓό Τẁϊтŧėŕ ąćċöΰйτ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẁє'ľĺ вяíŉġ ŷŏů ţо ťнė @Ĥªĺό Τẃįτтèř ăċċбŭńŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://twitter.com/Halo"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "ShortHeadline": {
                    "value": "Online Campaign Co-Op Flighting",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Testovací verze online kooperace v kampani",
                        "da-DK": "Online kampagne Co-Op flighting",
                        "de-DE": "Testprogramm für Online-Kampagnen-Koop",
                        "el-GR": "Δοκιμή διαδικτυακής εκστρατείας συνεργασίας",
                        "es-ES": "Versión de evaluación de campaña cooperativa en línea",
                        "es-MX": "Pruebas de campaña cooperativa en línea",
                        "fi-FI": "Online-kampanjayhteispeli-väliversio",
                        "fr-FR": "Tests de campagne coop en ligne",
                        "hu-HU": "Online kooperatív hadjárat – Tesztrepülés",
                        "it-IT": "Test online Campagna Co-Op",
                        "ja-JP": "オンライン キャンペーン協力プレイ フライティング",
                        "ko-KR": "온라인 캠페인 협동 게임 플라이팅",
                        "nb-NO": "Runde med historiesamarbeid på nett",
                        "nl-NL": "Flights voor online coöp-campagne",
                        "pl-PL": "Testy kooperacyjnej kampanii online",
                        "pt-BR": "Decolagem da Campanha Cooperativa Online",
                        "pt-PT": "Lançamento da Campanha cooperativa online",
                        "ru-RU": "Тестирование совместного прохождения кампании по сети",
                        "sv-SE": "Test av samarbetskampanj online",
                        "tr-TR": "Çevrimiçi Harekât İş Birliği Sınırlı Denemesi",
                        "zh-CN": "线上战役合作模式测试",
                        "zh-TW": "線上戰役合作模式測試",
                        "qps-ploc": "Øŉĺīл℮ Çǻмρäįĝή Сǿ-Όφ ₣ĺìģђŧíŉĝ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Οñłїпё Ĉăмρаîğŉ Сõ-Ŏρ ₣łїģћťιπğ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ώйĺійę Сάмρåϊġη Ćб-Ωр ₣ŀïğђťïпĝ !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "FullHeadline": {
                    "value": "Online Campaign Co-Op Flighting",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Testovací verze online kooperace v kampani",
                        "da-DK": "Online kampagne Co-Op flighting",
                        "de-DE": "Testprogramm für Online-Kampagnen-Koop",
                        "el-GR": "Δοκιμή διαδικτυακής εκστρατείας συνεργασίας",
                        "es-ES": "Versión de evaluación de campaña cooperativa en línea",
                        "es-MX": "Pruebas de campaña cooperativa en línea",
                        "fi-FI": "Online-kampanjayhteispeli-väliversio",
                        "fr-FR": "Tests de campagne coop en ligne",
                        "hu-HU": "Online kooperatív hadjárat – Tesztrepülés",
                        "it-IT": "Test online Campagna Co-Op",
                        "ja-JP": "オンライン キャンペーン協力プレイ フライティング",
                        "ko-KR": "온라인 캠페인 협동 게임 플라이팅",
                        "nb-NO": "Runde med historiesamarbeid på nett",
                        "nl-NL": "Flights voor online coöp-campagne",
                        "pl-PL": "Testy kooperacyjnej kampanii online",
                        "pt-BR": "Decolagem da Campanha Cooperativa Online",
                        "pt-PT": "Lançamento da Campanha cooperativa online",
                        "ru-RU": "Тестирование совместного прохождения кампании по сети",
                        "sv-SE": "Test av samarbetskampanj online",
                        "tr-TR": "Çevrimiçi Harekât İş Birliği Sınırlı Denemesi",
                        "zh-CN": "线上战役合作模式测试",
                        "zh-TW": "線上戰役合作模式測試",
                        "qps-ploc": "Øŉĺīл℮ Çǻмρäįĝή Сǿ-Όφ ₣ĺìģђŧíŉĝ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Οñłїпё Ĉăмρаîğŉ Сõ-Ŏρ ₣łїģћťιπğ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ώйĺійę Сάмρåϊġη Ćб-Ωр ₣ŀïğђťïпĝ !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "Body": {
                    "value": "Become a Halo Insider for a chance to participate in our upcoming flight of online 4-player Campaign Co-Op! \n\nThe Halo Insider program is the official way for Halo fans and community members to partner with 343 Industries to help improve our games, products, and services. \n\nAs a Halo Insider, you’ll join us in testing exclusive work-in-progress features and content, getting a first look at new updates and improvements coming to Halo Infinite. Your voice matters, so sign up and join us in public ‘flights’ (hands-on playtests) to provide feedback to our development teams. \n\nRegister today at aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Staňte se insiderem Halo a získáte šanci zúčastnit se naší připravované testovací verze online kooperace v kampani pro 4 hráče! \n\nProgram Halo Insider je oficiální způsob, jak se fanoušci a členové komunity Halo můžou stát partnery 343 Industries a pomáhat vylepšit naše hry, produkty a služby. \n\nJako insider Halo s námi budete moct testovat exkluzivní připravované funkce a obsah a získat první informace o nových aktualizacích a vylepšeních Hala Infinite. Váš hlas má váhu, proto se zaregistrujte a přidejte se k nám při testování veřejných verzí (kde budete moct sami testovací verze hrát), abyste mohli poskytovat zpětnou vazbu našim vývojářským týmům. \n\n Zaregistrujte se ještě dnes na aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "da-DK": "Bliv Halo Insider for at få chancen for at deltage i \"flyvningen\" af vores kommende samarbejdskampagne for fire spillere online! \n\nHalo Insider-programmet er den officielle mulighed for, at Halo-fans og medlemmer af spillets fællesskab kan samarbejde med 343 Industries om at hjælpe os med at forbedre vores spil, produkter og tjenester. \n\nSom Halo Insider vil du sammen med os teste eksklusive nye funktioner og indhold samt få smugkig på nye opdateringer og forbedringer, der er på vej til Halo Infinite. Din stemme betyder noget, så tilmeld dig, og deltag i offentlige \"flyvninger\" (hands-on-playtests) for at give feedback til vores udviklingshold. \n\n Tilmeld dig i dag på aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "de-DE": "Werde zum Halo Insider und erhalte die Chance, am Testprogramm für unseren kommenden Online-Kampagnen-Koop für 4 Spieler teilzunehmen! \n\nDas Halo-Infinite-Programm ist die Gelegenheit für Halo-Fans und Community-Mitglieder, sich mit 343 Industries zusammenzutun und aktiv bei der Verbesserung von Spielen, Produkten und Diensten mitzuhelfen. \n\nAls Halo Insider kannst du noch in der Entwicklung befindliche Funktionen und Inhalte ausprobieren und erhältst vorab Einblick in neue Updates und Verbesserungen für Halo Infinite. Deine Meinung ist uns wichtig, also melde dich an und mach bei öffentlichen Playtests mit, um unseren Entwicklerteams dein Feedback zu geben. \n\nMelde dich noch heute bei aka.ms/HaloInsider an! \n\n",
                        "el-GR": "Γίνε Halo Insider για να έχεις την ευκαιρία να συμμετάσχεις στην επερχόμενη διαδικτυακή Συνεργατική εκστρατεία 4 παικτών! \n\nΤο πρόγραμμα Halo Insider είναι ο επίσημος τρόπος για να συνεργαστούν οι οπαδοί και τα μέλη της κοινότητας του Halo με την 343 Industries για να βοηθήσουν στη βελτίωση των παιχνιδιών, των προϊόντων και των υπηρεσιών μας. \n\nΩς Halo Insider, θα συμμετάσχεις στη δοκιμή αποκλειστικών νέων λειτουργιών και περιεχομένου σε εξέλιξη, και θα ρίχνεις την πρώτη ματιά στις νέες ενημερώσεις και βελτιώσεις που έρχονται στο Halo Infinite. Η άποψή σου έχει σημασία, γι' αυτό γίνε μέλος και έλα μαζί μας στις δημόσιες δοκιμές για να μοιραστείς τα σχόλιά σου με τις ομάδες ανάπτυξής μας. \n\n Εγγράψου σήμερα στο aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "es-ES": "¡Conviértete en Halo Insider y podrás participar en la próxima campaña cooperativa para 4 jugadores en línea! \n\nEl programa Halo Insider es la forma oficial para que los seguidores y miembros de la comunidad de Halo se asocien con 343 Industries para ayudar a mejorar nuestros juegos, productos y servicios. \n\nComo Halo Insider, te unirás a nosotros para probar características y contenidos exclusivos en proceso de desarrollo, por lo que conocerás antes que nadie las nuevas actualizaciones y mejoras que llegarán a Halo Infinite. Tu opinión importa, así que regístrate y únete a nosotros en las versiones de evaluación públicas (pruebas de juego prácticas) y comparte tus comentarios con nuestros equipos de desarrollo. \n\n ¡Regístrate hoy mismo en aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "es-MX": "¡Inscríbete al programa Halo Insider para participar en nuestra próxima prueba de la campaña cooperativa para 4 jugadores! \n\nEl programa Halo Insider es la forma oficial en que los fanáticos y miembros de la comunidad de Halo pueden ayudar a 343 Industries a mejorar sus juegos, productos y servicios. \n\nComo parte del programa Halo Insider, nos ayudarás a probar características y contenido exclusivos en desarrollo y tendrás la oportunidad de probar las nuevas actualizaciones y mejoras que llegarán a Halo Infinite antes que nadie. Tu opinión es importante, así que regístrate y acompáñanos en las pruebas públicas de juego para compartir tus comentarios con nuestros equipos de desarrollo. \n\n ¡Regístrate hoy mismo en aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "fi-FI": "Liity Halo Insideriksi, niin pääset mukaan testaamaan neljän pelaajan online-kampanjayhteispeliä! \n\nHalo Insider -ohjelma on Halo-fanien ja yhteisön jäsenten virallinen mahdollisuus tehdä yhteistyötä 343 Industriesin kanssa ja auttaa meitä parantamaan pelejämme, tuotteitamme ja palveluitamme. \n\nHalo Insider -sisäpiiriläisenä pääset yksinoikeudella testaamaan tekeillä olevia ominaisuuksia ja sisältöä kanssamme ja näkemään Halo Infiniten uusimmat päivitykset ja parannukset ensimmäisten joukossa. Äänelläsi on merkitystä, joten rekisteröidy ja liity mukaan julkisiin väliversiotesteihin, niin pääset antamaan palautetta kehitystiimeillemme. \n\n Rekisteröidy osoitteessa aka.ms.HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "fr-FR": "Devenez un Halo Insider et vous participerez peut-être à notre prochain test de campagne coop en ligne à 4 joueurs ! \n\nLe programme Halo Insider est le moyen officiel pour les fans de Halo et les membres de la communauté de s'associer à 343 Industries pour aider à améliorer nos jeux, produits et services. \n\nEn tant que Halo Insider, vous vous joindrez à nous pour tester des fonctionnalités et du contenu exclusifs en cours de développement, en profitant des nouvelles mises à jour et améliorations en avant-première dans Halo Infinite. Votre voix compte, alors inscrivez-vous et rejoignez-nous dans des phases de test pratiques publiques pour fournir des commentaires à nos équipes de développement. \n\nRendez-vous sans tarder sur aka.ms/HaloInsider ! \n\n",
                        "hu-HU": "Légy te is Halo Insider, hogy esélyed legyen részt venni hamarosan induló online 4 fős kooperatív hadjáratunkban! \n\nA Halo Insider program a hivatalos csatorna, ahol a Halo-játékosok és a közösség tagja együttműködhetnek a 343 Industries fejlesztőivel, hogy közösen javíthassák játékainkat, termékeinket és szolgáltatásainkat. \n\n Halo Insiderként csatlakozhatsz hozzánk új, exkluzív és fejlesztés alatt álló funkciók tesztelésére, továbbá elsőként láthatod a Halo Infinite megjelenő frissítéseit és javításait. Számít a véleményed, jelentkezz tehát, és csatlakozz hozzánk publikus „csatákra” (gyakorlati játéktesztekre), majd küldd el visszajelzésed fejlesztőinknek. \n\n Regisztrálj már ma az aka.ms/HaloInsider címen! \n\n",
                        "it-IT": "Diventa un Halo Insider per avere l'occasione di partecipare ai nostri prossimi test online della Campagna Co-op a quattro giocatori! \n\nIl programma Halo Insider è il modo ufficiale con cui i fan e i membri della community di Halo possono collaborare con 343 Industries e contribuire a migliorare giochi, prodotti e servizi. \n\nIn qualità di Halo Insider, ti unirai a noi nel testare funzionalità e contenuti esclusivi ancora in fase di sviluppo, scoprendo in anteprima i nuovi aggiornamenti e miglioramenti in arrivo per Halo Infinite. La tua opinione è importante, quindi iscriviti e unisciti a noi nei test pubblici di gioco per fornire un feedback ai nostri team di sviluppo. \n\nRegistrati subito su aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "ja-JP": "Halo Insider になって、オンライン 4 プレイヤー キャンペーン協力プレイのフライトに参加するチャンスをゲットしよう! \n\nHalo Insider Program に参加することで、Halo ファンやコミュニティのメンバーが 343 Industries のゲーム、製品、サービスの向上に貢献する公式なパートナーになれます。 \n\nHalo Insider になると、『Halo Infinite』の新しいアップデートや改良をいち早く知ることができ、開発中の限定機能やコンテンツをテストできます。皆様の貴重なご意見をお待ちしております。ぜひ登録して、公開の「フライト」(テスト プレイ) に参加し、開発チームにフィードバックをお寄せください。\n\n さあ、aka.ms/HaloInsider で今すぐ登録を! \n\n",
                        "ko-KR": "Halo Insider가 되면 앞으로 있을 온라인 4인 캠페인 협동 게임 플라이팅에 참가할 기회가 생깁니다! \n\nHalo Insider 프로그램은 Halo 팬과 커뮤니티 멤버가 343 Industries와 함께 저희의 게임과 제품, 서비스를 향상시킬 수 있는 공식적인 방법입니다. \n\nHalo Insider가 되면 개발 중인 기능 및 콘텐츠의 독점 테스트에 참가하여, Halo Infinite에 추가될 새로운 업데이트 및 개선 사항을 먼저 확인하실 수 있습니다. 여러분의 의견은 중요합니다, 가입하시고 공개 '플라이팅(직접 플레이테스트)'에 참가하셔서 저희 개발 팀에 의견을 제공해 주십시오. \n\n aka.ms/HaloInsider에서 지금 등록하십시오! \n\n",
                        "nb-NO": "Bli en Halo Insider og få sjansen til å delta i kommende samarbeidsspill for 4 spillere! \n\nHalo Insider-programmet gjør det mulig for Halo-fans og medlemmer av nettfellesskapet å samarbeide med 343 Industries for å forbedre spillene, produktene og tjenestene våre. \n\nSom Halo Insider hjelper du oss med å teste eksklusive funksjoner og nytt innhold, og du blir blant de første som får sjekke ut nye oppdateringer og forbedringer som kommer til Halo Infinite. Stemmen din betyr noe, så registrer deg nå, og bli med oss på offentlige spilltester for å gi tilbakemelding til utviklingsteamene våre.\n\nRegistrerr deg i dag på aka.ms/Haloinsider \n\n",
                        "nl-NL": "Word een Halo Insider en test onze online coöp-campagne voor vier spelers! \n\nDankzij het Halo Insider-programma kunnen Halo-fans en -communityleden met 343 Industries samenwerken om onze games, producten en diensten nog verder te verbeteren. \n\nAls Halo Insider help je bij het testen van exclusieve content en functies die worden ontwikkeld. Je krijgt als eerste nieuwe updates en verbeteringen onder ogen die worden voorbereid voor Halo Infinite. Jouw mening is belangrijk! Doe mee aan de openbare 'flights' (gameplay-tests) en geef het ontwikkelteam waardevolle feedback. \n\n Registreer je vandaag nog op aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "pl-PL": "Dołącz do programu Halo Insider i zyskaj szansę na udział w nadchodzących testach kooperacyjnej kampanii online dla 4 graczy!\n\nProgram Halo Insider pozwala członkom społeczności i miłośnikom serii Halo pomagać studiu 343 Industries w doskonaleniu naszych gier, produktów i usług.\n\nPo dołączeniu do programu będziesz wraz z nami testować wyjątkowe funkcje i treści, nad którymi aktualnie pracujemy. Dzięki temu zyskasz dostęp do nowych aktualizacji i ulepszeń gry Halo Infinite. Zarejestruj się, uczestnicz w publicznych sesjach testowych i przesyłaj swoje uwagi naszym zespołom deweloperskim – twój głos ma znaczenie!\n\nZarejestruj się już dziś na aka.ms/HaloInsider!\n\n",
                        "pt-BR": "Torne-se um Halo Insider para ter a chance de participar do nosso próximo teste da Campanha Cooperativa online para 4 jogadores! \n\nO Programa Halo Insider é a forma oficial para os fãs de Halo e membros da comunidade fazerem parceria com a 343 Industries e ajudar a melhorar nossos jogos, produtos e serviços. \n\nComo Halo Insider, você se juntará a nós para testar recursos e conteúdos exclusivos de trabalho em andamento, dando uma primeira olhada nas novas atualizações e melhorias que chegam ao Halo Infinite. Sua opinião é importante, então inscreva-se e junte-se a nós em testes públicos (testes de jogo práticos) para fornecer feedback às nossas equipes de desenvolvimento. \n\n Registre-se hoje em aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "pt-PT": "Torna-te um Halo Insider para teres uma oportunidade de participar no nosso próximo lançamento da Campanha cooperativa para 4 jogadores! \n\nO programa Halo Insider é a forma oficial de os fãs e membros da comunidade do Halo se associarem à 343 Industries para ajudar a melhorar os nossos jogos, produtos e serviços. \n\nComo Halo Insider, irás juntar-te a nós para testar funcionalidades e conteúdos exclusivos em desenvolvimento, fazendo com que sejas uma das primeiras pessoas a ver as novas atualizações e melhorias do Halo Infinite. A tua opinião importa, por isso, inscreve-te e junta-te a nós nos testes de pré-lançamento públicos (testes de design práticos) para fornecer feedback às nossas equipas de desenvolvimento. \n\n Inscreve-te hoje em aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "ru-RU": "Присоединяйтесь к программе предварительной оценки Halo, и у вас появится шанс принять участие в тестировании режима совместного прохождения кампании по сети для 4 игроков!\n\nБлагодаря официальной программе предварительной оценки Halo поклонники серии и члены сообщества могут помогать 343 Industries улучшать свои игры, продукты и службы.\n\nСтав участником программы, вы сможете тестировать находящиеся в разработке функции и контент, чтобы в числе первых увидеть новинки, которые позже станут доступны всем игрокам в Halo Infinite. Ваш голос очень важен для нас, поэтому тестируйте игру и делитесь с разработчиками своим мнением.\n\nЗарегистрируйтесь прямо сейчас на сайте aka.ms/HaloInsider!\n\n",
                        "sv-SE": "Bli en Halo Insider för att få chansen att delta i vårt test av en samarbetskampanj för fyra spelare online!\n\nHalo Insider-programmet låter Halo-fans samarbeta med 343 Industries för att förbättra våra spel, produkter och tjänster.\n\nSom Halo Insider kan du testa funktioner och innehåll som fortfarande är under utveckling och få en förtitt på Halo Infinites framtid. Vi vill höra vad du tycker, så anmäl dig och var med i våra speltester för att ge våra utvecklingsteam feedback.\n\n Anmäl dig idag på aka.ms/HaloInsider! \n\n",
                        "tr-TR": "Yaklaşan çevrimiçi 4 oyunculu Harekât İş Birliği sınırlı denememize katılma şansı elde etmek için bir Halo Insider olun! \n\nHalo Insider programı, Halo hayranlarının ve topluluk üyelerinin oyunlarımızı, ürünlerimizi ve hizmetlerimizi geliştirmemize yardımcı olmak için 343 Industries ile iş birliği yapmalarının resmî yoludur. \n\nBir Halo Insider olarak, devam eden ayrıcalıklı özellik ve içerikleri test etmek için bize katılın ve Halo Infinite'e gelecek olan yeni güncellemeler ve iyileştirmelere ilk siz göz atın. Düşünceleriniz bizim için çok önemli, bu yüzden hemen kaydolun ve geliştirme ekiplerimize geri bildirim sağlamak için herkese açık olan \"test sürümlerine\" (uygulamalı oyun testlerine) katılın. \n\n Hemen aka.ms/HaloInsider adresinde kaydolun! \n\n",
                        "zh-CN": "成为 Halo Insider 就有机会获得资格，参加接下来的线上 4 人战役合作模式测试！\n\nHalo Insider 计划是光环粉丝和社区成员与 343 Industries 合作的正式方式，以此帮助改进我们的游戏、产品和服务。\n\n作为 Halo Insider，您将能参与独家开发中的功能与内容，在第一时间看到 Halo Infinite 的最新更新与改善功能。您的宝贵见解至关重要，立即注册并加入我们的游戏公开“测试”(实际游戏测试)，向我们的开发团队提供反馈。\n\n马上前往 aka.ms/HaloInsider 进行注册吧！\n\n",
                        "zh-TW": "成為 Halo Insider 就有機會獲得資格，參加接下來的線上 4 人戰役合作模式測試！\n\nHalo Insider 计划是 Halo 粉絲和社群成員與 343 Industries 合作的正式方式，以幫助改善我們的遊戲、產品和服務。\n\n成為 Halo Insider，您將能參與獨家開發中的功能與內容，在第一時間看到《Halo Infinite》的最新更新與改善功能。您的寶貴見解至關重要，立即註冊並加入我們的遊戲公開測試 (實際遊戲測試)，向我們的開發團隊提供意見回饋吧！\n\n馬上前往 aka.ms/HaloInsider 進行註冊！\n\n",
                        "qps-ploc": "ßëĉοmє а Ηаļθ Іήŝîđĕř ƒθŗ ã ¢ћàηсε тò ρãѓŧîćіφäţё іņ őΰґ цρĉómϊŋĝ ƒℓïģнτ бƒ оŋłίπэ 4-φłǻÿзř Ćãмρдĭġπ Ćо-Θр!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nŦнĕ Ħáĺσ İйşìδ℮ŕ φřōġřâм їš тħє ǿƒƒί¢ΐãℓ ωдў ƒσґ Ήãℓσ ƒάńš àňδ ĉōmмůήīтŷ mемьęŕş тǿ ρãѓтņёѓ ŵĩτћ 343 Îŋδũѕτѓїèѕ ŧö ĥĕŀр ιmφŗöνé όűя ğάмėş, φґõðũсťѕ, αήđ šêřνįčêš.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nΛѕ ª Ήãľǿ Îňŝíδëѓ, ÿøű’łĺ ĵóīń ůѕ ιŉ тєşтіńģ έж¢ļμѕĭνě щόґκ-ĩŋ-ρяόġřєşš ƒеąτцřēŝ âлď ¢ōⁿťзήτ, ğ℮ţτìⁿġ ª ƒìŗŝτ ℓôǿκ ąť иεω üφďāţēş ãⁿδ ímφѓθνеmêŉţŝ çбмīŋġ το Ηäĺö İñƒįⁿïŧэ. Ỳøüя νοΐčз маτţèřş, šσ ŝїġń ûр ªиδ јοîй цŝ íή рυвłĩč ‘ƒłιğħţş’ (ĥάńđš-σπ φļăŷτеšţѕ) тò ρřőνіδз ƒēěδьâčќ ťб оųѓ ðеνĕłôрmεņт тзåмŝ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\n Ŕэģϊѕτėг ţόďǻỳ äţ ãĸã.mš/ĤâļσÌŉşίđèѓ!  !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\n",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ьëςöмè ä Ĥäŀő Їпśìδεř ƒǿř ã ćĥąñčè τό ρåгţĩċΐφăťε íñ őùŕ ũрςǿmίŉģ ƒľїģнт ōƒ őńļíйê 4-рľаγеѓ Ćаmрдιġñ Çǿ-Ōр!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nΤђе Нąĺő Ίŋŝίďēř рŗǿğřам ïѕ ŧĥë θƒƒĭçιãŀ шâγ ƒθг Ндłǿ ƒàήš άηð čбmмūлíτŷ mέmьéřś τő ρąгŧизř щїťђ 343 Ίñðυŝŧґї℮ś ţō ħěłρ ĭmрřóνę óцř ĝамєš, φгоđûĉτś, āⁿð šęѓνį¢ėş.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nĄŝ à Наℓŏ Ìŉšĭδėŕ, ŷоΰ’ľł ĵòιл ũś ΐи ţέѕтíήĝ ĕхçłμšϊνэ ωòяк-ϊй-рґòğřęѕś ƒзатŭѓëś äπď соńтεñτ, ġёţťιⁿğ а ƒΐгšŧ ŀőøκ ат иĕẃ ϋφđªťэŝ áŉď ĩmрŕóνëмέητŝ ćοміⁿğ ţб Ηаľθ Їиƒιŋĩŧε. Ýøűř νŏïςе māτţέґś, ŝő ѕїĝŋ ύρ άŉð ĵоįň ûš îи рµьℓіç ‘ƒļĩğћтş’ (ħăήďş-όη ρŀàγţėśţś) ŧö рřőνìđě ƒё℮đьдçќ ŧό õµя đëνеľθрмėит ţєáмš.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\n Геġϊšτэґ τòðäý αŧ дķá.мѕ/ĦαļóΪηşιδέґ!  !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\n",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ъēςǿме à Ηдļø Їňŝϊðēŗ ƒôѓ â ćћåηćé τô рâřτі¢ïφàтě ìŋ ôüѓ ùφсõmīиġ ƒľΐĝнť øƒ ǿŉľíñè 4-ρłάуéг Čāmφăіğл Ĉő-Òρ!  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nŤħз Ήáĺǿ Ϊηşîðеŗ ρŕσĝяám ïš ťĥё οƒƒíčĩαĺ ẃăý ƒοґ Ĥãļô ƒâηş âпđ ćóмmџπίŧŷ мēмьєгŝ τö φдґŧňéŕ ŵітћ 343 Ĩйďΰѕŧŗìзš ţŏ нëĺр īмφяòνê õũг ģãмéš, ρґσðŭςťš, äńð ѕęгνíćеŝ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nΆŝ ā Ήάľò Îпѕίδēг, уού’ℓĺ јбíñ μѕ іл τėѕτĭņğ ěж¢ĺμѕīνэ ŵоґќ-їη-φґöĝřĕşŝ ƒёдţūгěś áⁿδ ćõήτэпť, ĝêтţìŋĝ à ƒìяŝτ ļбøκ äт ηèẅ ůрđāţεŝ άиď їмφřōνёmэⁿτş čθmίпģ тō Ĥάļø Ίñƒįņίтē. ¥ôũŕ νοΐçε мąтţэřѕ, śő ŝīģń ũφ äņđ ĵоîπ ũş ĭή ρΰьľϊς ‘ƒłîĝнťѕ’ (ћаήðŝ-ōπ ρℓáỳŧзşťş) ŧö ρґőνìđé ƒěêδвªςκ то ǿυŗ δèνèłŏрmєπť ťеαmş.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\n Ŗзģіśтзŗ ŧόðαý дτ āкã.mŝ/ΗāĺοЇйѕíδέя!  !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\n"
                    }
                },
                "ArticleImage": {
                    "Width": 1920,
                    "Height": 1080,
                    "Path": "news/Evergreen/CampaignCo-Op_MOTD.jpg"
                },
                "ArticleActions": [
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Become a Halo Insider",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Staňte se insiderem Halo.",
                                "da-DK": "Bliv en Halo Insider",
                                "de-DE": "Halo Insider werden",
                                "el-GR": "Γίνε μέλος του Halo Insider",
                                "es-ES": "Conviértete en Halo Insider",
                                "es-MX": "Únete al programa Halo Insider",
                                "fi-FI": "Liity Halo Insideriksi",
                                "fr-FR": "Devenir un Halo Insider",
                                "hu-HU": "Válj te is Halo Insiderré",
                                "it-IT": "Diventa un Halo Insider",
                                "ja-JP": "Halo Insider になろう",
                                "ko-KR": "Halo Insider가 되십시오",
                                "nb-NO": "Bli en Halo Insider",
                                "nl-NL": "Word een Halo Insider",
                                "pl-PL": "Dołącz do programu Halo Insider",
                                "pt-BR": "Torne-se um Halo Insider",
                                "pt-PT": "Torna-te um Halo Insider",
                                "ru-RU": "Предварительная оценка Halo",
                                "sv-SE": "Bli en Halo Insider",
                                "tr-TR": "Bir Halo Insider olun",
                                "zh-CN": "成为 Halo Insider",
                                "zh-TW": "成為 Halo Insider",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ьё¢őмë â Ĥāĺό İńşĩðēř !!! !!!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Вë¢омę ª Ήāĺó Íлšιďεѓ !!! !!!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ве¢бmê ā Ήàŀò Ĭήŝïďèг !!! !!!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to the Halo Insider website.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na web Halo Insider.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi fører dig til vores Halo Insider-hjemmesiden.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zur Website von Halo Insider weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στον ιστότοπο του Halo Insider.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a la página web de Halo Insider.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos al sitio web de Halo Insider.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut Halo Insiderin verkkosivuille.",
                                "fr-FR": "Nous allons vous diriger vers le site Halo Insider.",
                                "hu-HU": "A Halo Insider holnapra viszünk.",
                                "it-IT": "Sarai trasferito sul sito web di Halo Insider.",
                                "ja-JP": "詳細については、Halo Insider のウェブサイトをご確認ください。",
                                "ko-KR": "Halo Insider 웹사이트로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til Halo Insider-nettstedet.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar de website van Halo Insider.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię na stronę programu Halo Insider.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao site do Halo Insider.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao site do Halo Insider.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем вам сайт программы предварительной оценки Halo.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Halo Insiders webbplats.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi Halo Insider web sitesine aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们将带您前往 Halo Insider 网站。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們將帶您前往 Halo Insider 網站。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ŵé'ŀŀ вгϊиğ ỳöϋ ţö τђĕ Ндłò Ĩήѕîđēŗ ώēвŝїтє. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ŵé'ļŀ вѓîйġ уőϋ ťõ ťħė Ħäĺο Îñѕíðęг ẃєвѕìтê. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẁэ'ŀℓ вяïйģ ўŏц ţō ţђë Ηàłǿ Įñšìđέг ẅēъśϊŧé. !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://aka.ms/HaloInsider"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "ShortHeadline": {
                    "value": "LEADBELCHER Armor Set",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Sada brnění LEADBELCHER",
                        "da-DK": "LEADBELCHER-rustningssæt",
                        "de-DE": "Panzerungsset LEADBELCHER",
                        "el-GR": "Σετ Πανοπλίας ΜΟΛΥΒΔΟΡΙΠΤΗΣ",
                        "es-ES": "Conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER",
                        "es-MX": "Conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER",
                        "fi-FI": "LEADBELCHER-haarniskasarja",
                        "fr-FR": "Armure LEADBELCHER",
                        "hu-HU": "LEADBELCHER páncélkészlet",
                        "it-IT": "Set corazza LEADBELCHER",
                        "ja-JP": "リードベルチャー アーマー セット",
                        "ko-KR": "리드벨처 방어구 세트",
                        "nb-NO": "LEADBELCHER-rustningssett",
                        "nl-NL": "Pantserset 'LEADBELCHER'",
                        "pl-PL": "Zestaw pancerza OŁOWIANY ŁAŃCUCH",
                        "pt-BR": "Conjunto de Armadura LEADBELCHER",
                        "pt-PT": "Conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER",
                        "ru-RU": "Комплект брони «СВИНЦОВЫЙ ШАРФ»",
                        "sv-SE": "BLYSPOTTARE-rustningsset",
                        "tr-TR": "LEADBELCHER Zırh Seti",
                        "zh-CN": "喷弹者护甲套组",
                        "zh-TW": "LEADBELCHER 護甲組",
                        "qps-ploc": "£ЭΆĐΒЕŁĆĤĖΓ Ǻŕмõŕ Ѕετ !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "ĹËΛĐΒЗŁÇĦЄЯ Äřмŏŗ Şеŧ !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "ĽĒǺĐΒĔĹČНΕЃ Ăґмóѓ Śėτ !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "FullHeadline": {
                    "value": "LEADBELCHER Armor Set",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Sada brnění LEADBELCHER",
                        "da-DK": "LEADBELCHER-rustningssæt",
                        "de-DE": "Panzerungsset LEADBELCHER",
                        "el-GR": "Σετ Πανοπλίας ΜΟΛΥΒΔΟΡΙΠΤΗΣ",
                        "es-ES": "Conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER",
                        "es-MX": "Conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER",
                        "fi-FI": "LEADBELCHER-haarniskasarja",
                        "fr-FR": "Armure LEADBELCHER",
                        "hu-HU": "LEADBELCHER páncélkészlet",
                        "it-IT": "Set corazza LEADBELCHER",
                        "ja-JP": "リードベルチャー アーマー セット",
                        "ko-KR": "리드벨처 방어구 세트",
                        "nb-NO": "LEADBELCHER-rustningssett",
                        "nl-NL": "Pantserset 'LEADBELCHER'",
                        "pl-PL": "Zestaw pancerza OŁOWIANY ŁAŃCUCH",
                        "pt-BR": "Conjunto de Armadura LEADBELCHER",
                        "pt-PT": "Conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER",
                        "ru-RU": "Комплект брони «СВИНЦОВЫЙ ШАРФ»",
                        "sv-SE": "BLYSPOTTARE-rustningsset",
                        "tr-TR": "LEADBELCHER Zırh Seti",
                        "zh-CN": "喷弹者护甲套组",
                        "zh-TW": "LEADBELCHER 護甲組",
                        "qps-ploc": "£ЭΆĐΒЕŁĆĤĖΓ Ǻŕмõŕ Ѕετ !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "ĹËΛĐΒЗŁÇĦЄЯ Äřмŏŗ Şеŧ !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "ĽĒǺĐΒĔĹČНΕЃ Ăґмóѓ Śėτ !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "Body": {
                    "value": "Become a symbol of brotherhood stronger than steel. \n\nScour the trenches to claim vital territory with the LEADBELCHER Armor Set, featuring the LEADBELCHER helmet, Spelunker Light helmet attachment, Cloudjumper chest attachment, Grognards shoulder pads, Knee Shovel knee pads, Twin Teeth utility, and Citrine Wind visor, along with the Hazard Zone coating, and Ridgeback Cantonment Protocol emblem. \n\nPick up your set from the Shop today! \n\n",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Staňte se symbolem bratrství silnějšího než ocel. \n\nProjděte skrz naskrz zákopy a zaberte životně důležitá území se sadou brnění LEADBELCHER, která obsahuje helmu LEADBELCHER, doplněk helmy Jeskyňářovo světlo, doplněk hrudního brnění Nebeský skokan, nárameníky Grognardi, nákolenice Kolenní lopata, nástroj Dvojice zubů a hledí Citrínový vítr spolu s povrchem Nebezpečná zóna a emblémem Ridgebackový ubikační protokol. \n\nVyzvedněte si svoji sadu v Obchodě ještě dnes! \n\n",
                        "da-DK": "Bliv et symbol på et broderskab, der er stærkere end stål. \n\nGennemsøg skyttegravene for at gøre krav på vitalt territorium med LEADBELCHER-rustningssættet, der indeholder LEADBELCHER-hjelmen, den lette Spelunker-hjelmtilføjelse, Cloudjumper-torsotilføjelsen, Grognards-skulderplader, Knee Shovel-knæbeskyttere, Twin Teeth-udstyr og Citrine Wind-visiret sammen med Hazard Zone-overfladen og Ridgeback Cantonment Protocol-emblemet. \n\nHent dit sæt i butikken i dag! \n\n",
                        "de-DE": "Werde zum Symbol einer Bruderschaft, die stärker ist als Stahl. \n\nDurchstreife mit dem LEADBELCHER-Panzerungsset die Gräben und sichere wichtige Bereiche. Das Set enthält: LEADBELCHER-Helm, Spelunker-Light-Helmzubehör, Wolkenspringer-Brustzubehör, Grognards-Schulterpolster, Knieschaufel-Knieschoner, Zwillingszähne-Werkzeug, Citringelber-Wind-Visier, Gefahrenzone-Oberfläche und Ridgeback-Cantonment-Protocol-Emblem. \n\nHol dir heute noch das Set im Shop! \n\n",
                        "el-GR": "Γίνε ένα σύμβολο αδελφοσύνης πιο δυνατό κι από το ατσάλι. \n\nΕξερεύνησε τα χαρακώματα για να διεκδικήσεις ζωτικά εδάφη με το σετ πανοπλίας ΜΟΛΥΒΔΟΡΙΠΤΗΣ, που περιλαμβάνει το κράνος ΜΟΛΥΒΔΟΡΙΠΤΗΣ, το εξάρτημα κράνους Φως σπηλαιολόγου, το εξάρτημα θώρακα Αιθεροβάμων, τα επιθέματα ώμων Grognards, τα επιθέματα γονάτων Φτυάρι γόνατου, το βοηθητικό εργαλείο Δίδυμα δόντια, το γείσο Άνεμος κιτρίνης, μαζί με την επένδυση Ζώνη κινδύνου και το έμβλημα Πρωτόκολο καταυλισμού Ρίτζμπακ. \n\nΠάρε το σετ σου από το κατάστημα σήμερα! \n\n",
                        "es-ES": "Conviértete en un símbolo de hermandad más fuerte que el acero. \n\nRecorre las trincheras para reclamar un territorio vital con el conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER, que incluye el casco LEADBELCHER, el accesorio de casco Luz de Spelunker, el accesorio de pecho Saltanubes, las hombreras Grognards, las rodilleras Palas para las rodillas, la utilidad Dientes gemelos y el visor Viento citrino, así como el revestimiento Zona de peligro y el emblema Protocolo del acuartelamiento de Ridgeback. \n\n¡Recoge hoy mismo tu conjunto en la tienda! \n\n",
                        "es-MX": "Conviértete en un símbolo de hermandad más fuerte que el acero. \n\nConquista las trincheras para reclamar territorios cruciales con el conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER, que contiene el casco LEADBELCHER, el accesorio para casco Luz de espeleólogo, el accesorio para pecho Cloudjumper, las hombreras Grognards, las rodilleras Pala de rodilla, la herramienta Dientes gemelos y el visor Viento citrino. También incluye el recubrimiento Zona de peligro y el emblema Protocolo de acuartelamiento de Ridgeback. \n\n¡Consigue ya tu conjunto en la tienda! \n\n",
                        "fi-FI": "Tule terästä vahvemmaksi veljeyden symboliksi. \n\nTaistele juoksuhaudoissa ja ota haltuun tärkeät alueet LEADBELCH-haarniskasarjalla, jossa on LEADBELCHER-kypärä, Spelunker-valo -kypäräkiinnike, Cloudjumper-rintakiinnike, Grognardit-hartiat, Polvilapiot-polvisuojat, Kaksi hammasta -apuväline ja Sitriinituuli-visiiri, sekä Vaara-alue-pinnoite ja Ridgebackin kantonipartion protokolla -tunnus. \n\nNouda settisi Kaupasta jo tänään! \n\n",
                        "fr-FR": "Votre volonté est indéfectible. \n\nSillonnez les tranchées pour capturer des points stratégiques avec l'armure LEADBELCHER, comprenant le casque LEADBELCHER, l'accessoire de casque Lampe de spéléologue, l'accessoire de plastron Cloudjumper, les épaulières Grognards, les genouillères Pelles à genou, l'équipement utilitaire Double dent et la visière Vent jaune clair, ainsi que le revêtement Zone dangereuse et l'emblème Patrouille du camp de Ridgeback. \n\nRécupérez tout cet attirail en boutique dès aujourd'hui ! \n\n",
                        "hu-HU": "Légy az acélnál is erősebb testvériség jelképe. \n\nKússz tüzérség dúlta lövészárkokban és hódítsd méterről méterre a LEADBELCHER páncélkészlettel, amely tartalmazza a LEADBELCHER sisakot, a Spelunker Fény sisaktartozékot, a Felhőugró mellvért-kiegészítőt, a Grognards vállvértet, a Térdásók térdvédőt, az Ikerfogak eszközt és a Citrin szél sisakrostélyt, továbbá a Veszélyzóna bevontot és a Ridgeback kanton őrjárat emblémát. \n\nSzerezd meg a készletet az Áruházból még ma! \n\n",
                        "it-IT": "Diventa un simbolo di fratellanza più forte dell'acciaio. \n\nPassa al setaccio le trincee per rivendicare territorio vitale con il set corazza e il casco LEADBELCHER, la luce per casco Spelunker, l'accessorio per torace Cloudjumper, gli spallacci Grognards, le ginocchiere Knee Shovel, i foderi per coltelli Denti gemelli e il visore Citrine Wind, oltre alla livrea Zona di pericolo e all'emblema Protocollo di acquartieramento Ridgeback. \n\nFai tuo il set nel negozio oggi stesso! \n\n",
                        "ja-JP": "鋼鉄よりも強い絆の象徴となれ。\n\nリードベルチャー ヘルメット、スペランカー ライト ヘルメット アタッチメント、クラウドジャンパー チェスト アタッチメント、グロニャール ショルダーパッド、ニー シャベル ニーパッド、ツイン ティース ユーティリティ、 シトリン ウィンド バイザー、そしてハザード ゾーン コーティングとリッジバック カントーンメント プロトコル エンブレムがセットになったアーマー セットで、重要なテリトリーを守るため塹壕を駆け巡れ。\n\n今すぐショップでセットを手に入れよう!\n\n",
                        "ko-KR": "강철보다 강한 형제애의 상징이 되십시오. \n\n리드벨처 방어구 세트를 착용하고 참호를 수색하여 중요한 지역을 손에 넣으십시오. 이 세트에는 리드벨처 헬멧, 스펠렁커 조명 헬멧 부착물, 클라우드점퍼 흉부 부착물, 그로냐드 어깨 보호대, 무릎삽 무릎 보호대, 쌍둥이 치아 유틸리티, 레몬색 바람 바이저, 그리고 위험물 지역 코팅 및 릿지백 주둔지 순찰대 휘장이 포함됩니다. \n\n지금 상점에서 세트를 손에 넣으십시오! \n\n",
                        "nb-NO": "Bli et symbol på brorskap sterkere enn stål. \n\nHerje i skyttergravene for å ta tilbake viktige territorier med LEADBELCHER-rustningssettet, med LEADBELCHER-hjelm, Spelunker Light-hjelmtilbehør, Cloudjumper-brysttilbehør, Grognards-skulderputer, Knee Shovel-knebeskyttere, Twin Teeth-verktøy og Citrine Wind-visir, i tillegg til Hazard Zone-belegget og Ridgeback Cantonment Protocol-emblemet. \n\nHent settet ditt i butikken i dag! \n\n",
                        "nl-NL": "Een symbool van broederschap die sterker is dan staal. \n\nDoorzoek de loopgraven om vitaal gebied te veroveren met de pantserset 'LEADBELCHER', die bestaat uit de helm 'Leadbelcher', de helmuitbreiding 'Mijnlamp', de borstkasuitbreiding 'Cloudjumper', de schouderbescherming 'Grognards', de kniebeschermers 'Laadschop', het hulpmiddel 'Twin Teeth' en het vizier 'Citrienwind', samen met de coating 'Gevarenzone' en het embleem 'Ridgeback Cantonment-patrouille'. \n\nHaal de set vandaag nog in de shop! \n\n",
                        "pl-PL": "Stań się silniejszym niż stal symbolem braterstwa.\n\nPrzemierzaj okopy i zdobywaj kluczowe obszary po wyposażeniu zestawu pancerza OŁOWIANY ŁAŃCUCH, który zawiera hełm OŁOWIANY ŁAŃCUCH, dodatek do hełmu Światło grotołaza, dodatek do napierśnika Podniebny skoczek, naramienniki Wiarusi, nakolanniki Kolanowe łopaty, akcesorium użytkowe Bliźniacze zęby i wizjer Cytrynowy wiatr, a także powłokę Strefa zagrożenia i emblemat Patrol kwater wojskowych odyńca.\n\nOdbierz swój zestaw ze sklepu już dziś!\n\n",
                        "pt-BR": "Torne-se um símbolo de fraternidade mais forte que aço. \n\nPercorra as trincheiras para reivindicar território vital com o conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER, que inclui o capacete LEADBELCHER, acessório de capacete Luz Espelhadora, acessório de peitoral Saltador de Nuvens, ombreiras Grognards, joelheiras Joelho-Pá, utilitário Dentes Gêmeos e viseira Vento Citrino, juntamente com o revestimento Zona de Risco e o emblema do Protocolo de Cantonamento de Ridgeback. \n\nAdquira seu conjunto na Loja hoje mesmo! \n\n",
                        "pt-PT": "Torna-te um símbolo de irmandade mais forte que o aço. \n\nExplora as trincheiras para reivindicar território vital com o Conjunto de armadura LEADBELCHER, que inclui o capacete LEADBELCHER, o acessório de capacete Luz de espeleólogo, o acessório de peito Cloudjumper, as ombreiras Grognards, as joelheiras Pá de joelho, o utilitário Dentes gémeos e a viseira Vento cítrico, juntamente com o revestimento Zona de perigo e o emblema do Protocolo de acantonamento de Ridgeback. \n\nObtém o teu conjunto na loja ainda hoje! \n\n",
                        "ru-RU": "Станьте символом братства, узы которого прочнее стали.\n\nЗачищайте окопы и захватывайте стратегически важные районы, облачившись в комплект брони «СВИНЦОВЫЙ ШАРФ», который содержит шлем «СВИНЦОВЫЙ ШАРФ», надстройку шлема «Фонарь спелеолога», нагрудный модуль «Облачный десант», наплечники «Ворчуны», наколенники «Коленные лопаты», вспомогательное снаряжение «Двойные зубы» и визор «Лимонно-жёлтый ветер», а также окраску «Опасная зона» и эмблему «Дозор военной базы „Риджбек“».\n\nЗаходите в магазин за этим комплектом прямо сейчас!\n\n",
                        "sv-SE": "Bli en symbol för ett brödraskap starkare än stål.\n\nRensa skyttegravarna för att ta viktigt territorium med rustningssetet BLYSPOTTARE, som innehåller hjälmen BLYSPOTTARE, hjälmtillbehöret Grottforskarlampa, bröstkorgstillbehöret Molndykare, axelskydden Gammelsoldater, knäskydden Knäspadar, det praktiska tillbehöret Tvillingtänder, visiret Citrongul vind, beläggningen Farozon och emblemet Ridgeback-militärförläggningspatrull.\n\nSkaffa ditt set i butiken idag!\n\n",
                        "tr-TR": "Çelikten daha güçlü bir kardeşliğin sembolü olun. \n\nLEADBELCHER kaskı, Spelunker Işığı kask eklentisi, Bulut Cambazlı göğüs eklentisi, Grognards omuz zırhları, Diz Kürekleri dizlikleri, İkiz Dişler yardımcı aleti ve Sitrin Rüzgârı siperliğinin yanı sıra Tehlike Bölgesi kaplaması ve Ridgeback Ordugâhı Protokolü amblemini içeren LEADBELCHER Zırh Seti ile son derece önemli bir bölgeyi ele geçirmek için siperleri aşındırın. \n\nSetinizi hemen Mağaza'dan alın! \n\n",
                        "zh-CN": "化身比钢铁更坚定的兄弟情象徵。\n\n穿上喷弹者护甲组，搜查每一道壕沟，占领重要领土。这套战地戎装包括喷弹者头盔、地下冒险灯头盔配件、云团跳跃者胸部配件、老兵护肩、膝盖铲护膝、双齿配件、黄水晶之风面甲、危险区域涂装，以及脊背军营巡逻队徽章。\n\n立即前往商店入手这个护甲套组！ \n\n",
                        "zh-TW": "化身比鋼鐵更堅定的兄弟情象徵。\n\n穿上 LEADBELCHER 護甲組，搜查每一道壕溝，佔領重要領土。這套戰地戎裝包括 LEADBELCHER 頭盔、洞穴探險照明燈頭盔配件、雲躍者胸部配件、格羅納茲護肩、膝鏟護膝、雙生牙配件、茶晶風面甲、危險區域塗裝，以及脊背駐地協定徽章。\n\n立即前往商店入手這套護甲組！ \n\n",
                        "qps-ploc": "Βëćòmέ α ѕўмьοĺ ǿƒ ьřοŧђєгђóòď şŧŕόŋġэŗ ťђαⁿ šτеэℓ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nŜçőũŗ ţћ℮ ţřĕňćħēś τò ćŀдім νΐŧªŀ τεřřїтόřγ ŵīŧн тћё ĿĚÂĎВËĹČĦĔГ Ąřмøґ Śëţ, ƒèªтŭѓĩηġ τђē £ЭÁĐВĖĽ€ΉĖŘ ђέℓmеŧ, Ѕрĕļϋпкеѓ Łíĝћτ ђęĺмěţ ªτťąćнmеиť, Ċľσџδјųmφея çђεŝτ аτŧāċђмęηţ, Ğґбĝⁿªѓďŝ ѕнσџℓδèґ рαδѕ, Ќⁿέе Şħőνέł ķήёέ рªðş, Ťщϊπ Τéēτн υŧĩłιτÿ, ǻπď Ċіτŕįńè Щîлď νΐşŏя, âĺöńğ шϊτђ ťħз Ήǻżаѓđ Ζσńέ çоąτìηĝ, άηđ Řïđĝęъд¢ķ Çâⁿťóŋmеήť Ρŕǿτσςŏĺ ёmвŀéм.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\nРįćĸ ŭρ ỳσŭѓ ѕĕт ƒѓǿм тћę Ŝћőρ тöδάÿ!  !!! !!! !!! !!\n\n",
                        "qps-ploca": "В℮сσмę ä ѕỳмъół ǿƒ ьѓбтĥëгђŏöð ѕτřолğēг тĥαπ ŝτĕзℓ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nЅсőϋŗ ŧĥê тŗěņčђėŝ ťǿ čļдĭм νїтăł ťεřґĩтöґỳ шīťħ τĥè ŁÉÃÐВЭ₤€ΗΣГ Äŗмǿř Šėт, ƒэάŧμѓιńģ ŧħэ ĻĒǺÐЬЕĻĆĦЕЯ ĥеłměţ, Şφĕℓυŉķэґ Ļιģħт нēŀмэτ ǻтτąçћмέŉτ, Çľõųďĵùmρėя ¢ĥėѕŧ ατтǻ¢ĥmєπτ, Ğґǿģлāŗδś śноųĺðεŕ ρâđѕ, Κиё℮ Šћóνэľ κлєè ρáđŝ, Тẃïл Ŧ℮éţђ űťíľίτỳ, ªńð Ćïтŗîⁿє Ŵίňð νĭŝōŗ, αľôńģ ẃітн ťђэ Нåžªгð Żбйё ¢θąτĭпģ, άŋδ Ŕĩδğ℮вâćκ €ăŉŧǿпm℮ñт Ρřōţóĉõℓ ëmьĺёm.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\nΡїĉκ ųφ ỳθúѓ śêť ƒгøm ŧђ℮ Şђόφ тбđàý!  !!! !!! !!! !!\n\n",
                        "qps-plocm": "Бэςõmé å šÿмъθľ öƒ ъŕøтћέѓђбŏđ šťŕōŋĝεř τћâŉ šťеёℓ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! \n\nŠςőúŗ ţнě тŕéⁿĉђèѕ ŧõ ¢łǻΐм νīŧάľ ťĕяřіŧóŕу щϊţћ тĥэ Ľ∑ĀĎßÈĽÇΉЄŖ Аřmоґ Şэť, ƒέàŧύřΐŉģ ŧђë ŁЄАĐЪÉĹĆĦЗŘ ħ℮ľmèτ, Ѕφєŀΰńκėŗ Ľιĝħŧ ћеłmèţ āţτâсĥмëņτ, Ċłθûðĵúмφĕя ćнěşţ ªťτǻçђmэйτ, Ğѓθġñâґđś šħòůļđëŗ рăðѕ, Ķňёè Ŝнòνěŀ ќиęз ρąđŝ, Ťẁіπ Ŧеèтħ ùтϊľīтý, äňð Čίτґíńē Щΐиď νįѕøř, āłόлĝ ẅįţђ ŧћë Ήàżăгđ Žоηэ čόãťíŉģ, àπð Ŕíďğεьàċķ Čάńтòŉмеŉţ Ρгοτő¢бℓ ёмъĺєm.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !\n\nРíĉк ùр ŷōũґ šêţ ƒřőm ţĥз Ŝħőφ тôđǻŷ!  !!! !!! !!! !!\n\n"
                    }
                },
                "ArticleImage": {
                    "Width": 1920,
                    "Height": 1080,
                    "Path": "news/Season2/Shop/Leadbelcher_ArmorBundle_Shop_MOTD.jpg"
                },
                "ArticleActions": [
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Head to Shop",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Přejít na Obchod",
                                "da-DK": "Gå til butikken",
                                "de-DE": "Zum Shop",
                                "el-GR": "Μετάβαση στο Κατάστημα",
                                "es-ES": "Ve a la tienda",
                                "es-MX": "Entra a la tienda",
                                "fi-FI": "Siirry kauppaan",
                                "fr-FR": "Vers la boutique",
                                "hu-HU": "Ugrás az Áruházra",
                                "it-IT": "Vai al negozio",
                                "ja-JP": "ショップへ移動",
                                "ko-KR": "상점으로 이동",
                                "nb-NO": "Gå til butikken",
                                "nl-NL": "Ga naar de winkel",
                                "pl-PL": "Przejdź do sklepu",
                                "pt-BR": "Acesse a Loja",
                                "pt-PT": "Vai para a Loja",
                                "ru-RU": "Заглянуть в магазин",
                                "sv-SE": "Gå till butik",
                                "tr-TR": "Mağaza'ya Git",
                                "zh-CN": "前往商店",
                                "zh-TW": "前往商店",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ήεáδ ţō Şĥòφ !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ήέāđ ťό Šћóφ !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ήεаð ţό Ŝħòр !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll navigate you over to the Shop to check it out.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Přesuneme vás na Obchod, abyste se mohli podívat.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi sender dig over til vores butik, så du kan se på den.",
                                "de-DE": "Wir leiten dich zum Shop weiter, damit du ihn dir ansehen kannst.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε βοηθήσουμε να μεταβείς στο Κατάστημα για να ρίξεις μια ματιά.",
                                "es-ES": "Te redirigiremos a la tienda para que le eches un vistazo.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a la Tienda para que veas lo que hay.",
                                "fi-FI": "Viemme sinut kauppaan tutustuaksesi siihen.",
                                "fr-FR": "Vous arriverez à la boutique pour voir ce qui y est proposé.",
                                "hu-HU": "Az Áruházhoz navigálunk, hogy átnézd a kínálatot.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti indirizzeremo al Negozio per completare l'acquisto.",
                                "ja-JP": "ショップの内容をご案内します。",
                                "ko-KR": "상점을 확인할 수 있도록 이동시켜 드리겠습니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til butikken, så du kan sjekke den ut.",
                                "nl-NL": "We brengen je naar de winkel, zodat je 'm kunt bekijken.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię do sklepu – przejrzyj go.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você à Loja para conferir.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te até à Loja para que a possas explorar.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы проведём вас по магазину, чтобы вы нашли в нём всё необходимое.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till butiken så du kan kolla in den.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi göz atmanız için Mağaza'ya yönlendireceğiz.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们会带领您前往商店进行查看。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會引導您前往商店瞧瞧。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ẅê'ĺĺ ηǻνíĝǻţ℮ ýθŭ ǿνεя тŏ тђз Şнõρ ŧǿ ćћéсĸ ΐť óύτ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ẃз'ĺł ηāνìĝάťě ŷōц ôνёя ťσ тĥè Šђôφ ŧο ςћé¢ĸ іŧ оџŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẁэ'łĺ ňãνíġάτέ ўøű õνέг тσ ţħë Ѕĥǿρ ŧō ¢ћеĉк įţ øûт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "news://slamsContentScreen?slamsUri=store"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "ShortHeadline": {
                    "value": "Bluewood Bole Warthog Coating",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Povrch warthogu Kmen condalie",
                        "da-DK": "Bluewood Bole Warthog-overflade",
                        "de-DE": "Warthog-Oberfläche „Blauholz-Stamm“",
                        "el-GR": "Επίστρωση Αγριογούρουνου Κορμός Μπλε ξύλου",
                        "es-ES": "Revestimiento Tronco de madera azul de Warthog",
                        "es-MX": "Recubrimiento para Warthog Bluewood Bole",
                        "fi-FI": "Sinipuu-Warthog-pinnoite",
                        "fr-FR": "Revêtement de warthog Tronc de bois-bleu",
                        "hu-HU": "Kékfa törzs Warthog bevonat",
                        "it-IT": "Livrea per Warthog Bolus del bosco blu",
                        "ja-JP": "ブルーウッド ボレ ワートホグ コーティング",
                        "ko-KR": "블루우드 줄기 워트호그 코팅",
                        "nb-NO": "Bluewood Bole Warthog-belegg",
                        "nl-NL": "Warthog-coating 'Stam van blauwhout'",
                        "pl-PL": "Powłoka guźca Pień niebieskiego drzewa",
                        "pt-BR": "Revestimento de Warthog Tronco de Madeira-Azul",
                        "pt-PT": "Revestimento Warthog de tronco de madeira azul",
                        "ru-RU": "Окраска «Вепря» «Кряж синего дерева»",
                        "sv-SE": "Warthog-beläggning: Blå skogens stam",
                        "tr-TR": "Morumsu Balçık Kirpi Kaplaması",
                        "zh-CN": "蓝木树干疣猪号涂层",
                        "zh-TW": "藍木樹疣豬號塗層",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ьłůêщόőđ ßõĺέ Ẃąŗţħθĝ Ċǿαŧіņġ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Βℓџ℮ώōбδ Ъöłë Щάгтђóģ Çǿàтîñģ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ъľůэшöθď ßοłз Ẁåřтħбĝ Čõǻŧΐŋģ !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "FullHeadline": {
                    "value": "Bluewood Bole Warthog Coating",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Povrch warthogu Kmen condalie",
                        "da-DK": "Bluewood Bole Warthog-overflade",
                        "de-DE": "Warthog-Oberfläche „Blauholz-Stamm“",
                        "el-GR": "Επίστρωση Αγριογούρουνου Κορμός Μπλε ξύλου",
                        "es-ES": "Revestimiento Tronco de madera azul de Warthog",
                        "es-MX": "Recubrimiento para Warthog Bluewood Bole",
                        "fi-FI": "Sinipuu-Warthog-pinnoite",
                        "fr-FR": "Revêtement de warthog Tronc de bois-bleu",
                        "hu-HU": "Kékfa törzs Warthog bevonat",
                        "it-IT": "Livrea per Warthog Bolus del bosco blu",
                        "ja-JP": "ブルーウッド ボレ ワートホグ コーティング",
                        "ko-KR": "블루우드 줄기 워트호그 코팅",
                        "nb-NO": "Bluewood Bole Warthog-belegg",
                        "nl-NL": "Warthog-coating 'Stam van blauwhout'",
                        "pl-PL": "Powłoka guźca Pień niebieskiego drzewa",
                        "pt-BR": "Revestimento de Warthog Tronco de Madeira-Azul",
                        "pt-PT": "Revestimento Warthog de tronco de madeira azul",
                        "ru-RU": "Окраска «Вепря» «Кряж синего дерева»",
                        "sv-SE": "Warthog-beläggning: Blå skogens stam",
                        "tr-TR": "Morumsu Balçık Kirpi Kaplaması",
                        "zh-CN": "蓝木树干疣猪号涂层",
                        "zh-TW": "藍木樹疣豬號塗層",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ьłůêщόőđ ßõĺέ Ẃąŗţħθĝ Ċǿαŧіņġ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Βℓџ℮ώōбδ Ъöłë Щάгтђóģ Çǿàтîñģ !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ъľůэшöθď ßοłз Ẁåřтħбĝ Čõǻŧΐŋģ !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                },
                "Body": {
                    "value": "Does not include elbow grease or headlight fluid. \n\nComplete all of your Weekly Challenges and the Ultimate Challenge to earn this week’s Ultimate Reward – the Bluewood Bole Warthog coating. \n\nA new Ultimate Reward will become available every week, so be sure to keep an eye on your Challenges and take advantage of these free rewards..",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Nevyžaduje tvrdou dřinu ani kapalinu do potkávacích světel! \n\nDokončete všechny své týdenní výzvy i ultimátní výzvu a získáte ultimátní odměnu tohoto týdne – povrch warthogu Kmen condalie. \n\nKaždý týden bude k dispozici nová ultimátní odměna, proto nezapomeňte své výzvy sledovat a tyto bezplatné odměny využijte.",
                        "da-DK": "Indeholder ikke hverken knofedt eller forlygtevæske! \n\nGennemfør alle dine ugentlige udfordringer og den ultimative udfordring for at optjene denne uges ultimative belønning – Bluewood Bole Warthog-overfladen til din Warthog.  \n\nEn ny ultimativ belønning bliver tilgængelig hver uge, så sørg for at holde øje med dine udfordringer og udnytte disse gratis belønninger.",
                        "de-DE": "Enthält weder Muskelschmalz noch Scheinwerferflüssigkeit. \n\nSchließe alle deine wöchentlichen Herausforderungen und die ultimative Herausforderung ab, um die ultimative Belohnung dieser Woche zu erhalten – die Warthog-Oberfläche „Blauholz-Stamm“. \n\nJede Woche wird eine neue ultimative Belohnung verfügbar sein, also behalte deine Herausforderungen im Auge und nutze diese kostenlosen Belohnungen.",
                        "el-GR": "Δεν περιλαμβάνει γράσο αγκώνα ή υγρό προβολέων. \n\nΟλοκλήρωσε όλες τις Εβδομαδιαίες Προκλήσεις σου και την Απόλυτη Πρόκληση για να κερδίσεις την Απόλυτη Ανταμοιβή αυτής της εβδομάδας – την επίστρωση Αγριογούρουνου Κορμός Μπλε ξύλου. \n\nΚάθε εβδομάδα, θα γίνεται διαθέσιμη μια νέα Απόλυτη Ανταμοιβή, οπότε φρόντισε να παρακολουθείς τις Προκλήσεις σου και να επωφεληθείς από αυτές τις δωρεάν ανταμοιβές.",
                        "es-ES": "No incluye grasa para recodos ni líquido para faros. \n\nCompleta todos tus retos semanales y el reto definitivo para conseguir la recompensa definitiva de esta semana: el revestimiento Tronco de madera azul para Razorback. \n\nHabrá una recompensa definitiva cada semana, así que no pierdas de vista los retos y hazte con todas las recompensas gratuitas.",
                        "es-MX": "No incluye el líquido para las luces ni el sudor de tu frente. \n\nCompleta todos tus desafíos semanales y el desafío definitivo para obtener la recompensa definitiva de esta semana: el recubrimiento Bluewood Bole para Warthog. \n\nCada semana estará disponible una nueva recompensa definitiva, así que no pierdas de vista tus desafíos y aprovecha estas recompensas gratuitas.",
                        "fi-FI": "Ei sisällä rasvaa eikä etuvalonestettä. \n\nSuorita kaikki viikoittaiset haasteesi ja päähaasteesi ansaitaksesi tämän viikon pääpalkinnon – Sinipuu-pinnoitteen Warthogillesi. \n\nUusi pääpalkinto tulee saataville joka viikko, joten muista pitää silmällä haasteitasi ja hyödyntää näitä ilmaisia palkintoja.",
                        "fr-FR": "De quoi flanquer une peur bleue à tous ceux qui croiseront votre route. \n\nAccomplissez tous vos défis hebdomadaires ainsi que le défi ultime pour gagner la récompense ultime de cette semaine, à savoir le revêtement de warthog Tronc de bois-bleu. \n\nUne nouvelle récompense ultime sera disponible chaque semaine, alors pensez à garder un œil sur vos défis pour en profiter gratuitement !",
                        "hu-HU": "Nincs benne gépzsír vagy fejlámpaolaj! \n\nTeljesítsd az összes heti kihívást és a végső kihívást, hogy megszerezd az eheti végső jutalmat – a Kékfa törzs Warthog bevonatot. \n\nMinden héten új végső jutalom válik elérhetővé, ezért tartsd a szemedet a kihívásokon, és használd ki az ingyenes jutalmakat.",
                        "it-IT": "Olio di gomito ed estratto di materia grigia non inclusi. \n\nCompleta tutte le tue Sfide settimanali e la Sfida suprema per ottenere il Premio supremo di questa settimana: la livrea per Warthog Bolus del bosco blu. \n\nOgni settimana sarà disponibile un nuovo Premio supremo, quindi tieni sempre d'occhio le tue Sfide e approfitta di questi premi gratuiti.",
                        "ja-JP": "カーナビ、レコーダーのオプションは含まれません。\n\nウィークリー チャレンジとアルティメット チャレンジをすべてクリアすると、今週のアルティメット リワードであるブルーウッド ボレ ワートホグ コーティングが手に入ります。\n\n毎週新たなアルティメット リワードが登場しますので、チャレンジは常にチェックし、無料のリワードを取り逃がさないようにしましょう。",
                        "ko-KR": "팔꿈치 윤활유나 전조등 기름은 포함되지 않습니다. \n\n모든 주간 챌린지 및 궁극 챌린지를 완료하고 이번 주의 궁극 보상인 블루우드 줄기 워트호그 코팅을 획득하십시오. \n\n매주 새로운 궁극 보상이 제공될 예정이니 챌린지를 자주 확인하여 이 무료 보상 혜택을 놓치지 마십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Inkluderer ikke ekstra innsats eller væske til hodelykt. \n\nFullfør alle de ukentlige utfordringene og den ultimate utfordringen for å få denne ukens ultimate belønning – Bluewood Bole Warthog-belegget. \n\nDet kommer en ny ulitmat belønning hver uke, så sørg for å følge med på utfordringene dine og dra nytte av gratisbelønningene.",
                        "nl-NL": "Een mooie gelegenheid om de handen uit de mouwen te steken. \n\nVoltooi al je weekuitdagingen en de ultieme uitdaging om de ultieme beloning van deze week te verdienen: de Warthog-coating 'Stam van blauwhout'. \n\nElke week is er een nieuwe ultieme beloning beschikbaar, dus hou je uitdagingen in de gaten en profiteer van deze gratis beloningen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Trzeba tylko trochę pracy i płynu do świateł!\n\nUkończ wszystkie cotygodniowe wyzwania i ostateczne wyzwanie, aby zdobyć ostateczną nagrodę tego tygodnia – powłokę guźca Pień niebieskiego drzewa.\n\nNowa ostateczna nagroda będzie dostępna co tydzień, więc pamiętajcie, aby mieć oko na wyzwania i skorzystać z tych darmowych nagród.",
                        "pt-BR": "Não inclui graxa de cotovelo ou fluido de farol. \n\nConclua todos os seus Desafios Semanais e o Desafio Final para ganhar a Recompensa Final desta semana: o revestimento Tronco de Madeira-Azul para Warthog. \n\nUma nova Recompensa Final é disponibilizada a cada semana, então lembre-se de ficar de olho em seus Desafios e aproveitar essas recompensas gratuitas.",
                        "pt-PT": "Não inclui trabalho duro nem líquido para faróis. \n\nCompleta todos os teus Desafios Semanais e o Desafio Ultimate para ganhares a Recompensa Ultimate desta semana – o revestimento Warthog de tronco de madeira azul. \n\nUma nova Recompensa Ultimate estará disponível todas as semanas, por isso, não te esqueças de estar atento aos teus Desafios e aproveitar estas recompensas gratuitas.",
                        "ru-RU": "Терпение и труд, а также самопальный «ксенон» в комплект не входят.\n\nЗавершите все еженедельные и главное испытание, чтобы получить высшую награду этой недели — окраску «Вепря» «Кряж синего дерева».\n\nНовая главная награда появляется каждую неделю, так что следите за испытаниями и получайте бесплатные награды.",
                        "sv-SE": "Strålkastarväska ingår inte.\n\nKlara alla veckoutmaningar och den ultimata utmaningen för att få veckans ultimata belöning – warthog-beläggningen Blå skogens stam.\n\nEn ny ultimat belöning släpps varje vecka, så håll koll på utmaningarna och håva in belöningarna som väntar.",
                        "tr-TR": "Alın teri veya fiziksel güç içermez! \n\nBu haftaki Nihai Ödül olan Morumsu Balçık Kirpi kaplamasını kazanmak için tüm Haftalık Mücadeleler ve Nihai Mücadele'yi tamamlayın. \n\nHer hafta yeni bir Nihai Ödül verilecek, bu yüzden Mücadeleler bölümüne devamlı göz atın ve bu ücretsiz ödüllerden yararlanın.",
                        "zh-CN": "恕不附赠肘部润滑油和车头灯燃料。\n\n完成每周挑战及终极挑战，获取每周的终极奖励“蓝木树干疣猪号涂层”。\n\n我们每周都将推出新的终极奖励，请务必关注挑战菜单，赢取这些免费奖励，助力战事。",
                        "zh-TW": "恕不附贈肘部潤滑油和車頭燈燃料。\n\n完成所有每週挑戰和終極挑戰，就能獲得本週的終極獎勵：藍木樹疣豬號塗層。\n\n我們每週都會提供新的終極獎勵，因此請務必留意您的挑戰狀態，好好把握獲得免費獎勵的機會。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ðøěŝ ñöŧ їπčľµδě ℮ℓвοщ ğřėªśέ öѓ ћěάðłΐģћŧ ƒłűіδ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nСŏmрľзŧė äŀĺ øƒ ýθüř Ẃеёкľγ Ċћªℓłėиğéѕ ãⁿδ ŧнê Ũĺťímàŧє €ђáŀĺ℮йĝĕ тб èãŕň ţħïś ẁзєќ’ѕ Ųŀťιмãťė Ŗēŵаŗď – ťħε Βℓµεшǿøď ßоĺé Ẅαŕтнόğ ċōąţίηģ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nÁ и℮ẃ Џℓтìматé Řєẅäřđ ωĩļľ ъэčомε âναīĺąъľę ėνéŗỳ ŵêэκ, ŝσ ьè ŝųяë ŧσ ķзéφ áл ёŷé őи ỳбųř €ћàĺľĕŋĝēŝ áñð ţãķ℮ àðνăпτдĝé όƒ ŧнεѕè ƒязē ŕèώáгδѕ.. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Đöзš ŉбť ΐñсℓůðє εĺьôщ ġґëαѕê σř ħěǻðļїĝħţ ƒłύϊđ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nÇόmρľзţз ăŀℓ ôƒ ŷσůŗ Ẃêеќľÿ Čћăĺľεⁿģėѕ ªηď ŧħе Űļťїmãţę Сћăŀĺεйġе ŧо єагń ťħіş ώė℮ĸ’ś Цĺŧīмąţĕ Яêώαŕđ – τће ßℓµεшоθđ Βőļє Ẃªřŧнσĝ çσâţĩήğ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nΔ ηёώ Űĺτιmдţė Яēщάяð ẃįŀĺ ьęċòмέ дναϊļàъľз ёνēŕý ẅэēķ, śо ьз ѕџяз τσ ķĕёρ äл ёýé ŏл ŷöúř Čħąľŀêήĝęš аŋð ťаĸē åďνąиţаģė ǿƒ тђ℮şě ƒŕеє яêщąŕďš.. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ďőέś πóţ ΐŉċĺΰδĕ ëŀьōώ ġгеäśĕ σŗ ĥёдđℓìğђτ ƒłџįδ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nČōмφĺεţз äℓℓ оƒ ýбúя Ẅєзķļу €ħąľľέήģęѕ ǻлð ťĥē Ùĺţĩmăţ℮ Ċђāłℓëńġė ŧб зäŗņ ťђìş ŵę℮к’ѕ Ũŀτіматė Ŗєŵåŕđ – тħê Βłυęωθǿď Ьōℓé Ŵåѓťћōğ ĉǿǻŧιηģ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!\n\nΆ лēω Ûĺťїmªţĕ Ŗеẅäŗđ ẅĩĺľ ьêĉøм℮ ãνäìℓäвłë ένзгÿ ẅěëĸ, śσ ьě şμгē τõ кé℮р äπ εÿе òή ỳōûŗ Čħªľℓėŋģэś ªпδ τåĸε ǻðνªňťāğέ ǿƒ ťђėŝĕ ƒřεё гєẃάŗδѕ.. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                },
                "ArticleImage": {
                    "Width": 1920,
                    "Height": 1080,
                    "Path": "news/Season2/UltimateRewards/BluewoodBole_VehicleCoating_S2_Ultimate_MOTD.jpg"
                },
                "ArticleActions": [
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Check Challenge Progress",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zkontrolovat průběh výzvy",
                                "da-DK": "Tjek dine udfordringsfremskridt",
                                "de-DE": "Herausforderungsfortschritt überprüfen",
                                "el-GR": "Έλεγχος προόδου πρόκλησης",
                                "es-ES": "Comprobar el progreso del desafío",
                                "es-MX": "Revisar el progreso del desafío",
                                "fi-FI": "Tarkista haasteen edistyminen",
                                "fr-FR": "Vérifier la progression de défi",
                                "hu-HU": "Kihívási haladás megtekintése",
                                "it-IT": "Verifica l'avanzamento della Sfida",
                                "ja-JP": "チャレンジの進行状況を確認",
                                "ko-KR": "챌린지 진행 상황 확인",
                                "nb-NO": "Sjekk utfordringsfremdrift",
                                "nl-NL": "Uitdagingsvoortgang bekijken",
                                "pl-PL": "Sprawdź postępy w wyzwaniu",
                                "pt-BR": "Verificar o Progresso do Desafio",
                                "pt-PT": "Verifica o teu progresso no desafio",
                                "ru-RU": "Узнать прогресс в испытании",
                                "sv-SE": "Se utmaningsframsteg",
                                "tr-TR": "Mücadele İlerlemesini Kontrol Et",
                                "zh-CN": "查看挑战进度",
                                "zh-TW": "查看挑戰進度",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ćħéċк Ĉħāłļéпģé Рŗбģѓěŝś !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Čћёĉќ Çђдŀľ℮πģė Ρяοġŗėšѕ !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ĉђė¢ķ Сĥǻľľëŉģё Ρяοĝřέšŝ !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll navigate you over to the Challenge menu.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Přesuneme vás na nabídku Výzva.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi sender dig til Udfordringer-menuen.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zum Herausforderungsmenü weitergeleitet.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε βοηθήσουμε να μεταβείς στο μενού Προκλήσεων.",
                                "es-ES": "Te redirigiremos al menú de desafío.",
                                "es-MX": "Te guiaremos al menú de Desafíos.",
                                "fi-FI": "Viemme sinut Haaste-valikkoon.",
                                "fr-FR": "Vous arriverez au menu Défi.",
                                "hu-HU": "A Kihívás menühöz navigálunk.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti indirizzeremo al menu Sfida.",
                                "ja-JP": "チャレンジ メニューをご案内します。",
                                "ko-KR": "챌린지 메뉴로 이동시켜 드리겠습니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til utfordringsmenyen.",
                                "nl-NL": "We brengen je naar de uitdagingen.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię do menu wyzwania.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao menu de Desafios.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te até ao menu do Desafio.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы покажем вам, как устроено меню испытаний.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till utmaningsmenyn.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi Mücadele menüsüne yönlendireceğiz.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们会带领您前往挑战菜单进行查看。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們會引導您前往挑戰選單。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ẃё'ľŀ иãνΐĝдţέ ŷσυ òνéѓ ţŏ ťћė Ċħάļŀěήġє мëňů. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ẁě'łℓ ņąνíğăτέ ўőũ όνéг τø ţћę Снäļļéηĝё мёлũ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Шз'ĺľ ηανïġáţз ŷθµ øνέя τō ťнê Сђаļŀэйĝĕ меňù. !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "news://slamsContentScreen?slamsUri=progression_menu"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "ShortHeadline": {
                    "value": "Unity Emblem &amp; Nameplate",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Emblém a jmenovka Jednota",
                        "da-DK": "Unity-emblem og -navneskilt",
                        "de-DE": "Emblem und Namensschild „Einheit“",
                        "el-GR": "Έμβλημα και πινακίδα Unity",
                        "es-ES": "Emblema y placa de identificación de Unity",
                        "es-MX": "Emblema y placa de identificación de Unidad",
                        "fi-FI": "Yhtenäisyys-tunnus ja nimikyltti",
                        "fr-FR": "Emblème et plaque nominative Unité",
                        "hu-HU": "Egység embléma és névtábla",
                        "it-IT": "Emblema e targa identificativa Unità",
                        "ko-KR": "통합 휘장 및 명판",
                        "nb-NO": "Unity-emblem og -navneskilt",
                        "nl-NL": "Eenheid-embleem en -naamplaatje",
                        "pl-PL": "Emblemat i plakietka Jedność",
                        "pt-BR": "Emblema e Placa de Identificação Unidade",
                        "pt-PT": "Emblema e placa de identificação da Unidade",
                        "ru-RU": "Эмблема и табличка с именем «Единство»",
                        "sv-SE": "Sammanhållning-emblem och -namnskylt",
                        "tr-TR": "Birlik Amblemi ve İsim Plakası",
                        "zh-CN": "“团结 ”名牌和徽章",
                        "zh-TW": "「團結」名牌和徽章",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ûņïтў Еmъĺém &amp; Ňăмēρļαťэ !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ųňΐτў Ёmвℓěм &amp; Ñάмĕрĺåτé !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ũⁿΐŧў ∑mвŀзm &amp; Ňǻmĕρľąτё !!! !!! !"
                    }
                },
                "FullHeadline": {
                    "value": "Unity Emblem &amp; Nameplate",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Emblém a jmenovka Jednota",
                        "da-DK": "Unity-emblem og -navneskilt",
                        "de-DE": "Emblem und Namensschild „Einheit“",
                        "el-GR": "Έμβλημα και πινακίδα Unity",
                        "es-ES": "Emblema y placa de identificación de Unity",
                        "es-MX": "Emblema y placa de identificación de Unidad",
                        "fi-FI": "Yhtenäisyys-tunnus ja nimikyltti",
                        "fr-FR": "Emblème et plaque nominative Unité",
                        "hu-HU": "Egység embléma és névtábla",
                        "it-IT": "Emblema e targa identificativa Unità",
                        "ko-KR": "통합 휘장 및 명판",
                        "nb-NO": "Unity-emblem og -navneskilt",
                        "nl-NL": "Eenheid-embleem en -naamplaatje",
                        "pl-PL": "Emblemat i plakietka Jedność",
                        "pt-BR": "Emblema e Placa de Identificação Unidade",
                        "pt-PT": "Emblema e placa de identificação da Unidade",
                        "ru-RU": "Эмблема и табличка с именем «Единство»",
                        "sv-SE": "Sammanhållning-emblem och -namnskylt",
                        "tr-TR": "Birlik Amblemi ve İsim Plakası",
                        "zh-CN": "“团结 ”名牌和徽章",
                        "zh-TW": "「團結」名牌和徽章",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ûņïтў Еmъĺém &amp; Ňăмēρļαťэ !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ųňΐτў Ёmвℓěм &amp; Ñάмĕрĺåτé !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ũⁿΐŧў ∑mвŀзm &amp; Ňǻmĕρľąτё !!! !!! !"
                    }
                },
                "Body": {
                    "value": "Strength through diversity. \n\nA Spartan's job is to fight for all humanity and as a result, we're stronger together. \n\nLog into Halo Infinite this month to unlock the Unity nameplate and emblem for your Spartan, weapons, and vehicles.",
                    "status": "Test",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "V rozmanitosti je síla. \n\nÚkolem Sparťana je bojovat za celé lidstvo, proto jsme společně silnější. \n\nPřihlaste se tento měsíc do Halo Infinite a odemkněte jmenovku a emblém Jednota pro svého Sparťana, zbraně a vozidla.",
                        "da-DK": "Styrke gennem mangfoldighed. \n\nEn spartaners job er at kæmpe for hele menneskeheden, og derfor står vi stærkere sammen. \n\nLog ind i Halo Infinite i denne måned for at låse op for Unity-navneskiltet og -emblemet til din spartaner, våben og fartøjer.",
                        "de-DE": "Stärke durch Vielfalt.\n\nEin Spartan hat die Aufgabe, für die gesamte Menschheit zu kämpfen. So werden wir gemeinsam stärker.\n\nMelde dich diesen Monat in Halo Infinite an, um das Namensschild und Emblem „Einheit“ sowie Waffen und Fahrzeuge für deinen Spartan freizuschalten.",
                        "el-GR": "Δύναμη μέσα από τη διαφορετικότητα. \n\nΗ δουλειά ενός Spartan είναι να πολεμάει για όλη την ανθρωπότητα και ως αποτέλεσμα, είμαστε πιο δυνατοί μαζί. \n\nΣυνδεθείτε στο Halo Infinite αυτόν τον μήνα για να ξεκλειδώσετε την πινακίδα και το έμβλημα Unity για τον Spartan σας, τα όπλα και τα οχήματά σας.",
                        "es-ES": "En la diversidad reside nuestra fuerza. \n\nLa misión de los Spartan es luchar por toda la humanidad: unidos seremos más fuertes. \n\nInicia sesión en Halo Infinite este mes para desbloquear la placa de identificación y el emblema de Unity para tu Spartan, tus armas y tus vehículos.",
                        "es-MX": "Fuerza a través de la diversidad. \n\nEl trabajo de un Spartan es luchar por toda la humanidad, y como resultado, somos más fuertes juntos. \n\nInicia sesión en Halo Infinite este mes para desbloquear la placa de identificación y el emblema de Unidad para tu Spartan, armas y vehículos.",
                        "fi-FI": "Voimaa monimuotoisuuden kautta. \n\nSpartalaisen työnä on taistella koko ihmiskunnan puolesta, minkä ansiosta olemme vahvempia yhdessä. \n\nKirjaudu Halo Infiniteen tämän kuun aikana avataksesi Yhtenäisyys-tunnuksen ja -nimikyltin spartalaisellesi, aseillesi ja ajoneuvollesi.",
                        "fr-FR": "Unis dans la diversité. \n\nLa mission d'un Spartan consiste à se battre pour toute l'humanité ; c'est pourquoi il faut se montrer soudés. \n\nConnectez-vous sur Halo Infinite ce mois-ci pour déverrouiller la plaque nominative et l'emblème Unité pour votre Spartan, vos armes et vos véhicules.",
                        "hu-HU": "Erő a sokszínűségben. \n\nA Spartan feladata, hogy az egész emberiségért harcoljon, így együtt erősebbek lehetünk. \n\nJelentkezz be a Halo Infinite játékba a hónapban, és feloldhatod az Egység névtáblát, illetve emblémát Spartanod, fegyvereid és járműveid számára.",
                        "it-IT": "La diversità fa la forza. \n\nIl lavoro di uno Spartan è combattere per l'intera umanità... perché tutti insieme siamo più forti. \n\nAccedi a Halo Infinite questo mese per sbloccare la targa identificativa e l'emblema Unità per il tuo Spartan, le tue armi e i tuoi veicoli.",
                        "ko-KR": "다양성이 갖는 힘. \n\n스파르탄은 모든 인류를 위해 싸우므로, 우리는 뭉칠수록 강해집니다. \n\n이번 달에 Halo Infinite에 로그인해서 여러분의 스파르탄, 무기, 차량에 사용할 수 있는 통합 명판 및 휘장을 잠금 해제하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Styrke gjennom mangfold. \n\nEn spartaners jobb er å kjempe for hele menneskeheten, og som et resultat er vi sterkere sammen. \n\nLogg inn på Halo Infinite denne måneden for å låse opp Unity-navneskiltet og emblemet for spartaneren, våpnene og kjøretøyene dine.",
                        "nl-NL": "Kracht door diversiteit. \n\nEen Spartan strijdt altijd voor de gehele mensheid. Daarom staan we samen sterker. \n\nMeld je deze maand aan bij Halo Infinite en ontgrendel het Eenheid-naamplaatje en -embleem voor je Spartan, wapens en voertuigen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Siła dzięki różnorodności.\n\nSpratanie walczą w imieniu całej ludzkości, a razem jesteśmy silniejsi. \n\nZaloguj się do Halo Infinite w tym miesiącu, by odblokować tabliczkę plakietkę i emblemat Jedność, którymi ozdobisz spartanina, broń i pojazdy.",
                        "pt-BR": "A diversidade traz a força. \n\nO trabalho de um Spartan é lutar por toda a humanidade, portanto, somos mais fortes juntos. \n\nEntre no Halo Infinite este mês para desbloquear a placa de identificação e emblema Unidade para seu Spartan, armas e veículos.",
                        "pt-PT": "Força através da diversidade. \n\nO trabalho de um Spartan é lutar por toda a humanidade e, como resultado, somos mais fortes juntos. \n\nInicia sessão no Halo Infinite este mês para desbloqueares a placa de identificação e o emblema da Unidade para o teu Spartan, armas e veículos.",
                        "ru-RU": "Сила — в разнообразии.\n\nДело Спартанца — сражаться за всех представителей человечества, ведь вместе мы сильнее.\n\nВойдите в Halo до конца этого месяца, чтобы разблокировать табличку с именем и эмблему «Единство» для брони, оружия и техники своего Спартанца.",
                        "sv-SE": "Styrka genom mångfald.\n\nEn spartans jobb är att kämpa för hela mänskligheten och därför är vi starkare tillsammans.\n\nLogga in på Halo Infinite under den här månaden för att låsa upp namnskylten och emblemet Sammanhållning till din spartan, dina vapen och dina fordon.",
                        "tr-TR": "Çeşitlilikten gelen güç. \n\nBir Spartan'ın işi tüm insanlık için savaşmaktır, böylece birlikte daha güçlü oluruz. \n\nSpartan'ınız, silahlarınız ve araçlarınız için Birlik isim plakasının ve ambleminin kilidini açmak amacıyla bu ay Halo Infinite'e giriş yapın.",
                        "zh-CN": "多样性带来的力量。\n\n斯巴达战士的本职是为全人类而战，因此，团结将更强大。\n\n本月登录《光环：无限》以解锁您的斯巴达战士、武器和载具的“团结 ”名牌和徽章。",
                        "zh-TW": "多樣性就是實力。\n\n超級戰士的職責是為全人類而戰，因此，團結將使我們更強大。\n\n這個月登入《Halo Infinite》，即可為您的超級戰士、武器及載具解鎖「團結」名牌和徽章。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ŝţѓēηğţђ τнгǿúġĥ ďϊνєřšîţў.  !!! !!! !!\n\nΆ Ѕράŕţàń'ѕ ĵøъ îѕ τö ƒïģĥť ƒоř åŀļ ĥůмåлíтў αŋð аѕ ā ŗéšûļť, ẅё'яэ şťгøŋģêř ŧоģêτћêґ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nĹôģ ĭйťø Ηªŀǿ Ìйƒīήìţє ţħίѕ мόŋŧђ ŧó ūⁿĺσ¢к тĥє Ûŋîťÿ йàmêρľàτз àπđ ęмъļэm ƒбŗ ўòůŗ Şρдŗŧàй, ώęαρσⁿş, àñđ νзħįćłĕş. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Şтґéňğţн ţнŗούġћ đîνëřѕίŧÿ.  !!! !!! !!\n\nÄ Śρàґŧал'ŝ ĵóв ìŝ τθ ƒїġħτ ƒóя âŀĺ ћцмãŉīŧỳ ąиð άş ą ŕëşůłτ, ẃέ'řе šтřōπģèř ţōĝēŧĥēѓ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nĽőĝ їņţó Ήǻŀσ Їηƒĩйįťę тĥíş мбйτĥ ŧо ϋήļóćĸ ŧнè Űŉιτỳ πªméφĺǻţέ åπď émъŀėм ƒθř ÿоŭґ Śρàŗτªή, шёãроņś, åиđ νёћΐ¢ℓěş. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Šτѓĕņģтħ ťħřóűģħ δĭν℮ґşïτу.  !!! !!! !!\n\nΑ Şφäяţāŉ'ś ĵбь įś ţо ƒΐĝћť ƒòя αĺŀ ĥũмάňìτў àŋđ άś ά ѓèśμłŧ, ώё'ŕé şţřσлġеѓ ťοğěţнēґ.  !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nŁοĝ їиťò Нǻľǿ Ĭйƒïήïтë τĥìş мõйŧн ŧò µńŀóċк τĥè Ũиΐтỳ ňámεφℓâţė ăηδ êмьℓєm ƒόя ÿǿџŕ Şрàгтąй, ωёαφσŉŝ, ăňδ νéніċļěś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                },
                "ArticleImage": {
                    "Width": 1920,
                    "Height": 1080,
                    "Path": "news/Evergreen/Unity_1920x1080_MOTD.jpg"
                },
                "ArticleActions": [
                    {
                        "ActionTitle": {
                            "value": "Visit Xbox.com",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Navštivte Xbox.com",
                                "da-DK": "Besøg Xbox.com",
                                "de-DE": "Besuche Xbox.com",
                                "el-GR": "Επισκέψου το Xbox.com",
                                "es-ES": "Visita Xbox.com",
                                "es-MX": "Visita Xbox.com",
                                "fi-FI": "Mene sivulle Xbox.com",
                                "fr-FR": "Rendez-vous sur Xbox.com",
                                "hu-HU": "Keresd fel az Xbox.com oldalt",
                                "it-IT": "Visita Xbox.com",
                                "ja-JP": "Xbox.com にアクセスする",
                                "ko-KR": "Xbox.com 방문",
                                "nb-NO": "Gå til Xbox.com",
                                "nl-NL": "Ga naar Xbox.com",
                                "pl-PL": "Odwiedź Xbox.com",
                                "pt-BR": "Visite Xbox.com",
                                "pt-PT": "Visita Xbox.com",
                                "ru-RU": "Посетить Xbox.com",
                                "sv-SE": "Besök Xbox.com",
                                "tr-TR": "Xbox.com adresini ziyaret edin",
                                "zh-CN": "访问 Xbox.com",
                                "zh-TW": "前往 Xbox.com",
                                "qps-ploc": "Vìŝīт χъох.ĉòm !!! !!!",
                                "qps-ploca": "Vίšΐт Хвó×.соm !!! !!!",
                                "qps-plocm": "Vįşїт χвбх.ςòм !!! !!!"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionDescription": {
                            "value": "We'll bring you to Xbox.com to read more.",
                            "status": "Test",
                            "translations": {
                                "cs-CZ": "Zavedeme vás na Xbox.com, kde si budete moct přečíst více.",
                                "da-DK": "Vi fører dig hen til Xbox.com, hvor du kan læse mere.",
                                "de-DE": "Du wirst zu Xbox.com weitergeleitet, um mehr Details zu erfahren.",
                                "el-GR": "Θα σε μεταφέρουμε στο Xbox.com για να διαβάσεις περισσότερα.",
                                "es-ES": "Te llevaremos a Xbox.com para obtener más información.",
                                "es-MX": "Te llevaremos a Xbox.com para que obtengas más información.",
                                "fi-FI": "Ohjaamme sinut osoitteeseen Xbox.com, niin voit lukea lisää.",
                                "fr-FR": "Nous allons vous diriger vers Xbox.com pour de plus amples informations.",
                                "hu-HU": "Bővebb információkért az Xbox.com oldalra viszünk.",
                                "it-IT": "Ti trasferiremo su Xbox.com per proseguire la lettura.",
                                "ja-JP": "詳細については、Xbox.com をご確認ください。",
                                "ko-KR": "자세한 내용을 보실 수 있도록 Xbox.com로 이동합니다.",
                                "nb-NO": "Vi tar deg med til Xbox.com for å lese mer.",
                                "nl-NL": "We sturen je door naar Xbox.com, waar je meer kunt lezen.",
                                "pl-PL": "Przeniesiemy cię na stronę Xbox.com, gdzie znajdziesz więcej informacji.",
                                "pt-BR": "Vamos levar você ao Xbox.com para ler mais.",
                                "pt-PT": "Vamos levar-te ao Xbox.com para leres mais.",
                                "ru-RU": "Мы откроем для вас сайт Xbox.com, чтобы вы узнали подробности.",
                                "sv-SE": "Vi tar dig till Xbox.com så du kan läsa mer.",
                                "tr-TR": "Sizi daha fazla bilgi almanız için Xbox.com adresine aktaracağız.",
                                "zh-CN": "我们将带您前往 Xbox.com 阅读更多内容。",
                                "zh-TW": "我們將帶您前往 Xbox.com，閱讀更多資訊。",
                                "qps-ploc": "Ẅę'ľŀ ъřìπğ ŷóũ ťő Хьø×.čőм ŧő řедð мóґз. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-ploca": "Ẁе'ļĺ ьřĭńġ ўöµ ţо χвóх.ςσм ţσ ѓзâδ мθяè. !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                                "qps-plocm": "Ẃé'ŀł вŕĩйġ ýŏù ťò Хвόж.ĉóm тö ґéäđ môґё. !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                            }
                        },
                        "ActionUri": "https://news.xbox.com/en-us/2022/06/01/celebrate-pride-2022-with-team-xbox/"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
	</code>
</example>