<example>
	Here is an example response from the API, as snapshotted on 7/8/2022:
	<code>
    {
        "DateRange": {
            "status": "Ready",
            "value": "May 03, 2022 - November 08, 2022",
            "translations": {
                "cs-CZ": "3. května 2022 – 8. listopadu 2022",
                "da-DK": "3. maj 2022 - 8. november 2022",
                "de-DE": "03. Mai 2022 – 08. November 2022",
                "el-GR": "03 Μαΐου 2022 - 08 Νοεμβρίου 2022",
                "es-ES": "3 de mayo de 2022 - 8 de noviembre de 2022",
                "es-MX": "Del 3 de mayo al 8 de noviembre de 2022",
                "fi-FI": "3. toukokuuta 2022 - 8. marraskuuta 2022",
                "fr-FR": "3 mai 2022 - 8 novembre 2022",
                "hu-HU": "2022. május 3. – 2022. november 8.",
                "it-IT": "03 maggio 2022 - 08 novembre 2022",
                "ja-JP": "2022 年 5 月 3 日 ~ 2022 年 11 月 8 日",
                "ko-KR": "2022년 5월 3일 - 2022년 11월 8일",
                "nb-NO": "3. mai 2022 til 8. november 2022",
                "nl-NL": "03 mei 2022 - 08 november 2022",
                "pl-PL": "3 maja 2022 – 8 listopada 2022",
                "pt-BR": "De 03 de maio de 2022 a 08 de novembro de 2022",
                "pt-PT": "03 de maio de 2022 – 08 de novembro de 2022",
                "ru-RU": "3 мая 2022 г. — 8 ноября 2022 г.",
                "sv-SE": "3 maj 2022–8 november 2022",
                "tr-TR": "3 Mayıs 2022 - 8 Kasım 2022",
                "zh-CN": "2022 年 5 月 3 日 - 2022 年 11 月 8 日",
                "zh-TW": "2022 年 5 月 3 日 - 2022 年 11 月 8 日",
                "qps-ploc": "Μâŷ 03, 2022 - Ńóνэмьěř 08, 2022 !!! !!! !!! ",
                "qps-ploca": "Мąỳ 03, 2022 - Лöνèмьéг 08, 2022 !!! !!! !!! ",
                "qps-plocm": "Мăý 03, 2022 - Ńǿνεмъēґ 08, 2022 !!! !!! !!! "
            }
        },
        "Name": {
            "status": "Ready",
            "value": "Lone Wolves",
            "translations": {
                "cs-CZ": "Samotáři",
                "da-DK": "Ensomme ulve",
                "de-DE": "Einzelgänger",
                "el-GR": "Μοναχικοί Λύκοι",
                "es-ES": "Lobos solitarios",
                "es-MX": "Lobos solitarios",
                "fi-FI": "Yksinäiset sudet",
                "fr-FR": "Loups solitaires",
                "hu-HU": "Magányos farkasok",
                "it-IT": "Lupi solitari",
                "ja-JP": "ローン ウルフ",
                "ko-KR": "고독한 늑대",
                "nb-NO": "Ensomme ulver",
                "nl-NL": "Lone Wolves",
                "pl-PL": "Samotne wilki",
                "pt-BR": "Lobos Solitários",
                "pt-PT": "Lobos solitários",
                "ru-RU": "Волки-одиночки",
                "sv-SE": "Ensamvargar",
                "tr-TR": "Yalnız Kurtlar",
                "zh-CN": "孤狼",
                "zh-TW": "獨行俠",
                "qps-ploc": "Ľöñе Ẅбŀνеş !!!",
                "qps-ploca": "Ľǿпє Щòļνєş !!!",
                "qps-plocm": "Ŀöπé Ẅǿŀνëѕ !!!"
            }
        },
        "Logo": "progression/RewardTracks/Season_Switcher_S2_LW.png",
        "Number": 2,
        "Description": {
            "status": "Ready",
            "value": "A red carpet and unexpected guests.",
            "translations": {
                "cs-CZ": "Červený koberec a neočekávaní hosté",
                "da-DK": "En rød løber og uventede gæster.",
                "de-DE": "Ein roter Teppich und unerwartete Gäste.",
                "el-GR": "Ένα κόκκινο χαλί και απρόσμενοι επισκέπτες.",
                "es-ES": "Una alfombra roja e invitados inesperados.",
                "es-MX": "Una alfombra roja e invitados inesperados.",
                "fi-FI": "Punainen matto ja odottamattomia vieraita.",
                "fr-FR": "Un tapis rouge et des visiteurs inattendus.",
                "hu-HU": "Vörös szőnyeg és váratlan vendégek.",
                "it-IT": "Un tappeto rosso e ospiti inattesi.",
                "ja-JP": "レッド カーペットと予期せぬゲスト。",
                "ko-KR": "붉은 카펫과 예상치 못한 손님들.",
                "nb-NO": "En rød løper og uventede gjester.",
                "nl-NL": "Een rode loper en onverwachte gasten.",
                "pl-PL": "Czerwony dywan i niespodziewani goście.",
                "pt-BR": "Um tapete vermelho e convidados inesperados.",
                "pt-PT": "Um tapete vermelho e convidados inesperados.",
                "ru-RU": "Торжественный приём и незваные гости.",
                "sv-SE": "Röd matta och oväntade gäster.",
                "tr-TR": "Bir kırmızı halı ve beklenmedik misafirler.",
                "zh-CN": "红地毯和意外的客人。",
                "zh-TW": "隆重的接待與意外的客人。",
                "qps-ploc": "Ā ѓэð ćãѓρèτ αпð µπєжφе¢ť℮đ ġύēšтŝ. !!! !!! !!! !",
                "qps-ploca": "Ǻ ŕеδ çâґρзт àлđ ūņє×φ℮сŧέδ ģцёšτş. !!! !!! !!! !",
                "qps-plocm": "Δ řέδ ςāгρĕť дήď üňę×φεĉτέð ġűεŝţѕ. !!! !!! !!! !"
            }
        },
        "SummaryBackgroundPath": "progression/ScreenBackgrounds/Summary_Background.png",
        "ChallengesBackgroundPath": "progression/ScreenBackgrounds/challenges_background.png",
        "BattlePassLogoImage": "progression/ScreenBackgrounds/battlepass_logo.png",
        "SeasonLogoImage": "seasons/insignia_s2_lonewolves_512.png",
        "RitualLogoImage": "progression/ScreenBackgrounds/ritual_logo.png",
        "StorefrontBackgroundImage": "progression/ScreenBackgrounds/storefront_background.pn",
        "CardBackgroundImage": "progression/Switcher/Season_Switcher_S2_LW.png",
        "NarrativeBlurb": {
            "status": "Ready",
            "value": "Cortana’s dominion has ended, but the merciless forces of the Banished have rushed to fill the void, decimating all who stand in their way.\n\nSpartan Commander Agryna has enlisted a new generation of Spartans and is preparing them to face the Banished—and perhaps even more dangerous foes.\n\nBut a few scattered Spartans remain in the field. These Spartans are rugged and resourceful. Hunters in the dark. And they call themselves… Lone Wolves.",
            "translations": {
                "cs-CZ": "Nadvláda Cortany skončila, ale rychle ji nahradily nelítostné síly Vyhnanců, které ničí všechno, co jim stojí v cestě.\n\nSparťanská velitelka Agryna naverbovala novou generaci Sparťanů a připravuje ji na střet s Vyhnanci – a možná i ještě nebezpečnějšími nepřáteli.\n\nV terénu však zůstalo několik osamocených Sparťanů. Tito Sparťané jsou odolní a vynalézaví. Lovci v temnotě. A říkají si… Samotáři.",
                "da-DK": "Cortanas herredømme er slut, men de Forvistes nådesløse tropper er strømmet ind for at udfylde tomrummet og har nedslagtet alle, der stod i vejen for dem.\n\nSpartaner kommandøren Agryna har hvervet en ny generation spartanere og gør dem klar til at møde de Forviste—og måske endda endnu farligere fjender.\n\nMen nogle få, spredte spartanere er fortsat på slagmarken. Disse spartanere er hårdføre og snarrådige. Jægere i mørket. Og de kalder sig selv … ensomme ulve.",
                "de-DE": "Cortanas Herrschaft ist vorbei, aber die gnadenlosen Streitkräfte der Verbannten haben das Machtvakuum schnell gefüllt und haben keinerlei Skrupel, alles und jeden zu vernichten, der sich ihnen in den Weg stellt.\n\nSpartan-Commander Agryna hat eine neue Generation von Spartans angeworben und bereitet sie darauf vor, sich den Verbannten – und vielleicht noch gefährlicheren Gegnern – entgegenzustellen.\n\nAber ein paar verstreute Spartans bleiben auf dem Feld. Diese Spartans sind robust und einfallsreich. Diese Einzelgänger sind Jäger im Dunkeln, die die Verbannten das Fürchten lehren werden.",
                "el-GR": "Η κυριαρχία της Κορτάνα τελείωσε, αλλά οι ανελέητες δυνάμεις των Εξόριστων έσπευσαν να καλύψουν το κενό, αποδεκατίζοντας όσους βρίσκονταν στον δρόμο τους.\n\nH Διοικητής των Spartan Αγκρύνα στρατολόγησε μια νέα γενιά από Spartan και τους προετοιμάζει να αντιμετωπίσουν τους Εξόριστους και ίσως ακόμα πιο επικίνδυνους εχθρούς.\n\nΩστόσο μερικοί διάσπαρτοι Spartan παραμένουν στο πεδίο. Αυτοί οι Spartan είναι σκληρόπετσοι και πολυμήχανοι. Κυνηγοί στο σκοτάδι. Και αυτοαποκαλούνται... Μοναχικοί Λύκοι.",
                "es-ES": "El dominio de Cortana ha terminado, pero las fuerzas despiadadas de los desterrados se han apresurado a llenar el vacío, diezmando a todos los que se interponen en su camino.\n\nLa comandante Spartan Agryna ha reclutado a una nueva generación de Spartan y los está preparando para enfrentarse a los desterrados, y tal vez a enemigos aún más peligrosos.\n\nPero algunos Spartan dispersos permanecen sobre el terreno. Estos Spartan son fuertes e ingeniosos. Cazadores en la oscuridad. Y se llaman a sí mismos... lobos solitarios.",
                "es-MX": "El dominio de Cortana llegó a su fin, pero las despiadadas fuerzas de los Desterrados se apresuraron a llenar el vacío de poder y a acabar con todos los que se interponen en su camino.\n\nLa comandante Spartan Agryna reclutó a una nueva generación de Spartans y los está preparando para enfrentar a los Desterrados, y tal vez a enemigos aún más peligrosos.\n\nPero algunos Spartans permanecen dispersos en el campo de batalla. Estos Spartans son fuertes, resistentes e ingeniosos. Cazadores en la oscuridad. Y se hacen llamar... los Lobos solitarios.",
                "fi-FI": "Cortanan ote galaksista on irronnut, mutta Banishedin armottomat joukot ovat rynnänneet täyttämään tyhjiön tuhoten kaikki tielleen tulevat..\n\nSpartalaiskomentaja Agryna on värvännyt uuden spartalaissukupolven ja valmistautuu lähettämään taistelijat kohtaamaan Banishedin—ja kenties vieläkin vaarallisempia vihollisia..\n\nKentällä on kuitenkin yhä muutamia spartalaisia siellä täällä. Nämä spartalaiset ovat kovanahkaisia ja ovelia. Metsästäjiä pimeydessä. He kutsuvat itseään… Yksinäisiksi susiksi.",
                "fr-FR": "La domination de Cortana sur la galaxie a cessé, mais les impitoyables troupes parias se sont empressées de prendre la relève, décimant tout sur leur passage.\n\nLe commandant spartan Agryna a recruté une nouvelle génération de Spartans, et les prépare à affronter les Parias et toutes les autres menaces potentielles.\n\nMais il reste encore quelques Spartans sur le terrain. Déterminés, méthodiques, ces traqueurs tapis dans l'ombre se sont autoproclamés... les Loups solitaires.",
                "hu-HU": "Cortana uralma véget ért, de a Száműzöttek kíméletlen erői nem haboztak betölteni a hatalmi űrt, megtizedelve mindenkit, aki az útjukba áll.\n\nAgryna parancsnok a Spartanok új generációját állította csatasorba, felkészítve őket az összecsapásra a Száműzöttekkel – és talán még veszélyesebb ellenségekkel.\n\nNéhány magányos Spartan azonban a harcmezőn maradt. Ezek a Spartanok kemények és találékonyak. Vadászok a sötétben. Magányos Farkasoknak hívják magukat.",
                "it-IT": "Il dominio di Cortana è terminato, ma le forze spietate degli Esiliati si sono precipitate a riempire quel vuoto, decimando chiunque le ostacolasse.\n\nLa comandante Spartan Agryna ha arruolato una nuova generazione di Spartan e la sta preparando ad affrontare gli Esiliati... e forse nemici ancora più pericolosi.\n\nMa sul campo restano alcuni Spartan isolati, combattenti temprati e pieni di risorse. Cacciatori nell'oscurità. E si definiscono... Lupi solitari.",
                "ja-JP": "コルタナによる支配は終わりを告げたが、それによって生じた力の空白につけ入ろうと、バニッシュトは立ちはだかる者すべてを容赦なく殺戮している。\n\nスパルタン コマンダー アグリーナは、新世代のスパルタンを選抜し、バニッシュトやさらに危険な敵に立ち向かう準備を進めている。\n\nしかし、わずかだが今も戦場で戦い続けるスパルタンたちもいる。無骨だが機知に富んだ闇の中の狩人たち。彼らは自らを「ローン ウルフ」と呼んでいた...",
                "ko-KR": "코타나의 은하계 지배는 끝났지만, 배니시드의 무자비한 군대가 그 공백을 채우기 위해 뛰어들었으며 자신을 막는 모든 자들을 제거하고 있습니다.\n\n스파르탄 아그리나 중령은 새 세대의 스파르탄들을 모집했으며 그들이 배니시드를 상대하도록 준비시키고 있습니다. 어쩌면 더 강한 적을 상대해야 할지도 모릅니다.\n\n하지만 전장에는 흩어진 스파르탄 몇 명이 남아 있습니다. 이 스파르탄들은 유능하며 강인한, 어둠 속의 사냥꾼들입니다. 이들은 스스로를 '고독한 늑대'라고 부릅니다.",
                "nb-NO": "Cortanas galaktiske herredømme er over, men de nådeløse kreftene til de forviste har fylt tomrommet, og eliminerer alle som står i veien for dem.\n\nSpartanerkommandant Agryna har vervet en ny generasjon spartanere og forbereder dem på å møte de forviste og kanskje enda farligere fiender.\n\nMen noen få spredte spartanere forblir i felten. Disse spartanerne er robuste og ressurssterke. Jegere i mørket. Og de kaller seg ... de ensomme ulvene.",
                "nl-NL": "De heerschappij van Cortana is beëindigd, maar de meedogenloze legers van de Banished hebben het machtsvacuüm opgevuld en vernietigen iedereen en alles wat in hun weg staat.\n\nSpartan Commander Agryna heeft een nieuwe generatie Spartans verzameld en bereid ze voor om het op te nemen tegen de Banished, en misschien nóg gevaarlijkere vijanden.\n\nEnkele Spartans zijn achtergebleven op de strijdvelden. Deze Spartans zijn krachtig en vindingrijk. Het zijn jagers in het duister. Ze noemen zichzelf de Lone Wolves.",
                "pl-PL": "Panowanie Cortany dobiegło końca, ale bezlitośni Wygnańcy postanowili wypełnić próżnię i ruszyli do ataku, dziesiątkując wszystkich, którzy stanęli im na drodze.\n\nSpartańska komandor Agryna zwerbowała nowe pokolenie spartan i przygotowuje ich do walki z Wygnańcami – a być może także z jeszcze niebezpieczniejszymi przeciwnikami.\n\nJednakże niewielka grupa rozproszonych spartan kontynuuje walkę. To twardzi i zaradni żołnierze, łowcy czający się w ciemnościach, którzy sami siebie nazywają samotnymi wilkami.",
                "pt-BR": "O domínio de Cortana chegou ao fim, mas as forças impiedosas dos Banidos correram para preencher o vazio deixado por ela, dizimando todos que entram em seu caminho.\n\nA Comandante Spartan Agryna alistou uma nova geração de Spartans, que estão treinando para enfrentar os Banidos, e talvez inimigos ainda mais perigosos.\n\nMas alguns Spartans permanecem em campo. São caçadores no escuro. Experientes e engenhosos. E eles se chamam... Lobos Solitários.",
                "pt-PT": "O domínio da Cortana terminou, mas as forças impiedosas dos Banished apressaram-se a preencher o vazio, dizimando todos os que se meterem no seu caminho.\n\nA Comandante Agryna Spartan recrutou uma nova geração de Spartans e está a prepará-los para enfrentar os Banished e, talvez, até inimigos mais perigosos.\n\nMas alguns Spartans dispersos permanecem no campo. Estes Spartans são robustos e engenhosos. Caçadores no escuro. E chamam a si mesmos… Lobos solitários.",
                "ru-RU": "Власти Кортаны пришёл конец, но пустоту спешат заполнить безжалостные орды Изгнанников, уничтожающие всё на своём пути.\n\nКомандир Спартанцев Агрина собрала Спартанцев нового поколения, чтобы подготовить их к бою с Изгнанниками, а может, и более опасным врагом.\n\nНо некоторые Спартанцы по-прежнему вынуждены сражаться вдали от остальных. Это находчивые, закалённые в боях бойцы. Охотники во тьме. Они называют себя… волками-одиночками.",
                "sv-SE": "Cortanas herravälde är över, men de bannlystas skoningslösa styrkor har varit snabba att fylla tomrummet och krossat alla som stått i vägen.\n\nSpartanbefälhavaren Agryna har rekryterat en ny generation spartaner och gör dem redo att kämpa mot de bannlysta – och eventuellt ännu farligare fiender.\n\nDet finns några spartaner kvar därute. De är härdade och påhittiga. Jägare i mörkret. De kallar sig själva... ensamvargar.",
                "tr-TR": "Cortana'nın hâkimiyeti sona erdi ancak acımasız Sürgün kuvvetleri bir an önce boşluğu doldurmaya çalıştılar ve bu süreçte yollarına çıkan herkesi yok ettiler\n\nSpartan Komutan Agryna, yeni nesil Spartanları orduya kattı ve onları Sürgünler ve belki de daha tehlikeli düşmanlarla yüzleşmeye hazırlıyor.\n\nFakat sahada hâlâ birkaç Spartan var. Bu Spartanlar dayanıklı ve becerikliler. Karanlıkta avlanmayı severler. Ve Yalnız Kurtlar olarak biliniyorlar.",
                "zh-CN": "科塔娜的统治已经结束，但流放者的无情大军却四处烧杀掳掠，毁灭所有阻挡他们前进的人。\n\n斯巴达战士指挥官阿格里纳招募了新一代的斯巴达战士，准备正面抗击流放者，以及更为强大的潜在敌人。\n\n但仍有一些流落各地的斯巴达战士还在前线。他们坚忍不拔、足智多谋，他们是黑暗中的猎人，他们称自己为... 孤狼。",
                "zh-TW": "Cortana 的統治已經結束，但流放者的無情大軍卻四處燒殺擄掠，毀滅所有阻擋他們前進的人。\n\n超級戰士指揮官 Agryna  招募了新一代的超級戰士，準備正面迎擊流放者，以及更為強大的潛在敵人。\n\n但仍有一些流落各地的超級戰士還在前線。他們堅忍不拔、足智多謀，他們是黑暗中的獵人，他們稱自己為... 獨行俠。",
                "qps-ploc": "Сòŕťαňá’š ĝáľäċτīς ďοmĭņíσл ћάš ęŋđĕδ, ьųτ тнě m℮ѓĉîĺεşś ƒóґĉέş οƒ τħэ Ъàňϊšн℮đ ђªνέ ѓџŝнэð тο ƒîŀľ ťħê νõΐδ, δěĉїmàτįńğ дŀĺ щнô şťàńđ іŉ ŧнęīř ẁåý. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nŞрâŕţªй Çømмãпđέѓ Λģŕўπá ħáś ейŀϊѕŧ℮ð á ηёẅ ğěйęřάŧΐοη ǿƒ Šρāґτǻⁿѕ ªñď ΐş φѓёрàŗìŉġ ťħэm ţø ƒâċë ťћз ßаⁿĭşħêδ—āлð рэŗћâρŝ єνëй mσяε δάŉğëґθūŝ ƒőеѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nЬϋт а ƒ℮ш śçàтţ℮яеđ Śрăřтäпś ŕэmдίŉ ΐň тнэ ƒīēĺδ. Ţнёѕ℮ Ŝρâŗτãйš ǻřę яϋģĝěď āπð řëŝőŭŗсеƒμľ. Ηΰлτεŗѕ їή тђê đăřк. Ăŋď τђĕγ ċáĺł τнěmśєŀνёş… Ĺőпё Ẁθļνéѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                "qps-ploca": "Ćσŕťãŉά’ѕ ġǻłªςťîĉ ðόмĭņĭǿñ ћãŝ зŋðєð, ъůţ ŧнэ мέřċįŀєşś ƒõřčеŝ θƒ τћé Ъдηїѕнзđ ħāνέ řûšĥέð тõ ƒîĺℓ τђė νσіδ, ďєĉĩмªтϊиġ àļł ẅћó şτâпđ іη тн℮ίŗ ẃàỳ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nŚρǻŕτåŉ Ćóмmдήðэя Дĝгупå нâş ēηℓΐşτзδ д йєŵ ģ℮ńеѓáτîǿй θƒ Şρáŕťåńš āńđ ΐš φґєρªѓΐⁿğ ţĥëm τö ƒªċê τнě Ьąŋιşн℮đ—ãπđ рėяђǻрş зνèń mоŕе ďáήģĕřőϋš ƒοėś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nВūт ά ƒέщ şсαťτεґêď Śρàѓτáņś řèmáίń ϊй ŧнę ƒî℮ļď. Ŧħέŝé Śрąяťάńş άřĕ ґύğģëď άлð ŗėśõũřćėƒúľ. Ηũñţēґѕ īŉ ţће ðáŗĸ. Ăήð ţнėŷ сαŀľ ţђęmѕεłνėѕ… Ļŏήε Щøℓνеš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                "qps-plocm": "€ŏґŧдñă’ŝ ġаļдćťīć ðбмįηϊòŋ ђдš èηđēđ, ьϋτ ţĥé mëŕςīĺěѕѕ ƒόгĉеś σƒ ţнє Ъªñįѕĥεđ ħăνê ŕùѕћěđ ťθ ƒïļľ ťћé νőΐδ, đёćīmãŧîⁿğ дļļ ẅнσ ŝтåлď іη ŧн℮ĭŗ ẅдý. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nŠράŕŧǻņ Čōмmªήďэř Ǻġŕỳņà ђāѕ ëŋℓĩšťēď å ñзш ģêñεřàţіой òƒ Šрāгťäŋş ãпð іѕ φѓеφάřĭйġ τнêm ťò ƒǻςê тнę Бάήìśĥĕð—ąñð рèѓнąрś ένĕп мοŗэ δдńğèřöύѕ ƒόёš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!\n\nВϋŧ д ƒèω ŝĉàţтèřéð Ѕраřţáπş ŗзmąïŋ ιŋ ťħê ƒіĕľđ. Тћėšέ Şφăŗτдиš αгē яџġġєđ ªńď ŗеѕõůřćěƒџľ. Ηűñτ℮ґş ίŋ τĥė ďαŗќ. Ǻńδ ťћєγ ĉάļľ τħемş℮ļν℮ś… ₤ǿйë Щόłνēŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
            }
        },
        "BattlePassSeasonUpsellBackgroundImage": "progression/ScreenBackgrounds/season_upsell_background.png",
        "ProgressionBackgroundImage": "progression/ScreenBackgrounds/progression_background.png"
    }
	</code>
</example>