<example>
	Here is an example response from the API, as snapshotted on 7/20/2022:
	<code>
    {
        "ErrorList": [
            {
                "gameStartError": "InternalError",
                "gameStartErrorId": 0,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Unexpected error with the Halo Infinite services. Please try again later.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Došlo k neočekávané chybě služeb Halo Infinite. Zkuste to prosím znovu později.",
                        "da-DK": "Der opstod en uventet fejl med Halo Infinite-tjenesterne. Prøv igen senere.",
                        "de-DE": "Unerwarteter Fehler in Verbindung mit den Diensten von Halo Infinite. Bitte versuche es später erneut.",
                        "el-GR": "Μη αναμενόμενο σφάλμα με τις υπηρεσίες Halo Infinite. Προσπάθησε ξανά αργότερα.",
                        "es-ES": "Se ha producido un error inesperado con los servicios de Halo Infinite. Inténtalo de nuevo más tarde.",
                        "es-MX": "Error inesperado con los servicios de Halo Infinite. Intenta más tarde.",
                        "fi-FI": "Odottamaton virhe Halo Infinite -palveluissa. Yritä myöhemmin uudelleen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Une erreur inattendue s'est produite sur les services de Halo Infinite. Veuillez réessayer ultérieurement.",
                        "hu-HU": "Váratlan probléma merült fel a Halo Infinite szerverekkel. Próbálkozz újra.",
                        "it-IT": "Si è verificato un errore imprevisto con i servizi di Halo Infinite. Riprova più tardi.",
                        "ja-JP": "Halo Infinite のサービスで予期しないエラーが発生しました。後ほどあらためてお試しください。",
                        "ko-KR": "Halo Infinite 서비스에 예기치 않은 오류가 발생했습니다. 나중에 다시 시도하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Uventet feil i Halo Infinites tjenester. Prøv igjen senere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Onverwachte fout met de Halo Infinite-services. Probeer het later opnieuw.",
                        "pl-PL": "Nieoczekiwany błąd usług Halo Infinite. Spróbuj ponownie później.",
                        "pt-BR": "Erro inesperado com os serviços de Halo Infinite. Tente novamente mais tarde.",
                        "pt-PT": "Erro inesperado com os serviços do Halo Infinite. Tenta de novo mais tarde.",
                        "ru-RU": "Неожиданная ошибка в работе сервисов Halo Infinite. Попробуйте позже.",
                        "sv-SE": "Oväntat fel i Halo Infinites tjänster. Försök igen senare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Halo Infinite hizmetlerinde beklenmeyen hata. Lütfen daha sonra tekrar deneyin.",
                        "zh-CN": "Halo Infinite 服务发生意外错误。请稍后再试。",
                        "zh-TW": "《Halo Infinite》服務發生預期外的錯誤。請稍後再試。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ùⁿежρēčτзđ еŗřõř щїŧħ ťђё Ήдľø Ίлƒĩⁿīţз ŝéŗνĭ¢ęş. Рℓэάśε τŕγ äĝαĭⁿ łǻŧèѓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Úŉé×φêςťеđ єягóя ώϊτћ ţħē Нàľǿ Îńƒїŋïт℮ śέґνïčёś. Ρļęāśє ťгγ āĝаίŉ ℓдτėř. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ūñéжрέĉтєđ эŗѓǿř ŵιťђ ţђэ Ήäľő Їηƒíñîŧé šзŗνīćèŝ. Ρℓёåšέ τѓý áģąіη ŀǻťęѓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "IncompatibleClientBuilds",
                "gameStartErrorId": 1,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Fireteam members have different versions of Halo Infinite and cannot play together.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Členové palebného týmu mají různé verze hry Halo Infinite a nemohou hrát společně.",
                        "da-DK": "Kampgruppemedlemmer har forskellige versioner af Halo Infinite og kan ikke spille sammen.",
                        "de-DE": "Die Feuerteammitglieder haben verschiedene Versionen von Halo Infinite und können nicht zusammen spielen.",
                        "el-GR": "Τα μέλη της Ομάδα Μάχης έχουν διαφορετικές εκδόσεις του Halo Infinite και δεν μπορούν να παίξουν μαζί.",
                        "es-ES": "Los miembros del equipo de asalto tienen versiones distintas de Halo Infinite, por lo que no pueden jugar juntos.",
                        "es-MX": "Los miembros del equipo tienen diferentes versiones de Halo Infinite y no pueden jugar juntos.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimin jäsenillä on eri versiot Halo Infinitestä, eivätkä he voi pelata yhdessä.",
                        "fr-FR": "Les membres de l'équipe ont des versions différentes de Halo Infinite et ne peuvent pas jouer ensemble.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod tagjai a Halo Infinite különböző verzióival rendelkeznek, és nem tudnak együtt játszani.",
                        "it-IT": "I membri della squadra d'assalto hanno versioni diverse di Halo Infinite e non possono giocare insieme.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームのメンバーの Halo Infinite バージョンが異なるため、一緒にプレイできません。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버들의 Halo Infinite 버전이 서로 달라 함께 플레이할 수 없습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Gruppemedlemmer har forskjellige versjoner av Halo Infinite og kan ikke spille sammen.",
                        "nl-NL": "Vuurteamleden hebben verschillende versies van Halo Infinite en kunnen niet samen spelen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Członkowie drużyny mają różne wersje gry Halo Infinite i nie mogą grać razem.",
                        "pt-BR": "Os membros da esquadra têm versões diferentes de Halo Infinite e não podem jogar juntos.",
                        "pt-PT": "Os membros da Fireteam têm versões do Halo Infinite diferentes e não podem jogar juntos.",
                        "ru-RU": "Участники отряда используют разные версии Halo Infinite и не могут играть вместе.",
                        "sv-SE": "Gruppmedlemmar har olika versioner av Halo Infinite och kan inte spela tillsammans.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timi üyeleri Halo Infinite'in farklı sürümlerine sahipler ve birlikte oynayamazlar.",
                        "zh-CN": "火力小队成员的 Halo Infinite 版本不同，无法一起游戏。",
                        "zh-TW": "火力小組成員的《Halo Infinite》版本不同，無法一起玩遊戲。",
                        "qps-ploc": "₣ïŗęťéâm мεмвéґŝ ĥãν℮ đīƒƒèяèŋť νėŕšϊσŉş őƒ Ĥâľσ Ĭήƒĭŋїτė ªήδ ċāиñõţ φļду ťοĝέŧђёѓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "₣īŕзтèâм m℮mв℮яš ĥдνэ đĭƒƒέŕéňť νėѓŝΐøπş бƒ Ĥαℓŏ Ìйƒϊπĭτз ǻήð ¢áπņőт рļаỳ τøĝêŧĥēŗ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "₣ίřзτéαм мёмъęгś нāν℮ δϊƒƒěřëńτ νėґśìθиŝ θƒ Ĥаľõ İиƒϊŉíŧ℮ αńδ çãллōŧ ρľáў ŧòġєŧћ℮ѓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "MaximumMultiplayerSplitScreenExceeded",
                "gameStartErrorId": 2,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Too many players are signed into one of the devices on this fireteam.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "K jednomu ze zařízení tohoto palebného týmu je přihlášeno příliš mnoho hráčů.",
                        "da-DK": "Alt for mange spillere i denne kampgruppe er logget ind på en af enhederne.",
                        "de-DE": "Auf einem der Geräte dieses Feuerteams sind zu viele Spieler angemeldet.",
                        "el-GR": "Πάρα πολλοί παίκτες είναι συνδεδεμένοι σε μία από τις συσκευές σε αυτήν την ομάδα μάχης.",
                        "es-ES": "Demasiados jugadores han iniciado sesión en uno de los dispositivos de este equipo de asalto.",
                        "es-MX": "Demasiados jugadores iniciaron sesión en uno de los dispositivos de este equipo.",
                        "fi-FI": "Yhdelle tulitiimin laitteelle on kirjautuneena liian monta pelaajaa.",
                        "fr-FR": "Un trop grand nombre de joueurs est connecté sur l'un des dispositifs de cette équipe.",
                        "hu-HU": "Túl sok játékos jelentkezett be az egyik eszközről ebbe a tűzcsoportba.",
                        "it-IT": "Troppi giocatori hanno effettuato l'accesso a uno dei dispositivi di questa squadra d'assalto.",
                        "ja-JP": "このファイヤーチームのデバイスの 1 つにサインインしているプレイヤーが多すぎます。",
                        "ko-KR": "이 화력조의 장치들 중 하나에 너무 많은 플레이어가 로그인했습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "For mange spillere er logget på en av gruppens enheter.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er zijn te veel spelers aangemeld bij een van de apparaten in dit vuurteam.",
                        "pl-PL": "Na jednym z urządzeń tej drużyny jest zalogowanych zbyt wielu graczy.",
                        "pt-BR": "Muitos jogadores estão conectados a um dos dispositivos nesta esquadra.",
                        "pt-PT": "Demasiados jogadores estão inscritos num dos dispositivos desta fireteam.",
                        "ru-RU": "Слишком много игроков вошли в этот отряд через одно и то же устройство.",
                        "sv-SE": "För många spelare är inloggade på en av gruppens enheter.",
                        "tr-TR": "Bu atış timindeki cihazlardan birinde çok fazla oyuncu oturum açtı.",
                        "zh-CN": "这个火力小队中有太多玩家登录至其中一部装置。",
                        "zh-TW": "這個火力小組中有太多玩家登入至其中一部裝置。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ţοŏ mãήỳ рłªÿėяś ǻґ℮ ѕϊĝη℮ð íⁿţø ôήэ ŏƒ ţћэ δęνïĉēś òŉ тђίѕ ƒĭѓετęâm. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ŧοσ мäлў рĺãўеřŝ åřę ѕΐğпėð іñтō õήę õƒ ťђĕ ďзνįċěş θⁿ ţћіѕ ƒįѓēτêąm. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Τōŏ măŋў φłаγëѓŝ àге šΐğŋêđ їⁿτо őⁿє οƒ ţћз ďėνī¢ëѕ ǿŋ ŧĥιś ƒίřëтĕαм. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "LobbyTooLarge",
                "gameStartErrorId": 3,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Your fireteam is too large for the selected activity.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Váš palebný tým je pro vybranou aktivitu příliš velký.",
                        "da-DK": "Din kampgruppe er for stor til den valgte aktivitet.",
                        "de-DE": "Dein Feuerteam ist zu groß für die gewählte Aktivität.",
                        "el-GR": "Η ομάδα μάχης σου είναι πολύ μεγάλη για την επιλεγμένη δραστηριότητα.",
                        "es-ES": "Tu equipo de asalto es demasiado grande para la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "es-MX": "Tu equipo es demasiado grande para la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimisi on liian suuri valittuun aktiviteettiin.",
                        "fr-FR": "Votre équipe est trop nombreuse pour l'activité sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod túl nagy a választott aktivitáshoz.",
                        "it-IT": "La tua squadra d'assalto è troppo numerosa per l'attività selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "選択しているアクティブティに対して、ファイヤーチームを構成するプレイヤーが多すぎます。",
                        "ko-KR": "선택한 활동을 하기에는 화력조 멤버가 너무 많습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Gruppen din er for stor for den valgte aktiviteten.",
                        "nl-NL": "Je vuurteam is te groot voor de geselecteerde activiteit.",
                        "pl-PL": "Twoja drużyna jest zbyt duża, aby było możliwe wykonanie wybranej aktywności.",
                        "pt-BR": "Sua esquadra é muito grande para a atividade selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "A tua fireteam é demasiado grande para a atividade selecionada.",
                        "ru-RU": "Ваш отряд слишком большой для выбранного занятия.",
                        "sv-SE": "Din grupp är för stor för den valda aktiviteten.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timiniz seçili etkinlik için çok büyük.",
                        "zh-CN": "您火力小队的玩家太多，无法进行所选取的活动。",
                        "zh-TW": "您火力小組的玩家太多，無法進行所選取的活動。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ỳøûѓ ƒíґεтέάм ΐŝ тǿŏ ℓáґġз ƒθя ťħê šëℓεçţêď ǻçтîνïŧÿ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Υōŭř ƒīґ℮ţëдm іş ŧøó ĺâřġё ƒоř ţħэ ŝеļēčťèδ âċţĭνīţỳ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "¥óŭѓ ƒïѓèτεâm ίš τθø ľάѓģé ƒôŗ ŧнĕ ѕěℓěćŧĕď аĉţΐνĭтў. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "LobbyTooSmall",
                "gameStartErrorId": 4,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Your fireteam is too small for the selected activity.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Váš palebný tým je pro vybranou aktivitu příliš malý.",
                        "da-DK": "Din kampgruppe er for lille til den valgte aktivitet.",
                        "de-DE": "Dein Feuerteam ist zu klein für die gewählte Aktivität.",
                        "el-GR": "Η ομάδα μάχης σου είναι πολύ μικρή για την επιλεγμένη δραστηριότητα.",
                        "es-ES": "Tu equipo de asalto es demasiado pequeño para la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "es-MX": "Tu equipo es demasiado pequeño para la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimisi on liian pieni valittuun aktiviteettiin.",
                        "fr-FR": "Votre équipe est trop petite pour l'activité sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod túl kicsi a választott aktivitáshoz.",
                        "it-IT": "La tua squadra non è abbastanza numerosa per l'attività selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "選択したアクティビティに対して、ファイヤーチームが小さすぎます。",
                        "ko-KR": "선택한 활동을 하기에는 화력조 멤버가 너무 적습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Gruppen din er for liten for den valgte aktiviteten.",
                        "nl-NL": "Je vuurteam is te klein voor de geselecteerde activiteit.",
                        "pl-PL": "Twoja drużyna jest zbyt mała, aby było możliwe wykonanie wybranej aktywności.",
                        "pt-BR": "Sua esquadra é muito pequena para a atividade selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "A tua fireteam é demasiado pequena para a atividade selecionada.",
                        "ru-RU": "Ваш отряд слишком мал для выбранного занятия.",
                        "sv-SE": "Din grupp är för liten för den valda aktiviteten.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timiniz seçili etkinlik için çok küçük.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队人数对于所选活动而言太少。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組人數對於所選活動而言太少。",
                        "qps-ploc": "¥ôűґ ƒìяēтēам їŝ ţоǿ şмάłļ ƒоŗ ŧĥĕ śэŀĕĉťєď ǻĉŧіνίτу. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ŷôŭѓ ƒϊґêτêαм їş тôò ѕмäĺł ƒŏѓ ŧĥέ šёļêčτěð ăсţįνíŧγ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "¥øυѓ ƒíгєŧёдм íŝ ŧòо ŝmàłł ƒóѓ ťĥ℮ ŝєļēçťêδ αςťįνíţγ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "NoMultiplayerPrivilege",
                "gameStartErrorId": 5,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "At least one player in your fireteam is not currently permitted to play Xbox Live multiplayer games.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden hráč z vašeho palebného týmu nemá v současné době povoleno hrát ve službě Xbox Live hry pro více hráčů.",
                        "da-DK": "Mindst ét medlem af din kampgruppe har i øjeblikket ikke tilladelse til at spille multiplayerspil på Xbox Live.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Spieler deines Feuerteams darf derzeit keine Multiplayer-Spieler über Xbox Live spielen.",
                        "el-GR": "Τουλάχιστον ένας παίκτης της ομάδας μάχης σου δεν επιτρέπεται προς το παρόν να παίζει παιχνίδια για πολλούς παίκτες στο xbox Live.",
                        "es-ES": "Al menos un jugador de tu equipo de asalto no puede jugar ahora mismo partidas multijugador en Xbox Live.",
                        "es-MX": "Al menos uno de los miembros de tu equipo no puede jugar en partidas de multijugador en Xbox Live.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yhdellä tulitiimisi pelaajista ei ole tällä hetkellä lupaa pelata Xbox Live -moninpelejä.",
                        "fr-FR": "Au moins un joueur de votre équipe n'est pas autorisé à participer à des parties multijoueur Xbox Live.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoport legalább egyik tagja jelenleg nem tud játszani az Xbox Live többszemélyes játékokkal.",
                        "it-IT": "Almeno un giocatore della tua squadra d'assalto al momento non può giocare partite multiplayer Xbox Live.",
                        "ja-JP": "少なくともファイヤーチーム内の 1 人のプレイヤーが Xbox Live マルチプレイヤーのプレイを許可されていません。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조의 플레이어 중 적어도 한 명에게 Xbox Live 멀티 플레이어 게임을 할 권한이 없습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Minst én spiller i gruppen har ikke tillatelse til å spille flerspillerspill via Xbox Live.",
                        "nl-NL": "Ten minste één speler in je vuurteam mag momenteel geen Xbox Live-multiplayergames spelen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden gracz z twojej drużyny nie może obecnie grać w gry wieloosobowe w ramach usługi Xbox Live.",
                        "pt-BR": "Pelo menos um jogador em sua esquadra não tem permissão para jogar o modo multijogador no Xbox Live no momento.",
                        "pt-PT": "Pelo menos um jogador na tua fireteam não está atualmente autorizado a jogar jogos multijogador no Xbox Live.",
                        "ru-RU": "Как минимум у одного из игроков в вашем отряде нет разрешения играть в сетевом режиме через Xbox Live.",
                        "sv-SE": "Minst en spelare i gruppen har inte tillstånd att spela flerspelarspel via Xbox Live.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizdeki en az bir oyuncunun şu anda Xbox Live çok oyunculu oyunlarını oynamasına izin verilmiyor.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中，至少有 1 位玩家目前没有进行 Xbox Live 多人游戏的权限。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中，至少有 1 位玩家目前沒有進行 Xbox Live 多人遊戲的權限。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ăţ ŀέâśť оñĕ φłάÿèґ ĩπ ỳбūя ƒĭř℮тεáм ïş ⁿŏŧ ċµŗŕëňŧℓў φεřmĩţтèð τθ φľâў χвσх Ļíνę mцľτîφŀâуěŕ ğãмеŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Áť ŀéáşť őŋė рľªγêř їⁿ ўőúř ƒίґéŧěаm ïѕ йøт ćúґгēήτĺγ ρëŗмïťţěď ťô рℓаŷ Χъόх Ŀíνĕ мΰłтïρļªŷēг ģăмèŝ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ат łěāşт θŋе рℓäγēя ĩń ўøця ƒіřėтėªm ΐѕ ŋòť ĉũгяеņťĺỳ рэŗmĭţťěδ ţǿ ρłаў Χьőж Ľινэ mûℓţįφℓǻγēř ĝаmεš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "UserBanned",
                "gameStartErrorId": 6,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "At least one player in your fireteam is banned from playing Halo Infinite.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden hráč z vašeho palebného týmu má zakázáno hrát hru Halo Infinite.",
                        "da-DK": "Mindst én spiller i din kampgruppe har forbud mod at spille Halo Infinite.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Spieler deines Feuerteams wurde für Halo Infinite gesperrt.",
                        "el-GR": "Τουλάχιστον ένας παίκτης της ομάδας μάχης σου απαγορεύεται να παίζει Halo Infinite.",
                        "es-ES": "Al menos un jugador de tu equipo de asalto está excluido de Halo Infinite.",
                        "es-MX": "Al menos uno de los miembros de tu equipo está expulsado de Halo Infinite.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yhdellä tulitiimisi pelaajista on pelikielto Halo Infiniteen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Au moins un joueur de votre équipe est exclu des serveurs Halo Infinite.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod legalább egy tagja ki van tiltva a Halo Infinte-ből.",
                        "it-IT": "Almeno un giocatore nella tua squadra d'assalto è stato bannato da Halo Infinite.",
                        "ja-JP": "少なくともファイヤーチーム内の 1 人のプレイヤーが Halo Infinite のプレイ禁止処分を受けています。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조의 플레이어 중 적어도 한 명이 Halo Infinite 플레이가 차단되었습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Minst én spiller i gruppen er utestengt fra Halo Infinite.",
                        "nl-NL": "Ten minste één speler in je vuurteam is verbannen van Halo Infinite.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden gracz z twojej drużyny ma bana na grę w Halo Infinite.",
                        "pt-BR": "Pelo menos um jogador em sua esquadra está banido de jogar Halo Infinite.",
                        "pt-PT": "Pelo menos um jogador na tua fireteam está banido de jogar Halo Infinite.",
                        "ru-RU": "Как минимум один игрок из вашего отряда заблокирован в игре Halo Infinite.",
                        "sv-SE": "Minst en spelare i gruppen är avstängd från Halo Infinite.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizdeki en az bir oyuncunun Halo Infinite oynaması yasaklandı.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中，至少有 1 位玩家遭到禁止进行 Halo Infinite 游戏的惩罚。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中，至少有 1 位玩家遭到禁止進行 Halo 5 Infinite 的懲罰。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Àŧ ļēąşť õŉě рℓàуέѓ ïл ўōця ƒϊґęтέãм īş ьåηŉзđ ƒґŏm рŀāўíñģ Ήàĺõ Ĩπƒϊπίţε. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Αţ łėαśţ øлĕ рľάÿěř ιŋ γбŭя ƒíŕēτęáм іś ъåñηĕđ ƒѓőm ρℓăỳĩⁿģ Ήãłŏ Ìŋƒîńĩŧė. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Дť ľзǻŝт οπê φĺáγеŕ ĭñ ỳôųř ƒīгěťëăм ϊš ъąñⁿëď ƒŕøm рľαỳįиġ Ħăℓø Įпƒįйìť℮. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "NoQoSServerMatch",
                "gameStartErrorId": 10,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Could not find a data center suitable for all members of your fireteam. This is often due to network connectivity or latency issues.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Nepodařilo se najít datové centrum vhodné pro všechny členy vašeho palebného týmu. Často je to způsobeno problémy se síťovým připojením nebo latencí.",
                        "da-DK": "Der blev ikke fundet et datacenter, der passer til alle medlemmer af din kampgruppe. Dette skyldes ofte problemer med netværksforbindelsen eller ventetiden.",
                        "de-DE": "Es konnte kein passendes Datenzentrum für alle Mitglieder deines Feuerteams gefunden werden. Das ist oft aufgrund von Problemen mit der Netzwerkverbindung oder der Latenz der Fall.",
                        "el-GR": "Δεν ήταν δυνατή η εύρεση ενός κέντρου δεδομένων κατάλληλου για όλα τα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης σου. Αυτό συχνά οφείλεται σε ζητήματα σύνδεσης δικτύου ή καθυστέρησης.",
                        "es-ES": "No se ha encontrado un centro de datos adecuado para todos los miembros de tu equipo de asalto. Esto suele deberse a problemas de conectividad de la red o de latencia.",
                        "es-MX": "No se pudo encontrar un centro de datos adecuado para todos los miembros de tu equipo. Esto a menudo se debe a problemas de conectividad de la red o de latencia.",
                        "fi-FI": "Kaikille tulitiimin jäsenille sopivaa datakeskusta ei löytynyt. Syynä on usein verkkoyhteyteen tai -viiveeseen liittyvä ongelma.",
                        "fr-FR": "Impossible de trouver un centre de données adapté à tous les membres de votre équipe. Cela est souvent dû à des problèmes de connexion ou de latence.",
                        "hu-HU": "Nem található adatközpont, amely megfelel a tűzcsoportod minden tagjának. Ez általában hálózati kapcsolódási vagy latenciaproblémák miatt van.",
                        "it-IT": "Impossibile trovare un data center adatto a tutti i membri della tua squadra d'assalto. Disguidi simili spesso sono dovuti a problemi di connettività di rete o di latenza.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームのメンバー全員に適したデータセンターが見つかりません。多くの場合、ネットワーク接続やレイテンシーの問題が原因です。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조의 모든 멤버에 적합한 데이터 센터를 찾지 못했습니다. 네트워크 연결 또는 지연 문제로 자주 발생하는 문제입니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Kunne ikke finne et datasenter som passer for alle gruppemedlemmene. Dette skyldes vanligvis problemer med nettverkstilkobling eller latens.",
                        "nl-NL": "Kon geen datacenter vinden dat geschikt is voor alle leden van je vuurteam. Dit is vaak te wijten aan een slechte netwerkverbinding of netwerkvertraging.",
                        "pl-PL": "Nie udało się znaleźć centrum danych odpowiedniego dla wszystkich członków twojej drużyny. Zwykle dzieje się tak z powodu problemów z łącznością sieciową lub opóźnieniami.",
                        "pt-BR": "Não foi possível encontrar um centro de dados adequado para todos os membros da sua esquadra. Isso geralmente ocorre devido a problemas de conectividade ou latência de rede.",
                        "pt-PT": "Não foi possível encontrar um centro de dados adequado a todos os membros da tua fireteam. Isto deve-se frequentemente a problemas de conectividade de rede ou de latência.",
                        "ru-RU": "Не удалось найти дата-центр, подходящий для всех участников вашего отряда. Это часто происходит из-за проблем с сетевым соединением или задержкой сигнала.",
                        "sv-SE": "Kunde inte hitta ett datacenter som passar alla gruppmedlemmar. Det här beror oftast på problem med nätverksanslutning eller latens.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin tüm üyeleri için uygun bir veri merkezi bulunamadı. Bunun nedeni genellikle ağ bağlantısı veya gecikme süresi sorunlarıdır.",
                        "zh-CN": "找不到适合您火力小队所有成员的数据中心。这通常是由于网路连接或延迟问题所致。",
                        "zh-TW": "找不到適合您火力小組所有成員的資料中心。這通常是由於網路連線或延遲問題所致。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Čоúļδ ňôť ƒĩŋđ à ðατà ćêŋťéѓ şύĩŧǻьŀέ ƒøř àŀℓ mēмъзяś ǿƒ ỳόũŕ ƒïяéтέáм. Ŧнĩş їѕ оƒťєй ďυэ ţŏ ŋėŧщогκ čōппėċťĩνĩťў όř ľдтēŋčу ιšŝüêš. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ćόΰℓδ ņòŧ ƒįлđ ā đāťă ćěитеѓ şυĭŧãъŀ℮ ƒоŕ ąľŀ měмвèгѕ όƒ уσυř ƒîгēťěám. Ţнíѕ їŝ όƒтęй ðύê тσ ŉзтẅǿŗκ сοпñеĉŧινïŧÿ òґ ľáŧзņċγ ίѕşůĕś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Сŏúļđ иőŧ ƒίπδ å đаτά сзñťёř şûīŧάвļз ƒσř åľŀ мëмьëґš ôƒ ỳоŭя ƒΐязŧèăм. Ţħĭѕ ïѕ σƒťěп đûē ŧõ ηêţẅøґκ сøŋŋэςτĭνϊтγ бŗ ŀдтēйçŷ ĭšśûėś. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "NoQoSServerSuccessfulPingsInClientData",
                "gameStartErrorId": 11,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Error retrieving data center connection quality information. Please try again later.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Při načítání informací o kvalitě připojení k datovému centru došlo k chybě. Zkuste to prosím znovu později.",
                        "da-DK": "Der opstod en fejl under hentning af oplysninger om datacenterforbindelseskvalitet. Prøv igen senere.",
                        "de-DE": "Fehler beim Abrufen der Informationen zur Verbindungsqualität des Rechenzentrums. Versuchen Sie es später erneut.",
                        "el-GR": "Σφάλμα κατά την ανάκτηση πληροφοριών ποιότητας σύνδεσης κέντρου δεδομένων. Προσπάθησε ξανά αργότερα.",
                        "es-ES": "Error al recuperar información sobre la calidad de la conexión del centro de datos. Inténtalo más tarde.",
                        "es-MX": "Error al recuperar información sobre la calidad de la conexión del centro de datos. Inténtalo más tarde.",
                        "fi-FI": "Virhe noudettaessa datakeskuksen yhteyden laatutietoja. Ole hyvä ja yritä myöhemmin uudelleen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Une erreur est survenue lors de la récupération des informations relatives à la qualité de la connexion au centre de données. Veuillez réessayer ultérieurement.",
                        "hu-HU": "Hiba történt a kapcsolati minőséginformációk lekérése közben az adatközpontból. Kérjük, próbáld újra később.",
                        "it-IT": "Si è verificato un errore durante il recupero delle informazioni sulla qualità della connessione al centro dati. Riprova più tardi.",
                        "ja-JP": "データ センター接続クオリティ情報の取得でエラーが発生しました。 後でもう一度お試しください。",
                        "ko-KR": "데이터 연결의 질에 대한 정보를 받아오는 중에 오류가 발생했습니다. 나중에 다시 시도하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Det oppstod en feil under henting av informasjon om tilkobling til datasenter. Prøv igjen senere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Fout bij het ophalen van informatie over de verbindingskwaliteit van het datacenter. Probeer het later opnieuw.",
                        "pl-PL": "Błąd pobierania informacji o jakości połączenia z centrum danych. Spróbuj ponownie później.",
                        "pt-BR": "Erro ao recuperar as informações da qualidade de conexão da central de dados. Tente novamente mais tarde.",
                        "pt-PT": "Erro ao recuperar as informações de qualidade da ligação do centro de dados. Tenta de novo mais tarde.",
                        "ru-RU": "Ошибка получения информации о качестве связи с дата-центром. Попробуйте позже.",
                        "sv-SE": "Fel uppstod vid hämtning av information om anslutning till datacenter. Försök igen senare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Veri merkezi bağlantı kalitesi bilgileri alınırken hata oluştu. Lütfen daha sonra tekrar deneyin.",
                        "zh-CN": "获取数据中心连接质量信息时发生错误，请稍后再试。",
                        "zh-TW": "讀取資料中心連線品質資訊時發生錯誤，請稍後再試。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ėŕѓог řéţгіéνίиġ đãţа ćєитěѓ ςσήήê¢тιόŋ qцąŀĩŧỳ įŋƒοřmăŧíóŉ. Рłёãśè ţřў ąġάιй ℓаţ℮ŕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Зяŕòя ŕëţяïеνìńģ ðáţα ċëŉŧέř ĉσŋήēćŧϊǿη qùãĺîтγ ϊñƒőгмăτīôņ. Ρℓęªšě ţřŷ ãġáїл ŀáţєг. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ĕřгσř řзтяϊêνіπĝ ðåţă čėлтėґ çòйñėçтϊσñ qϋªŀíτÿ ιηƒōямåτîоŉ. Ρĺėàšę тґŷ άģàįⁿ łáŧēŕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "NoMatchingGsiSetInThunderhead",
                "gameStartErrorId": 12,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "No dedicated servers are available for your version of Halo Infinite at this time.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Pro vaši verzi hry Halo Infinite nejsou v tuto chvíli k dispozici žádné vyhrazené servery.",
                        "da-DK": "Der er ingen dedikerede servere tilgængelige til din version af Halo Infinite på nuværende tidspunkt.",
                        "de-DE": "Derzeit sind keine dedizierten Server für deine Version von Halo Infinite verfügbar.",
                        "el-GR": "Δεν υπάρχουν διαθέσιμοι διακομιστές για αυτήν την έκδοση του Halo Infinite προς το παρόν.",
                        "es-ES": "En este momento no hay servidores específicos disponibles para tu versión de Halo Infinite.",
                        "es-MX": "En este momento no hay servidores dedicados disponibles para tu versión de Halo Infinite.",
                        "fi-FI": "Halo Infinite -versiollesi ei ole tällä hetkellä saatavilla dedikoituja palvelimia.",
                        "fr-FR": "Aucun serveur dédié n'est disponible actuellement pour votre version de Halo Infinite.",
                        "hu-HU": "Jelenleg nincs elérhető szerver a Halo Infinite ezen verziója számára.",
                        "it-IT": "Nessun server dedicato risulta al momento disponibile per la versione in uso di Halo Infinite.",
                        "ja-JP": "現在、このバージョンの Halo Infinite に対応している専用サーバーで利用できるものはありません。",
                        "ko-KR": "지금은 Halo Infinite의 이 버전에 맞는 전용 서버가 없습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Det er ingen dedikerte servere tilgjengelig for din versjon av Halo Infinite akkurat nå.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er zijn momenteel geen dedicated servers beschikbaar voor jouw versie van Halo Infinite.",
                        "pl-PL": "W tej chwili nie są dostępne żadne dedykowane serwery dla twojej wersji gry Halo Infinite.",
                        "pt-BR": "Não há servidores dedicados disponíveis para a sua versão de Halo Infinite no momento.",
                        "pt-PT": "Não existem servidores dedicados disponíveis para a tua versão do Halo Infinite neste momento.",
                        "ru-RU": "Для вашей версии Halo Infinite выделенные серверы в настоящий момент недоступны.",
                        "sv-SE": "Det finns inga dedikerade servrar tillgängliga för din version av Halo Infinite just nu.",
                        "tr-TR": "Halo Infinite sürümünüz için şu anda uygun özel sunucu bulunmuyor.",
                        "zh-CN": "目前没有您的 Halo Infinite 版本可用的专属服务器。",
                        "zh-TW": "目前沒有您的 Halo Infinite 版本可用的專用伺服器。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ňó ďėðїćάťεð śèřνεŗѕ дгě άνąīℓāъļé ƒбř ỳőúѓ νêѓşįθπ øƒ Ηåļǿ Їńƒΐŋįţ℮ дť ťħĭŝ ŧïmĕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ňō ðέðíςăŧěð ś℮ŕνёŕѕ äяė áνáіľáъļэ ƒόŕ ỳǿūŗ νéřšïοй θƒ Ħªłǿ Íňƒіηíťэ ǻт тĥïş тĭmè. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Пó δёđї¢άτ℮ð śεґνéґѕ āгε áνąïłąьľė ƒôѓ уθμŗ νêřśίõň σƒ Нąłό Įņƒΐńιťē āт ťћĩŝ τΐmе. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "NoRulesDefined",
                "gameStartErrorId": 14,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "There was an error starting your activity. Please try again later.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Při zahajování vaší aktivity došlo k chybě. Zkuste to prosím znovu později.",
                        "da-DK": "Der opstod en fejl under start af aktiviteten. Prøv igen senere.",
                        "de-DE": "Beim Starten Ihrer Aktivität ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Bitte versuchen Sie es später erneut.",
                        "el-GR": "Παρουσιάστηκε σφάλμα κατά την εκκίνηση της δραστηριότητάς σου. Προσπάθησε ξανά αργότερα.",
                        "es-ES": "Se ha producido un error al iniciar tu actividad. Vuelve a intentarlo más tarde.",
                        "es-MX": "Se produjo un error al iniciar tu actividad. Vuelve a intentarlo más tarde.",
                        "fi-FI": "Aktiviteetin aloittamisessa tapahtui virhe. Yritä myöhemmin uudelleen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Une erreur est survenue au démarrage de votre activité. Veuillez réessayer plus tard.",
                        "hu-HU": "Hiba történt az aktivitás megkezdése során. Kérjük, próbálkozz később.",
                        "it-IT": "Si è verificato un errore durante l'avvio dell'attività. Riprova più tardi.",
                        "ja-JP": "エラーが発生してアクティビティを開始できませんでした。 後でもう一度お試しください。",
                        "ko-KR": "활동을 시작하는 중에 오류가 발생했습니다. 나중에 다시 시도하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Det oppstod en feil under aktivitetsstart. Prøv igjen senere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er is een fout opgetreden bij het starten van je activiteit. Probeer het later opnieuw.",
                        "pl-PL": "Wystąpił błąd przy rozpoczęciu twojego działania. Spróbuj ponownie później.",
                        "pt-BR": "Ocorreu um erro ao iniciar sua atividade. Tente novamente mais tarde.",
                        "pt-PT": "Ocorreu um erro ao iniciar a tua atividade. Tenta de novo mais tarde.",
                        "ru-RU": "При запуске действия произошла ошибка. Попробуйте позже.",
                        "sv-SE": "Ett fel uppstod vid aktivitetsstart. Försök igen senare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Etkinliğiniz başlatılırken bir hata oluştu. Lütfen daha sonra tekrar deneyin.",
                        "zh-CN": "启动您的活动时发生错误，请稍后再试。",
                        "zh-TW": "系統在啟動您的活動時發生錯誤，請稍後再試。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ŧћèяε ŵãś άπ èřŕõѓ šťăŗŧįŋĝ ўôùř ăĉτïνĭтγ. Рℓέαśэ τгý äĝάîй ľãŧέг. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ťħèŗě ωαş āň ęгŗøѓ ѕŧǻřτīņġ ŷόūѓ дĉţîνїту. Рļзάśĕ ţѓỳ äģдīή ℓдτęŕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Тħєѓэ ŵаş ăņ зřгоґ šтдŗтιήģ ŷθùя ąсτîνĩŧў. Рļèдѕè ŧгу âĝãїπ ĺªтеґ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "HighQosResultsDetected",
                "gameStartErrorId": 15,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "One or more members of your fireteam has high latency to the dedicated server.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden člen vašeho palebného týmu hasičů má při komunikaci s vyhrazeným serverem vysokou latenci.",
                        "da-DK": "Et eller flere medlemmer af din kampgruppe har høj latenstid til den dedikerede server.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Mitglied deines Feuerteams kann nur mit sehr hoher Latenz mit dem dedizierten Server kommunizieren.",
                        "el-GR": "Ένα ή περισσότερα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης σου έχουν υψηλή χρονοκαθυστέρηση στον ειδικό διακομιστή.",
                        "es-ES": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo de asalto tienen una latencia alta en el servidor dedicado.",
                        "es-MX": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo tienen una latencia alta con el servidor dedicado.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yhdellä tulitiimisi jäsenistä on korkea viive dedikoituun palvelimeen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Un ou plusieurs membres de votre équipe ont une latence de connexion élevée aux serveurs dédiés.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod legalább egyik tagjának magas a latenciája a dedikált szerverrel.",
                        "it-IT": "Uno o più membri della tua squadra d'assalto presentano una latenza elevata sul server dedicato.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームのメンバーの中に、専用サーバーのレイテンシーが高いプレイヤーがいます。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버 중 한 명 이상이 전용 서버에 대해 지연이 심합니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Ett eller flere gruppemedlemmer har høy latens til den dedikerte serveren.",
                        "nl-NL": "Een of meer leden van je vuurteam hebben veel vertraging met de dedicated server.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden członek twojej drużyny ma duże opóźnienia połączenia z dedykowanym serwerem.",
                        "pt-BR": "Um ou mais membros da sua esquadra estão com alta latência para o servidor dedicado.",
                        "pt-PT": "Um ou mais membros da tua fireteam têm latência elevada para o servidor dedicado.",
                        "ru-RU": "У одного или нескольких участников вашего отряда слишком большое время задержки при обмене информацией с выделенным сервером.",
                        "sv-SE": "En eller fler gruppmedlemmar har hög latens till den dedikerade servern.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin bir veya daha fazla üyesinin belirlenmiş sunucu bağlantısında yüksek gecikme süresi bulunmaktadır.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中有一名或多名成员对专属服务器有严重的延迟问题。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中至少有 1 位成員對專用伺服器有嚴重的延遲問題。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Оπє ǿѓ мøŗέ м℮mьёŗѕ бƒ ỳσџŗ ƒìгёťèàм нàš ћіģћ ĺаţèņ¢ÿ ŧǿ ŧђе ðěďїčáτęδ š℮яνéř. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Φήė όř mогě мêmьзŕѕ őƒ ŷοùř ƒίґěţęáм ђãŝ ĥíğн ŀâţéπçỳ ťŏ ŧħě ďēďįçаτèδ śėŗνεг. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ôпέ ǿґ мσгє мèmъέřś ǿƒ ÿőúř ƒíř℮ťęàm ĥдѕ ĥιġћ ĺдŧęŋċý ťő тĥê ďёðĭčдťзď ѕєѓνеѓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "CmsContentNotFound",
                "gameStartErrorId": 16,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "There was an error retrieving content from the Halo Infinite CMS system. Please try again later.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Při načítání obsahu ze systému Halo Infinite CMS došlo k chybě. Zkuste to prosím znovu později.",
                        "da-DK": "Der opstod en fejl under hentning af indhold fra Halo Infinite CMS-systemet. Prøv igen senere.",
                        "de-DE": "Beim Laden von Inhalten aus dem CMS-System von Halo Infinite ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Bitte versuche es später erneut.",
                        "el-GR": "Παρουσιάστηκε σφάλμα κατά την ανάκτηση περιεχομένου από το σύστημα Halo Infinite CMS. Προσπάθησε ξανά αργότερα.",
                        "es-ES": "Se ha producido un error al recuperar contenido del sistema de gestión de contenidos de Halo Infinite. Vuelve a intentarlo más tarde.",
                        "es-MX": "Hubo un error al recuperar contenido de los servicios de gestión de contenidos de Halo Infinite. Por favor intenta más tarde.",
                        "fi-FI": "Virhe noudettaessa sisältöä Halo Infiniten CMS-järjestelmästä. Yritä myöhemmin uudelleen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Une erreur est survenue lors de la récupération du contenu auprès du système CMS de Halo Infinite. Veuillez réessayer ultérieurement.",
                        "hu-HU": "Hiba történt a Halo Infinite CMS rendszerről történő tartalom lekérése során. Kérjük, próbáld később.",
                        "it-IT": "Si è verificato un errore durante il recupero dei contenuti del sistema CMS di Halo Infinite. Riprova più tardi.",
                        "ja-JP": "Halo Infinite CMS システムからコンテンツを取得する際にエラーが発生しました。後ほどあらためてお試しください。",
                        "ko-KR": "Halo Infinite CMS 시스템에서 콘텐츠를 받아오는 중에 오류가 발생했습니다. 나중에 다시 시도하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Det oppstod en feil under nedlasting av innhold fra Halo Infinites innholdshåndteringssystem. Prøv igjen senere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er is een fout opgetreden bij het ophalen van content uit het CMS-systeem van Halo Infinite. Probeer het later opnieuw.",
                        "pl-PL": "Podczas pobierania zawartości z systemu CMS Halo Infinite wystąpił błąd. Spróbuj ponownie później.",
                        "pt-BR": "Ocorreu um erro ao recuperar o conteúdo do sistema CMS de Halo Infinite. Tente novamente mais tarde.",
                        "pt-PT": "Ocorreu um erro ao recuperar conteúdos do sistema CMS do Halo Infinite. Tenta de novo mais tarde.",
                        "ru-RU": "Ошибка получения контента от системы управления контентом Halo Infinite. Попробуйте позже.",
                        "sv-SE": "Ett fel uppstod när innehåll hämtades från Halo Infinites innehållshanteringssystem. Försök igen senare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Halo Infinite CMS sisteminden içerik alınırken bir hata oluştu. Lütfen daha sonra tekrar deneyin.",
                        "zh-CN": "从 Halo Infinite CMS 系统获取内容时发生错误，请稍后再试。",
                        "zh-TW": "從 Halo Infinite CMS 系統擷取內容時發生錯誤，請稍後再試。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ŧћěřз ŵąš άŉ έѓŗǿґ яέτŕϊéνìñģ ćòńŧёητ ƒґŏм τħé Нâĺö Ϊπƒϊñíте ĆМŜ ŝŷѕŧèм. Рĺęàŝє ŧѓŷ дģäιⁿ ŀªτēѓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Тĥέŕé шāŝ аŋ éŗřόř ŕēťѓîęνįŉģ ćôήţέňŧ ƒябm тнē Нąℓσ Іŋƒíлĩŧė €ΜЅ ѕγşτêм. Ρĺēãśě ţѓỳ ăĝάΐņ ŀåτеř. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ŧнзŗé ώàś αή ēяŗοŕ гèтгîενĭиġ сöηţéηť ƒѓőм τħз Нãℓб Іņƒĭηìťé ČМŞ šўšтέm. Ρŀзαšè ťѓý áĝǻìñ ℓάтεř. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "CmsServiceUnavailable",
                "gameStartErrorId": 17,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "There was an error contacting the Halo Infinite CMS system. Please try again later.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Při kontaktování systému Halo Infinite CMS došlo k chybě. Zkuste to prosím znovu později.",
                        "da-DK": "Der opstod en fejl under kontakt med Halo Infinite CMS-systemet. Prøv igen senere.",
                        "de-DE": "Beim Kontaktieren des CMS-Systems von Halo Infinite ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Bitte versuche es später erneut.",
                        "el-GR": "Παρουσιάστηκε σφάλμα κατά την επικοινωνία με το σύστημα Halo Infinite CMS. Προσπάθησε ξανά αργότερα.",
                        "es-ES": "Se ha producido un error al contactar con el sistema de gestión de contenidos de Halo Infinite. Vuelve a intentarlo más tarde.",
                        "es-MX": "Hubo un error al contactar con el sistema de gestión de contenidos de Halo Infinite. Por favor intenta más tarde.",
                        "fi-FI": "Virhe muodostettaessa yhteyttä Halo Infiniten CMS-järjestelmään. Yritä myöhemmin uudelleen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Une erreur est survenue lors de la connexion au système CMS de Halo Infinite. Veuillez réessayer ultérieurement.",
                        "hu-HU": "Hiba történt a Halo Infinite CMS rendszerrel való kapcsolatfelvétel közben. Kérjük, próbáld később.",
                        "it-IT": "Si è verificato un errore durante la comunicazione con il sistema CMS di Halo Infinite. Riprova più tardi.",
                        "ja-JP": "Halo Infinite CMS システムにアクセスする際にエラーが発生しました。後ほどあらためてお試しください。",
                        "ko-KR": "Halo Infinite CMS 시스템에 연결하는 중에 오류가 발생했습니다. 나중에 다시 시도하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Halo Infinites innholdshåndteringssystem kunne ikke kontaktes. Prøv igjen senere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er is een fout opgetreden bij het verbinden met het CMS-systeem van Halo Infinite. Probeer het later opnieuw.",
                        "pl-PL": "Podczas łączenia się z systemem CMS Halo Infinite wystąpił błąd. Spróbuj ponownie później.",
                        "pt-BR": "Ocorreu um erro ao contatar o sistema CMS de Halo Infinite. Tente novamente mais tarde.",
                        "pt-PT": "Ocorreu um erro ao contactar o sistema CMS do Halo Infinite. Tenta de novo mais tarde.",
                        "ru-RU": "Ошибка установки связи с системой управления контентом Halo Infinite. Попробуйте позже.",
                        "sv-SE": "Halo Infinites innehållshanteringssystem kunde inte kontaktas. Försök igen senare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Halo Infinite CMS sistemiyle bağlantı kurulurken bir hata oluştu. Lütfen daha sonra tekrar deneyin.",
                        "zh-CN": "连接 Halo Infinite CMS 系统时发生错误，请稍后再试。",
                        "zh-TW": "連絡 Halo Infinite CMS 系統時發生錯誤，請稍後再試。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ťĥēґё ŵâş дŉ эřŗоř čбñţα¢ťīпğ ŧђė Ĥαľö Įήƒĭиĩτе ÇΜŠ ŝỳşτêм. Рℓεªѕ℮ тгу áğãіπ ĺåτёґ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ŧħěřэ ẁáš άⁿ ëгяǿѓ ćŏлŧдċţíñĝ ţнé Нªĺσ Īⁿƒîήįŧε ÇМŞ ŝγşţèm. Ρℓєåśε ŧŗγ ãģáíŋ łàŧęŗ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Τћëґê ẃªŝ дή ëŗřőґ ¢ôηţåςţίπģ ţђз Ήąŀö Ίŉƒίŋιŧё ĈΜŚ şγѕтєm. Ρŀëâśė ŧŕỳ аĝаíŋ ľдтęя. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "UgcContentNotFound",
                "gameStartErrorId": 18,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "There was an error retrieving content from the Halo Infinite UGC service. Please try again later.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Při načítání obsahu ze služby Halo Infinite UGC došlo k chybě. Zkuste to prosím znovu později.",
                        "da-DK": "Der opstod en fejl under hentning af indhold fra Halo Infinite UGC-tjenesten. Prøv igen senere.",
                        "de-DE": "Beim Laden von Inhalten aus dem UGC-Dienst von Halo Infinite ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Bitte versuche es später erneut.",
                        "el-GR": "Παρουσιάστηκε σφάλμα κατά την ανάκτηση περιεχομένου από την υπηρεσία Halo Infinite UGC. Προσπάθησε ξανά αργότερα.",
                        "es-ES": "Se ha producido un error al recuperar contenido del servicio de contenidos generados por el usuario de Halo Infinite. Vuelve a intentarlo más tarde.",
                        "es-MX": "Hubo un error al recuperar contenido de los servicios de gestión de contenidos generados por usuarios de Halo Infinite. Por favor intenta más tarde.",
                        "fi-FI": "Virhe noudettaessa sisältöä Halo Infiniten UGC-palvelusta. Yritä myöhemmin uudelleen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Une erreur est survenue lors de la récupération du contenu auprès des services UGC de Halo Infinite. Veuillez réessayer ultérieurement.",
                        "hu-HU": "Hiba történt a Halo Infinite UGC szolgáltatásról történő tartalom lekérése során. Kérjük, próbáld később.",
                        "it-IT": "Si è verificato un errore durante il recupero dei contenuti del servizio UGC di Halo Infinite. Riprova più tardi.",
                        "ja-JP": "Halo Infinite UGC サービスからコンテンツを取得する際にエラーが発生しました。後ほどあらためてお試しください。",
                        "ko-KR": "Halo Infinite UGC 서비스에서 콘텐츠를 받아오는 중에 오류가 발생했습니다. 나중에 다시 시도하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Det oppstod en feil under nedlasting av innhold fra Halo Infinites tjeneste for brukeropprettet innhold. Prøv igjen senere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er is een fout opgetreden bij het ophalen van content uit de UGC-service van Halo Infinite. Probeer het later opnieuw.",
                        "pl-PL": "Podczas pobierania zawartości z usługi UGC Halo Infinite wystąpił błąd. Spróbuj ponownie później.",
                        "pt-BR": "Ocorreu um erro ao recuperar o conteúdo do serviço de UGC de Halo Infinite. Tente novamente mais tarde.",
                        "pt-PT": "Ocorreu um erro ao recuperar conteúdos do serviço UGC do Halo Infinite. Tenta de novo mais tarde.",
                        "ru-RU": "Ошибка получения контента от сервиса пользовательского контента Halo Infinite. Попробуйте позже.",
                        "sv-SE": "Ett fel uppstod när innehåll hämtades från Halo Infinites tjänst för användarskapat innehåll. Försök igen senare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Halo Infinite UGC hizmetinden içerik alınırken bir hata oluştu. Lütfen daha sonra tekrar deneyin.",
                        "zh-CN": "从 Halo Infinite UGC 系统获取内容时发生错误，请稍后再试。",
                        "zh-TW": "從 Halo Infinite UGC 系統擷取內容時發生錯誤，請稍後再試。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ţĥеяε ẃāś àņ зггθř ѓêτгїэνίņğ čōπтêŋţ ƒґöм ŧħє Ĥăłσ Іņƒîńітē ЏĞС šęяνìςę. Ρĺэαšè ţѓу ªģαϊп ļаτèř. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ŧђēřё ẃдŝ άŋ ęяѓοя ŗęŧґĩěνιлģ ςōήтęήť ƒŕǿm ťħε Ήąℓο Ìпƒΐпіτė ÙĢС ŝзřνĭсę. Рŀĕäśĕ ŧгý аĝаĩņ ŀáτзŕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Τнéřë щăѕ ăи éřгбř яэτřĭёνιпĝ çöŋţέŉτ ƒŕοm ţħε Ħåŀб Íńƒϊŉΐтě ŪĠĆ śêгνí¢ē. Рŀèâşэ тřу âġáìи ĺăŧеѓ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "UgcServiceUnavailable",
                "gameStartErrorId": 19,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "There was an error contacting the Halo Infinite UGC service. Please try again later.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Při kontaktování služby Halo Infinite UGC došlo k chybě. Zkuste to prosím znovu později.",
                        "da-DK": "Der opstod en fejl under forsøg på at kontakte Halo Infinite UGC-tjenesten. Prøv igen senere.",
                        "de-DE": "Beim Kontaktieren des UGC-Dienstes von Halo Infinite ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Bitte versuche es später erneut.",
                        "el-GR": "Παρουσιάστηκε σφάλμα κατά την επικοινωνία με την υπηρεσία Halo Infinite UGC. Προσπάθησε ξανά αργότερα.",
                        "es-ES": "Se ha producido un error al contactar con el servicio de contenidos generados por el usuario de Halo Infinite. Vuelve a intentarlo más tarde.",
                        "es-MX": "Hubo un error al contactar con el sistema de gestión de contenidos generados por usuarios de Halo Infinite. Por favor intenta más tarde.",
                        "fi-FI": "Virhe muodostettaessa yhteyttä Halo Infiniten UGC-palveluun. Yritä myöhemmin uudelleen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Une erreur est survenue lors de la connexion au service UGC de Halo Infinite. Veuillez réessayer ultérieurement.",
                        "hu-HU": "Hiba történt a Halo Infinite UGC szolgáltatással való kapcsolatfelvétel közben. Kérjük, próbáld később.",
                        "it-IT": "Si è verificato un errore durante la comunicazione con il servizio UGC di Halo Infinite. Riprova più tardi.",
                        "ja-JP": "Halo Infinite UGC サービスにアクセスする際にエラーが発生しました。後ほどあらためてお試しください。",
                        "ko-KR": "Halo Infinite UGC 서비스에 연결하는 중에 오류가 발생했습니다. 나중에 다시 시도하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Halo Infinites tjeneste for brukeropprettet innhold kunne ikke kontaktes. Prøv igjen senere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er is een fout opgetreden bij het verbinden met de UGC-service van Halo Infinite. Probeer het later opnieuw.",
                        "pl-PL": "Podczas łączenia się z usługą UGC Halo Infinite wystąpił błąd. Spróbuj ponownie później.",
                        "pt-BR": "Ocorreu um erro ao contatar o serviço de UGC de Halo Infinite. Tente novamente mais tarde.",
                        "pt-PT": "Ocorreu um erro ao contactar o serviço UGC do Halo Infinite. Tenta de novo mais tarde.",
                        "ru-RU": "Ошибка установки связи с сервисом пользовательского контента Halo Infinite. Попробуйте позже.",
                        "sv-SE": "Halo Infinites tjänst för användarskapat innehåll kunde inte kontaktas. Försök igen senare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Halo Infinite UGC hizmetiyle bağlantı kurulurken bir hata oluştu. Lütfen daha sonra tekrar deneyin.",
                        "zh-CN": "连接 Halo Infinite UGC 系统时发生错误，请稍后再试。",
                        "zh-TW": "連絡 Halo Infinite UGC 系統時發生錯誤，請稍後再試。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ťнεґē шάѕ äл έřґσя ćθňťαċŧιиĝ ťнē Нαłó Ϊñƒīⁿïťε ЦĜĊ şėŗνίćé. Ρŀęаśє τѓγ аģāϊη ľāťёř. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ťħ℮řе ẅаš ąŋ ěѓřōґ ċôπţáčţìñĝ ŧнэ Ηǻĺθ Ìŋƒìńїţę ÜĠС ŝéгνіĉĕ. Рłėãşë ťřỳ âġаïñ łăŧèґ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Τĥëяê шªş àи ℮ŗŗòг ĉóпţąĉťįиģ ťћē Ήǻŀο Îήƒíŋìţ℮ ÙĢĊ śèґνїćě. Ρŀ℮αšė ŧŗў аġάΐп ľâтеř. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "GameUpdateRequired",
                "gameStartErrorId": 20,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "An update is available for Halo Infinite.  Please update and restart the title.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Pro hru Halo Infinite je k dispozici aktualizace. Aktualizujte prosím hru a pak ji restartujte.",
                        "da-DK": "Der findes en opdatering til Halo Infinite. Opdater, og genstart venligst spillet.",
                        "de-DE": "Für Halo Infinite steht ein Update bereit. Bitte aktualisiere den Titel und starte ihn neu.",
                        "el-GR": "Μια ενημέρωση είναι διαθέσιμη για το Halo Infinite. Ενημέρωσε και κάνε επανεκκίνηση του παιχνιδιού.",
                        "es-ES": "Hay una actualización disponible para Halo Infinite. Actualiza y reinicia el juego.",
                        "es-MX": "Hay una actualización disponible para Halo Infinite.  Actualiza y reinicia el juego.",
                        "fi-FI": "Halo Infiniteen on saatavilla päivitys. Päivitä peli ja käynnistä uudelleen.",
                        "fr-FR": "Une mise à jour est disponible pour Halo Infinite. Veuillez mettre à jour et relancer le jeu.",
                        "hu-HU": "Frissítés érhető el a Halo Infinite-hez. Kérjük, telepítsd és indítsd újra a játékot.",
                        "it-IT": "È disponibile un aggiornamento per Halo Infinite. Aggiorna e riavvia il gioco.",
                        "ja-JP": "Halo Infinite でアップデートが利用可能です。ゲームをアップデートして再起動してください。",
                        "ko-KR": "Halo Infinite의 업데이트가 대기 중입니다. 업데이트 후에 타이틀을 다시 시작하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "En Halo Infinite-oppdatering er tilgjengelig. Oppdater og start spillet på nytt.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er is een update beschikbaar voor Halo Infinite. Installeer de update en start de game opnieuw op.",
                        "pl-PL": "Dostępna jest aktualizacja dla Halo Infinite. Zaktualizuj ten tytuł i ponownie go uruchom.",
                        "pt-BR": "Uma atualização está disponível para Halo Infinite. Atualize e reinicie o jogo.",
                        "pt-PT": "Uma atualização está disponível para o Halo Infinite. Atualiza e reinicia o título.",
                        "ru-RU": "Доступно обновление для Halo Infinite. Пожалуйста, обновите и перезапустите игру.",
                        "sv-SE": "En Halo Infinite-uppdatering är tillgänglig. Uppdatera och starta om spelet.",
                        "tr-TR": "Halo Infinite için bir güncelleme mevcut. Lütfen güncellemeyi yapın ve oyunu yeniden başlatın.",
                        "zh-CN": "Halo Infinite 有可用更新。请更新并重新开始游戏。",
                        "zh-TW": "《Halo Infinite》有可用更新。請更新並重新開始遊戲。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Άи úφδаŧё іś âνªīľâъĺé ƒōґ Ήāŀσ Ĩñƒîиïţё.  Рłэáѕé ũρðàŧз άńď г℮şťαгт ŧћě ţιŧĺе. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ąπ ūφđąтє ϊś ªνäĩłāвĺэ ƒǿŕ Ндľö Іⁿƒĭŉітè.  Ρłéдşé μρðâţє äпđ ѓęśţǻŕŧ ťнё ťϊτŀē. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ăй ūρďªτē ϊş ąνāιļªьľę ƒöґ Ĥдľο Ĭпƒïńιтè.  Ρłēāşē µφđáŧє äⁿď řĕŝţāřτ тħè τįŧŀě. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "UgcNotAllowed",
                "gameStartErrorId": 21,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "A fireteam member's online safety settings do not allow them to view community creations.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Nastavení online zabezpečení člena palebného týmu mu brání v prohlížení obsahu vytvořeného komunitou.",
                        "da-DK": "Et kampgruppemedlems onlinesikkerhedsindstillinger forhindrer vedkommende i at se produktioner fra fællesskabet.",
                        "de-DE": "Die Online-Sicherheitseinstellungen eines Feuerteammitglieds verhindern, dass Community-Inhalte angezeigt werden.",
                        "el-GR": "Οι διαδικτυακές ρυθμίσεις ασφάλειας ενός μέλους της ομάδας μάχης δεν τους επιτρέπουν να βλέπουν δημιουργίες της κοινότητας.",
                        "es-ES": "Los ajustes de seguridad en línea de uno de los miembros impiden al equipo ver las creaciones de la comunidad.",
                        "es-MX": "Los ajustes de seguridad en línea de uno de los miembros del equipo le impiden ver creaciones de la comunidad.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimisi jäsenen verkkosuojausasetukset eivät salli hänen tarkastella yhteisön luomuksia.",
                        "fr-FR": "Les paramètres de sécurité en ligne d'un membre de l'équipe bloquent l'affichage des créations de la communauté.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoport egyik tagjának online biztonsági beállításai nem teszik lehetővé közösségi alkotások megtekintését.",
                        "it-IT": "Le impostazioni di sicurezza online di un membro della squadra d’assalto non gli consentono di visualizzare le creazioni della community.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチーム メンバーのオンライン セーフティー設定により、このコミュニティーの作品を表示できません。",
                        "ko-KR": "한 화력조 멤버의 온라인 보안 설정이 커뮤니티 제작 콘텐츠를 보는 것을 허용하지 않습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Online-sikkerhetsinnstillingene til ett av gruppemedlemmene forbyr vedkommende å se elementer lagd av fellesskapet.",
                        "nl-NL": "Een vuurteamlid kan deze creaties uit de community niet bekijken vanwege zijn of haar online beveiligingsinstellingen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Ustawienia zabezpieczeń online członka drużyny uniemożliwiają mu wyświetlanie treści tworzonych przez społeczność.",
                        "pt-BR": "As configurações de segurança online de um membro da esquadra não permitem a visualização das criações da comunidade.",
                        "pt-PT": "As definições de segurança online de um membro da fireteam não te permitem visualizar as criações da comunidade.",
                        "ru-RU": "Настройки сетевой безопасности кого-то из отряда не позволяют просматривать творения сообщества.",
                        "sv-SE": "En gruppmedlems onlinesäkerhetsinställningar förbjuder denne från att se gemenskapens skapelser.",
                        "tr-TR": "Bir atış timi üyesinin çevrim içi güvenlik ayarları topluluk eserlerini görüntülemesine izin vermiyor.",
                        "zh-CN": "火力小队成员的线上安全设定不允许他们查看社区创作内容。",
                        "zh-TW": "火力小組成員的線上安全設定不允許他們檢視社群創作內容。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ǻ ƒіяęτёåm męмьεѓ'ѕ σŉŀĩηё śдƒέţў šэŧтïⁿğѕ ďб ņõť аľĺσш ţђém ťô νіέẃ тђïš ċôńŧзńτ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ą ƒΐяэţėäм мêмьеŕ'ŝ òйľįπë ŝдƒěŧў šĕťŧίňģş ðõ пòт ªľľóω тћёm ťò νìèώ ţђįş čоήţёńţ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "À ƒїŕěŧеåm mĕмвĕг'ś øήŀϊŋέ śáƒёţγ ѕёţτíйġś ðο ńŏţ âľŀσш ţнёm ŧθ νìэш тћιѕ ćõŉτэńŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "InsufficientNonObservers",
                "gameStartErrorId": 22,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "You must have at least one non-observer player in the fireteam.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "V palebném týmu musíte mít aspoň jednoho hráče, který není pozorovatelem.",
                        "da-DK": "Du skal have mindst én ikke-tilskuerspiller i kampgruppen.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Spieler aus Ihrem Feuerteam darf sich nicht im Zuschauermodus befinden.",
                        "el-GR": "Πρέπει να έχεις τουλάχιστον έναν παίκτη που δεν είναι παρατηρητής στην ομάδα μάχης.",
                        "es-ES": "Debes tener al menos un jugador no observador en el equipo.",
                        "es-MX": "Debes tener al menos un jugador no observador en el equipo.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimissäsi on oltava vähintään yksi ei-tarkkailijapelaaja.",
                        "fr-FR": "Il vous faut au moins un joueur non-spectateur dans l'équipe.",
                        "hu-HU": "Legalább egy nem megfigyelő szerepű játékosnak jelen kell lennie a tűzcsoportban.",
                        "it-IT": "La tua squadra d'assalto deve includere almeno un giocatore non spettatore.",
                        "ja-JP": "オブザーバーではないプレイヤーがファイアチームに 1 人以上必要です。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력팀에 관전자가 아닌 플레이어가 한 명 이상 있어야 합니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Du må ha minst en deltakende spiller i gruppen.",
                        "nl-NL": "Je vuurteam moet ten minste één speler bevatten die geen toeschouwer is.",
                        "pl-PL": "Musisz mieć co najmniej jednego gracza, który nie jest obserwatorem w drużynie.",
                        "pt-BR": "Você precisa ter pelo menos um jogador não observador na esquadra.",
                        "pt-PT": "Tens de ter pelo menos um jogador não observador na fireteam.",
                        "ru-RU": "По крайней мере один из игроков в отряде не должен быть наблюдателем.",
                        "sv-SE": "Du måste ha minst en deltagande spelare i gruppen.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinde en az bir gözlemci olmayan oyuncu olmalı.",
                        "zh-CN": "你的火力小队必须拥有至少 1 名非观战玩家。",
                        "zh-TW": "您必須至少要有 1 位不是旁觀者的玩家在火力小組。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ỳŏū mùşŧ ђăνě ǻť łęăşť öŉė ňōń-σвśеŗνзґ рłαŷ℮г ĭŉ тђě ƒĭгзţéдm. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ύθµ mųѕť ĥāνэ дт ľéдšτ ŏйέ ⁿŏπ-ŏьşēŕνěя ρłäуεŗ íи ťħē ƒīŕ℮ťэåm. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ŷóυ мûѕт ђανè áŧ ĺèåŝτ õπё ŉǿй-οьśёґνĕř φĺǻÿ℮я įⁿ ťћĕ ƒϊřéťēäм. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "MaxFireteamSizeExceeded",
                "gameStartErrorId": 23,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "You have too many players in your Fireteam to start the match. Please increase the number of Max Players or remove some members to start.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "V palebném týmu máte příliš mnoho hráčů na to, abyste mohli zahájit zápas. Pokud chcete začít, zvyšte prosím maximální počet hráčů nebo některé členy odstraňte.",
                        "da-DK": "Du har for mange spillere i din kampgruppe til at starte kampen. For det maksimale antal spillere, eller fjern nogle medlemmer for at starte.",
                        "de-DE": "Es befinden sich zu viele Spieler in deinem Feuerteam, die Partie kann nicht gestartet werden. Bitte erhöhe das Spielermaximum oder entferne ein paar Mitglieder.",
                        "el-GR": "Έχεις πολλούς παίκτες στην Ομάδα Μάχης σου για να ξεκινήσεις τον αγώνα. Αύξησε τον αριθμό των μέγιστων παικτών ή διώξε ορισμένα μέλη για να ξεκινήσεις.",
                        "es-ES": "Tu equipo de asalto tiene demasiados jugadores para empezar la partida. Aumenta el número máximo de jugadores o retira algunos miembros para comenzar.",
                        "es-MX": "Tu equipo tiene demasiados jugadores para comenzar la partida. Aumenta el número de máximo de jugadores o elimina a algunos miembros para comenzar.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimissäsi on liian monta pelaajaa ottelun aloittamiseen. Nosta pelaajien enimmäismäärää tai poista jäseniä aloittaaksesi.",
                        "fr-FR": "Votre équipe est trop nombreuse pour pouvoir démarrer la partie. Augmentez le nombre de joueurs maximum ou réduisez le nombre de joueurs de votre équipe pour démarrer.",
                        "hu-HU": "Túl sok játékos van a tűzcsoportodban a mérkőzés megkezdéséhez. Növeld a maximális játékosszámot, vagy távolíts el néhány tagot a kezdéshez.",
                        "it-IT": "La tua squadra d'assalto include troppi giocatori per poter avviare la partita. Aumenta il numero massimo di giocatori ammessi o rimuovi alcuni membri della squadra per iniziare.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームの人数が多すぎるため、マッチを開始できません。最大プレイヤー数を増やすか、メンバーを削除して開始してください。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조에 플레이어가 너무 많아서 매치를 시작할 수 없습니다. 최대 플레이어 수를 늘리거나 일부 멤버를 내보내십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Det er for mange spillere i gruppen din til å starte kampen. Øk det maksimale antallet spillere, eller fjern noen spillere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Er zijn te veel spelers in je vuurteam om de match te kunnen starten. Verhoog het maximale aantal spelers of verwijder enkele spelers.",
                        "pl-PL": "W twojej drużynie jest zbyt wielu graczy, aby można było rozpocząć mecz. Aby rozpocząć, zwiększ maksymalną dozwoloną liczbę graczy lub usuń część członków.",
                        "pt-BR": "Sua esquadra tem jogadores demais para iniciar a partida. Aumente o número máximo de jogadores ou remova alguns membros.",
                        "pt-PT": "Tens demasiados jogadores na tua Fireteam para começar o jogo. Aumenta o número Máximo de jogadores ou remove alguns membros para começar.",
                        "ru-RU": "Невозможно начать матч, в вашем отряде слишком много игроков. Увеличьте максимальное количество игроков или удалите кого-то из отряда.",
                        "sv-SE": "Du har för många spelare för att starta matchen i din grupp. Öka maxantalet spelare eller ta bort några spelare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizde karşılaşmayı başlatmak için çok fazla oyuncu var. Başlamak için lütfen Maksimum Oyuncu sayısını artırın veya bazı üyeleri çıkarın.",
                        "zh-CN": "由于您的火力小队中有太多玩家而无法开始匹配游戏。请增加最大玩家数或移除一些成员即可开始匹配游戏。",
                        "zh-TW": "由於您的火力小組中有太多玩家而無法開始配對遊戲。請增加最大玩家數或移除一些成員即可開始配對遊戲。",
                        "qps-ploc": "¥ōц ндνз τθо măņу рļаŷ℮яŝ їŉ ўŏŭř ₣ìŕєţеàм ťò śτдгţ τĥё мáţĉћ. Ρľèãśë ίпςѓėāѕє тħз ńџmвёѓ θƒ Μâж Рŀâÿэŗѕ ōŕ řзмσνë śοmė мèmъέŗš ŧο šţąřт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ўόū ĥāνё τõθ мāлý ρĺàỳзѓş íⁿ ỳøυґ ₣ïѓęτēàm ťö şťāяţ ţħê мáťсђ. Ρŀёªś℮ ĭηсг℮άşе ŧђë иųmъεř ŏƒ Мд× Рłăÿéřş θг ŗéмоνе şσмě mєmьéгѕ ţō śťаят. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ўőυ ĥāνē ŧσŏ mаŉý ρļâỳĕřѕ ïл ÿōúя ₣ίřęтêăm ŧǿ ŝŧдŕţ тĥё måŧċћ. Рļэāşе īηċřēášė ţĥё ⁿцmьèř øƒ Мãж Ρℓǻýěřş ôř ґémòνε śόмë мêмъêѓŝ ťо šτãгť. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "PartySizeNotAllowed",
                "gameStartErrorId": 24,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Your fireteam's size is not allowed in the selected activity.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Velikost vašeho palebného týmu není ve vybrané aktivitě povolena.",
                        "da-DK": "Din kampgruppes størrelse er ikke tilladt i den valgte aktivitet.",
                        "de-DE": "Die Größe deines Feuerteams ist in der gewählten Aktivität nicht zulässig.",
                        "el-GR": "Το μέγεθος της ομάδας μάχης σου δεν επιτρέπεται στην επιλεγμένη δραστηριότητα.",
                        "es-ES": "El tamaño de tu equipo de asalto no está permitido en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "es-MX": "El tamaño de tu equipo no se permite en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimisi koko ei ole sallittu valitussa aktiviteetissa.",
                        "fr-FR": "La taille de votre équipe n'est pas autorisée dans l'activité sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsapatod mérete nem engedélyezett a választott aktivitáshoz.",
                        "it-IT": "Le dimensioni della squadra d'assalto non sono ammesse nell'attività selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "選択したアクティビティでファイヤーチームのサイズが許可されていません。",
                        "ko-KR": "현재의 화력조 멤버수로는 선택된 활동을 할 수 없습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Gruppen din har feil størrelse for den valgte aktiviteten.",
                        "nl-NL": "De grootte van je vuurteam is niet toegestaan voor de geselecteerde activiteit.",
                        "pl-PL": "Liczebność twojej drużyny nie spełnia wymagań dla wybranej aktywności.",
                        "pt-BR": "O tamanho da sua esquadra não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "O tamanho da tua fireteam não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "ru-RU": "Недопустимый размер отряда для выбранного занятия.",
                        "sv-SE": "Din grupp har fel storlek för den valda aktiviteten.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin boyutuna seçili etkinlikte izin verilmemektedir.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队人数不符合所选活动要求。",
                        "zh-TW": "所選活動不允許您的火力小組人數。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ŷöůя ƒΐřέŧёăм'ѕ ѕįźз îś ñοŧ åŀľǿŵĕð ΐи ţнě şэℓεćţεð аčτїνΐтŷ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Υõùґ ƒìяėтёάм'ѕ šìźе îŝ иǿτ áļĺόщëđ ΐп тĥз šėŀęςтĕδ âςтїνίτу. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Υøûѓ ƒíŗèţєдm'ŝ ѕΐžé їş ńōτ αłĺόωєð їπ ŧћė şêļėсţεď âćťїνïтγ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "DisallowedDeviceClass",
                "gameStartErrorId": 27,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "One or more members of your fireteam is on a device type that's not allowed in the selected activity.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden člen vašeho palebného týmu používá typ zařízení, které není ve vybrané aktivitě povoleno.",
                        "da-DK": "Et eller flere medlemmer af din kampgruppe bruger en enhedstype, der ikke er tilladt i den valgte aktivitet.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Mitglied deines Feuerteams verwendet ein Gerät, das in der ausgewählten Aktivität nicht zugelassen ist.",
                        "el-GR": "Ένα ή περισσότερα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης σου βρίσκονται σε έναν τύπο συσκευής που δεν επιτρέπεται στην επιλεγμένη δραστηριότητα.",
                        "es-ES": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo de asalto están usando un tipo de dispositivo no permitido en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "es-MX": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo están en un tipo de dispositivo que no está permitido en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yksi tulitiimisi jäsenistä käyttää laitetyyppiä, jota ei sallita valitussa aktiviteetissa.",
                        "fr-FR": "Un ou plusieurs membres de l'équipe jouent sur un dispositif qui n'est pas autorisé dans l'activité sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod legalább egy tagja olyan eszköztípust használ, amely nem engedélyezett a választott aktivitásban.",
                        "it-IT": "Uno o più membri della tua squadra d'assalto giocano su un tipo di dispositivo che non consente loro di accedere all'attività selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームの 1 人以上のメンバーが、選択したアクティビティで許可されていないデバイス タイプを使用しています。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버 중 한 명 이상이 선택된 활동을 할 수 없는 장치 유형을 사용 중입니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Ett eller flere gruppemedlemmer bruker en enhetstype som ikke er tillatt i den valgte aktiviteten.",
                        "nl-NL": "Een of meer leden van je vuurteam spelen op een apparaattype dat niet is toegestaan voor de geselecteerde activiteit.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden członek twojej drużyny korzysta z typu urządzenia, który nie jest dozwolony w przypadku wybranej aktywności.",
                        "pt-BR": "Um ou mais membros da sua esquadra estão em um tipo de dispositivo que não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "Um ou mais membros da tua fireteam estão a utilizar um tipo de dispositivo que não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "ru-RU": "Один или несколько участников вашего отряда используют тип устройства, запрещённый для выбранного занятия.",
                        "sv-SE": "En eller fler gruppmedlemmar använder en enhetstyp som inte är tillåten i den valda aktiviteten.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin bir veya daha fazla üyesi, seçili etkinlikte izin verilmeyen bir cihaz türü kullanmaktadır.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中有一名或多名成员正在使用所选活动中不允许使用的装置类型。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中有一名或多名成員正在使用所選活動中不允許使用的裝置類型。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Öňę őř mòгè мεmвєѓś õƒ ŷθùř ƒĩґêŧзâm ίѕ οй а đėνΐĉë τγφè тнąţ'š ńóţ âℓļőŵзδ їй τђê šеℓ℮ςτēď дčťĭνĩτγ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ώŉэ őг мõгє měмъεŗŝ óƒ уоūѓ ƒìŕĕťєăм іѕ оп α đěνīčë ŧўφе ťђåτ'ѕ ⁿöŧ αľľòẅęđ ίπ ťђę ѕ℮ľєċτëđ ãċтїνĩтŷ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Фиė όř mŏгè мémьĕгѕ бƒ ŷоűř ƒїŕěтëäm їŝ õñ â ďêνïς℮ тýре τђăτ'š ŉøт αĺℓοшеď ĭⁿ ŧђ℮ ѕèľéĉŧёδ åςτїνïťў. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "DisallowedInputType",
                "gameStartErrorId": 28,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "One or more members of your fireteam is using an input type that's not allowed in the selected activity.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden člen vašeho palebného týmu používá typ vstupu, který není ve vybrané aktivitě povolen.",
                        "da-DK": "Et eller flere medlemmer af din kampgruppe bruger en inputtype, der ikke er tilladt i den valgte aktivitet.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Mitglied deines Feuerteams verwendet einen Eingabetyp, der in der ausgewählten Aktivität nicht zugelassen ist.",
                        "el-GR": "Ένα ή περισσότερα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης σου χρησιμοποιούν έναν τύπο εισόδου που δεν επιτρέπεται στην επιλεγμένη δραστηριότητα.",
                        "es-ES": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo de asalto están utilizando un dispositivo de entrada no permitido en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "es-MX": "Uno o varios miembros de tu equipo están usando un tipo de entrada que no está permitido en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yksi tulitiimisi jäsenistä käyttää syötetyyppiä, jota ei sallita valitussa aktiviteetissa.",
                        "fr-FR": "Un ou plusieurs membres de l'équipe utilisent un périphérique d'entrée qui n'est pas autorisé dans l'activité sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod legalább egy tagja olyan beviteli típust használ, amely nem engedélyezett a választott aktivitásban.",
                        "it-IT": "Uno o più membri della tua squadra d'assalto utilizzano un tipo di input non consentito nell'attività selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームの 1 人以上のメンバーが、選択したアクティビティで許可されていない入力タイプを使用しています。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버 중 한 명 이상이 선택된 활동을 할 수 없는 입력 유형을 사용 중입니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Ett eller flere gruppemedlemmer bruker en kontrolltype som ikke er tillatt i den valgte aktiviteten.",
                        "nl-NL": "Een of meer leden van je vuurteam gebruiken een invoerapparaat dat niet is toegestaan voor de geselecteerde activiteit.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden członek twojej drużyny korzysta z urządzenia wejściowego, które nie jest dozwolone w przypadku wybranej aktywności.",
                        "pt-BR": "Um ou mais membros da sua esquadra estão usando um tipo de entrada que não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "Um ou mais membros da tua fireteam estão a utilizar um tipo de entradas que não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "ru-RU": "Один или несколько участников вашего отряда используют устройство ввода, запрещённое для выбранного занятия.",
                        "sv-SE": "En eller fler gruppmedlemmar använder en kontrolltyp som inte är tillåten i den valda aktiviteten.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin bir veya daha fazla üyesi, seçili etkinlikte izin verilmeyen bir giriş türü kullanıyor.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中有一名或多名成员正在使用所选活动中不允许使用的输入类型。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中有一名或多名成員正在使用所選活動中不允許使用的輸入類型。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ωйė ŏѓ мόřê мемьęѓŝ ôƒ ỳбùŕ ƒĩяєťęдм ïś μśιлğ ăή įňφūŧ ťуρε ţђάт'ŝ йοт αĺĺǿẁĕδ ίп ŧђě ѕėℓεсťëδ ąстĭνιťý. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Øήē ôг мöřê męmьēґŝ σƒ ỳоųř ƒΐґěτĕâm įş µşϊŉĝ дⁿ ĩлρϋт τуφє ŧħąţ'ś пőť ªľľøωèð іņ тħê şзļеčŧεð áċţіνїтý. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Õņē õг мǿŕê мĕмъêřš òƒ ýőůŕ ƒϊřεťзаm іś υśїⁿğ ǻл ιñрūţ ťỳρě τћâŧ'ş ŉŏţ ăŀℓõẁзð іи ťђε ŝéŀĕ¢ťέđ ǻ¢ŧίνϊťý. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "IncompatibleClearanceIds",
                "gameStartErrorId": 29,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Fireteam members are synchonizing game data; please wait.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Členové palebného týmu si synchronizují herní data; počkejte prosím.",
                        "da-DK": "Kampgruppemedlemmer synkroniserer spildata; vent venligst.",
                        "de-DE": "Feuerteammitglieder synchronisieren Spieldaten. Bitte warten.",
                        "el-GR": "Τα μέλη της Ομάδα Μάχης συγχρονίζουν τα δεδομένα του παιχνιδιού. Περίμενε λίγο.",
                        "es-ES": "Los miembros del equipo de asalto están sincronizando los datos de juego. Espera un momento.",
                        "es-MX": "Los miembros del equipo están sincronizando los datos del juego; espera.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimin jäsenet synkronoivat pelitietoja; ole hyvä ja odota.",
                        "fr-FR": "Les membres de l'équipe synchronisent les données de jeu, veuillez patienter.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoport tagjainak adatai szinkronizálás alatt; kérjük, várj.",
                        "it-IT": "I membri della squadra d'assalto stanno sincronizzando i dati di gioco. Attendi.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームのメンバーはゲームデータを同期しています。お待ちください。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버들이 게임 데이터를 동기화 중입니다. 기다려 주십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Gruppemedlemmer synkroniserer spilldata. Vennligst vent.",
                        "nl-NL": "Vuurteamleden synchroniseren gamegegevens. Even geduld...",
                        "pl-PL": "Członkowie drużyny synchronizują dane gry; poczekaj.",
                        "pt-BR": "Os membros da esquadra estão sincronizando os dados do jogo. Aguarde.",
                        "pt-PT": "Os membros da Fireteam estão a sincronizar dados do jogo; aguarda.",
                        "ru-RU": "Участники отряда синхронизируют игровые данные. Подождите.",
                        "sv-SE": "Gruppmedlemmar synkroniserar speldata. Vänligen vänta.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timi üyelerinin oyun verileri senkronize ediliyor; lütfen bekleyin.",
                        "zh-CN": "火力小队成员正在同步游戏数据；请稍候。",
                        "zh-TW": "火力小組成員正在同步遊戲資料；請稍候。",
                        "qps-ploc": "₣īřęţеαm мέмвëяŝ åřê śγл¢ћоηїżíŉģ ğãmе ðáţа; рℓεаşĕ ẃąíт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "₣îяєτєãм mέмъёґś ąгз ŝўň¢ĥσпįžіŋĝ ġдмë ðáтâ; рļзåśе ŵàįŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "₣ιѓěтęαm mëmъëгş áѓэ şγπċћǿňížíŋģ ġǻмĕ ðăτª; ρļ℮ąŝĕ ωǻìţ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "InsufficientClientCount",
                "gameStartErrorId": 30,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Fireteam does not have the minimum number of devices required for online play.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Palebný tým nemá minimální počet zařízení potřebný pro online hraní.",
                        "da-DK": "Kampgruppen har det minimale antal enheder, der er påkrævet til onlinespil.",
                        "de-DE": "Das Feuerteam verfügt nicht über die Mindestanzahl von Geräten, um online zu spielen.",
                        "el-GR": "Η Ομάδα Μάχης δεν διαθέτει τον ελάχιστο αριθμό συσκευών που απαιτούνται για το διαδικτυακό παιχνίδι.",
                        "es-ES": "El equipo de asalto no dispone del número mínimo de dispositivos necesario para jugar en línea.",
                        "es-MX": "El equipo no tiene el número mínimo de dispositivos necesarios para el juego en línea.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiimillä ei ole vähimmäismäärää laitteita, jotka verkkopelaaminen vaatii.",
                        "fr-FR": "L'équipe ne dispose pas du nombre minimum de dispositifs requis pour le jeu en ligne.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoport nem rendelkezik a minimális szükséges számú eszközzel az online játékhoz.",
                        "it-IT": "La squadra d'assalto non dispone del numero minimo di dispositivi necessari per il gioco online.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームが、オンラインプレイに必要なデバイス数を持っていません。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조가 온라인 플레이에 필요한 최소 장치 개수를 갖추고 있지 않습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Gruppen har ikke minimumsantallet med enheter som kreves for onlinespill.",
                        "nl-NL": "Vuurteam heeft niet het minimale aantal apparaten dat nodig is om online te spelen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Drużyna nie ma minimalnej liczby urządzeń wymaganych do gry online.",
                        "pt-BR": "A esquadra não tem o número mínimo de dispositivos necessários para jogar online.",
                        "pt-PT": "A fireteam não tem o número mínimo de dispositivos necessários para jogar online.",
                        "ru-RU": "В отряде нет минимального количества устройств, необходимых для игры по сети.",
                        "sv-SE": "Gruppen har inte minimiantalet enheter som krävs för onlinespel.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timi, çevrimiçi oyun için gereken minimum cihaz sayısına sahip değildir.",
                        "zh-CN": "火力小队没有在线游戏所需的最少装置数量。",
                        "zh-TW": "火力小組沒有線上遊戲所需的最少裝置數量。",
                        "qps-ploc": "₣įяěťёдм đóзş ņøτ ћǻνę ťĥē mіŉîmυm ⁿűмвēŗ бƒ đзνίςéѕ яęqũΐґěð ƒǿя опľιņê ρļąŷ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "₣ΐŗêτēāм δôěš йōţ ћąνè тнэ мįйϊmũм ŋũmьĕг õƒ δэνïċëś řęqџįŕëð ƒõґ бпļίи℮ рļǻý. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "₣ïŕēŧėãм ďо℮š ňøť нǻνё ţħё mίήìmûm иũmвëř ǿƒ đēνіĉέş ŗēqůįґёđ ƒőя ŏⁿℓĭŉę рĺāÿ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "CampaignContentNotInstalled",
                "gameStartErrorId": 31,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "All fireteam members must have the selected campaign content installed.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Všichni členové palebného týmu musí mít nainstalovaný vybraný obsah kampaně.",
                        "da-DK": "Alle kampgruppemedlemmer skal have det valgte kampagneindhold installeret.",
                        "de-DE": "Die gewählten Kampagneninhalte müssen bei allen Feuerteammitgliedern installiert sein.",
                        "el-GR": "Όλα τα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης πρέπει να έχουν εγκατεστημένο το επιλεγμένο περιεχόμενο εκστρατείας.",
                        "es-ES": "Todos los miembros del equipo de asalto deben tener instalado el contenido de campaña seleccionado.",
                        "es-MX": "Todos los miembros del equipo deben tener instalado el contenido de la campaña seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Kaikilla tulitiimin jäsenillä on oltava valittu kampanjasisältö asennettuna.",
                        "fr-FR": "Tous les membres de l'équipe doivent avoir la campagne sélectionnée installée.",
                        "hu-HU": "Minden tűzcsoport tagnak telepítenie kell a választott hadjárat tartalmat.",
                        "it-IT": "Tutti i membri della squadra d'assalto devono avere installato i contenuti della Campagna selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "すべてのファイヤーチーム メンバーが、選択したキャンペーン コンテンツをインストールしている必要があります。",
                        "ko-KR": "모든 화력조 멤버가 선택된 캠페인 콘텐츠를 설치해야 합니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Alle gruppemedlemmer må ha det valgte kampanjeinnholdet installert.",
                        "nl-NL": "Alle vuurteamleden moeten de geselecteerde campagnecontent hebben geïnstalleerd.",
                        "pl-PL": "Wszyscy członkowie drużyny muszą mieć zainstalowaną zawartość wybranej kampanii.",
                        "pt-BR": "Todos os membros da esquadra devem ter o conteúdo da campanha selecionada instalado.",
                        "pt-PT": "Todos os membros da fireteam devem ter o conteúdo da campanha selecionada instalado.",
                        "ru-RU": "У всех участников отряда должен быть установлен выбранный контент кампании.",
                        "sv-SE": "Alla gruppmedlemmar måste ha det valda kampanjinnehållet installerat.",
                        "tr-TR": "Tüm atış timi üyelerinin seçilen harekât içeriğini yüklemiş olması gerekir.",
                        "zh-CN": "所有火力小队成员必须安装所选战役内容。",
                        "zh-TW": "所有火力小組成員必須安裝所選戰役內容。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Åłĺ ƒĩгëτęãm mémьєгš mцśť ĥåνé ŧнє ŝëľēčτєđ ċãmράíğπ ςόлтĕŉŧ іиѕţąŀļëď. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Дĺľ ƒιŗėτęαм mėmъêřś múšт ħâνз ťђė śεĺέĉťéð ςǻмрàĭĝл čǿπτęйţ ϊņŝţąļĺєδ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Àĺℓ ƒīŕěтěάм mεmьёгš мūśτ ħâνĕ тĥё śëľęςтзď çаmраιĝŉ ćоηťέлτ іñşťąłľéď. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "CampaignContentNotEntitled",
                "gameStartErrorId": 32,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "All fireteam members must be entitled to the selected campaign content.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Všichni členové palebného týmu musí mít přístupová oprávnění k vybranému obsahu kampaně.",
                        "da-DK": "Alle kampgruppemedlemmer skal have adgang til det valgte kampagneindhold.",
                        "de-DE": "Alle Feuerteammitglieder benötigen die Berechtigung für die gewählten Kampagneninhalte.",
                        "el-GR": "Όλα τα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης πρέπει να δικαιούνται το επιλεγμένο περιεχόμενο εκστρατείας.",
                        "es-ES": "Todos los miembros del equipo de asalto deben tener acceso al contenido de campaña seleccionado.",
                        "es-MX": "Todos los miembros del equipo deben tener acceso al contenido de la campaña seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Kaikilla tulitiimin jäsenillä on oltava käyttöoikeus valittuun kampanjasisältöön.",
                        "fr-FR": "Tous les membres de l'équipe doivent avoir accès à la campagne sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "Minden tűzcsoport tagnak jogosultnak kell lennie a választott hadjárat tartalomra.",
                        "it-IT": "Tutti i membri della squadra d'assalto devono avere accesso ai contenuti della Campagna selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "すべてのファイヤーチーム メンバーが、選択したキャンペーン コンテンツのプレイ資格を持っている必要があります。",
                        "ko-KR": "모든 화력조 멤버가 선택된 캠페인 콘텐츠를 플레이할 권한이 있어야 합니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Alle gruppemedlemmer må ha tilgang til det valgte kampanjeinnholdet.",
                        "nl-NL": "Alle vuurteamleden moeten bevoegd zijn om de geselecteerde campagnecontent te spelen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Wszyscy członkowie drużyny muszą mieć dostęp do zawartości wybranej kampanii.",
                        "pt-BR": "Todos os membros da esquadra devem ter acesso ao conteúdo da campanha selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "Todos os membros da fireteam devem ter direito ao conteúdo selecionado da campanha.",
                        "ru-RU": "У всех участников отряда должен быть доступ к выбранному контенту кампании.",
                        "sv-SE": "Alla gruppmedlemmar måste ha tillgång till det valda kampanjinnehållet.",
                        "tr-TR": "Tüm atış timi üyelerinin seçilen harekât içeriğine yetkilerinin olması gerekir.",
                        "zh-CN": "所有火力小队成员必须有玩所选战役内容的权限。",
                        "zh-TW": "所有火力小組成員必須有玩所選戰役內容的權限。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Äļł ƒιŗĕţεâm mеmвěяѕ mùşτ ьз ęňтίţļзð ţθ тћĕ śεℓěčтεδ ċăмρąïģη ċóńŧ℮ŋт. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Δℓŀ ƒϊгėŧĕαм мемъзѓš mџѕτ ьě ēņтĩţŀêđ ŧб ţђê ŝέļêĉτęð çαмраїĝή ċοйťéňţ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Áłł ƒϊřëτεáм мзмьеŗŝ mųśţ вê ěñтíτľёđ ţò ţђè ѕеĺзćťĕď çάmрăιğň ¢øŋŧεⁿτ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "TooManyNonObservers",
                "gameStartErrorId": 33,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "The number of non-observers in the game is larger than the maximum number of players allowed.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Počet hráčů, kteří ve hře nejsou pozorovateli, je vyšší než maximální povolený počet hráčů.",
                        "da-DK": "Antallet af ikke-tilskuere i spillet er større end det maksimale antal tilladte spillere.",
                        "de-DE": "Die Anzahl der Teilnehmer, die keine Zuschauer sind, ist höher als das zulässige Spielermaximum.",
                        "el-GR": "Ο αριθμός των μη παρατηρητών στο παιχνίδι είναι μεγαλύτερος από τον μέγιστο επιτρεπόμενο αριθμό παικτών.",
                        "es-ES": "El número de jugadores no espectadores de la partida es superior al máximo de jugadores permitidos.",
                        "es-MX": "El número de no observadores en el juego es mayor que el número máximo de jugadores permitidos.",
                        "fi-FI": "Pelissä olevien ei-tarkkailijapelaajien määrä ylittää sallittujen pelaajien enimmäismäärän.",
                        "fr-FR": "Le nombre de non-observateurs en jeu est supérieur au nombre maximal de joueurs autorisé.",
                        "hu-HU": "A játékban lévő, nem megfigyelők száma nagyobb, mint a maximálisan megengedett játékosszám.",
                        "it-IT": "Il numero di non osservatori nel gioco è maggiore del numero massimo di giocatori consentiti.",
                        "ja-JP": "ゲーム内の非オブザーバーの数が、許可されているプレイヤーの最大数よりも多いです。",
                        "ko-KR": "이 게임의 비관전자 수가 허용된 인원 수보다 많습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Antall deltakende spillere er større enn maksimalt antall tillatte spillere.",
                        "nl-NL": "Het aantal niet-toeschouwers in de game is groter dan het maximale aantal dat is toegestaan.",
                        "pl-PL": "Liczba osób w grze, które nie są obserwatorami, jest większa niż maksymalna dozwolona liczba graczy.",
                        "pt-BR": "O número de não espectadores no jogo é maior do que o número máximo de jogadores permitido.",
                        "pt-PT": "O número de não observadores no jogo é superior ao número máximo de jogadores permitido.",
                        "ru-RU": "Количество игроков, не являющихся наблюдателями, превышает максимально допустимое количество игроков в игре.",
                        "sv-SE": "Antalet deltagande spelare är större än maxantalet tillåtna spelare.",
                        "tr-TR": "Oyundaki gözlemci olmayan oyuncu sayısı, izin verilen maksimum oyuncu sayısından daha fazla.",
                        "zh-CN": "游戏中的非旁观者数量大于允许的玩家人数上限。",
                        "zh-TW": "遊戲中的非旁觀者數量大於允許的玩家人數上限。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ţħе ňůмъéґ оƒ йøп-ōьšзřνзѓѕ īŉ ţђę ĝǻмę ĩş ľăřģėг ţђäή ţĥĕ мâхϊмŭm πΰмвзя оƒ рℓªỳёгš αŀℓőωέδ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-ploca": "Тħè ηùmьзř оƒ ņŏŉ-òъѕεгνéгš íņ ŧђĕ ġàm℮ īš ℓªřğег ťђãη τħε máжĩmΰм πµmъ℮я õƒ ρļåўĕѓš ªłľбŵêð. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! ",
                        "qps-plocm": "Τнė ňџmвзř σƒ ⁿŏη-оьśзгνзŕś ïπ ťђє ĝâмє īŝ ļдŗġêѓ τћâη ţћë mάжïmųm йΰmвėѓ ŏƒ рĺдỳ℮ŗŝ αļŀόώěď. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! "
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "TemporarilyDisabled",
                "gameStartErrorId": 34,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Due to high server load, this mode is temporarily disabled.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Z důvodu vysokého zatížení serveru je tento režim dočasně zakázaný.",
                        "da-DK": "På grund af høj serverbelastning er denne spiltype midlertidigt deaktiveret.",
                        "de-DE": "Aufgrund von hoher Serverauslastung ist dieser Modus vorübergehend deaktiviert.",
                        "el-GR": "Λόγω υψηλού φόρτου διακομιστή, αυτή η λειτουργία είναι προσωρινά απενεργοποιημένη.",
                        "es-ES": "Este modo se ha deshabilitado temporalmente por el elevado tráfico del servidor.",
                        "es-MX": "Debido a la alta sobrecarga del servidor, este modo está deshabilitado temporalmente.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tämä tila on poistettu tilapäisesti käytöstä palvelimen raskaan kuormituksen vuoksi.",
                        "fr-FR": "En raison d'une charge élevée du serveur, ce mode est temporairement désactivé.",
                        "hu-HU": "A szerverek leterheltsége miatt ez a játékmód jelenleg nem elérhető.",
                        "it-IT": "A causa dell'elevato carico del server, questa modalità è temporaneamente disabilitata.",
                        "ja-JP": "サーバー負荷が高いため、このモードは一時的に無効になります。",
                        "ko-KR": "서버 부하가 높아서 이 모드가 일시적으로 비활성화되었습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Denne modusen er midlertidig deaktivert på grunn av høy serverbelastning.",
                        "nl-NL": "Vanwege de hoge serverbelasting is dit speltype tijdelijk niet beschikbaar.",
                        "pl-PL": "Ten tryb jest tymczasowo wyłączony ze względu na duże obciążenie serwera.",
                        "pt-BR": "Devido à sobrecarga do servidor, este modo está temporariamente desativado.",
                        "pt-PT": "Devido à elevada carga do servidor, este modo está temporariamente desativado.",
                        "ru-RU": "Этот режим временно отключён из-за высокой нагрузки на сервер.",
                        "sv-SE": "På grund av hög serverbelastning är det här läget tillfälligt avstängt.",
                        "tr-TR": "Yüksek sunucu yükü nedeniyle bu mod geçici olarak devre dışı bırakıldı.",
                        "zh-CN": "由于服务器负载过高，此模式已暂时禁用。",
                        "zh-TW": "由於伺服器負載過高，此模式已暫時停用。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Đųε ťô ђΐğђ ŝεŕνêř ĺǿąδ, ţђįś mőδě îş τėmρθѓąřιĺý ďιśăъłέð. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ďűз ţö ĥìĝћ şεѓνėґ ŀőàđ, τĥįś møðê ιś ţéмφõŕªгĩĺγ ďïşªвℓêđ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Đüε ţô нїĝĥ ŝėяνêг łσâď, ťĥίş møðę ìş ţèмрσѓǻŗїľÿ ðïšαьľéδ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "GameContentNotInstalled",
                "gameStartErrorId": 35,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "All fireteam members must have the selected game content installed.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Všichni členové palebného týmu musí mít nainstalovaný vybraný herní obsah.",
                        "da-DK": "Alle kampgruppemedlemmer skal have det valgte spilindhold installeret.",
                        "de-DE": "Die gewählten Spielinhalte müssen bei allen Feuerteammitgliedern installiert sein.",
                        "el-GR": "Όλα τα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης πρέπει να έχουν εγκατεστημένο το επιλεγμένο περιεχόμενο παιχνιδιού.",
                        "es-ES": "Todos los miembros del equipo de asalto deben tener instalado el contenido del juego seleccionado.",
                        "es-MX": "Todos los miembros del equipo deben tener instalado el contenido del juego seleccionado.",
                        "fi-FI": "Kaikilla tulitiimin jäsenillä on oltava valittu pelisisältö asennettuna.",
                        "fr-FR": "Tous les membres de l'équipe doivent avoir le contenu sélectionné installé.",
                        "hu-HU": "Minden tűzcsoport tagnak telepítenie kell a választott játéktartalmat.",
                        "it-IT": "Tutti i membri della squadra d'assalto devono avere installato i contenuti di gioco selezionati.",
                        "ja-JP": "すべてのファイヤーチーム メンバーが、選択したゲームコンテンツをインストールしている必要があります。",
                        "ko-KR": "모든 화력조 멤버가 선택된 게임 콘텐츠를 설치해야 합니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Alle gruppemedlemmer må ha det valgte spillinnholdet installert.",
                        "nl-NL": "Alle vuurteamleden moeten de geselecteerde gamecontent hebben geïnstalleerd.",
                        "pl-PL": "Wszyscy członkowie drużyny muszą mieć zainstalowaną zawartość wybranej gry.",
                        "pt-BR": "Todos os membros da esquadra devem ter o conteúdo do jogo selecionado instalado.",
                        "pt-PT": "Todos os membros da fireteam devem ter o conteúdo de jogo selecionado instalado.",
                        "ru-RU": "У всех участников отряда должен быть установлен выбранный игровой контент.",
                        "sv-SE": "Alla gruppmedlemmar måste ha det valda spelinnehållet installerat.",
                        "tr-TR": "Tüm atış timi üyelerinin seçilen oyun içeriğini yüklemiş olması gerekir.",
                        "zh-CN": "所有火力小队成员必须安装所选游戏内容。",
                        "zh-TW": "所有火力小組成員必須安裝所選遊戲內容。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Άℓľ ƒϊяэŧēàm mêмвέřş мūşŧ ĥâνë τħе ŝèĺεсţзđ ġãmз сöŋτēŉţ ìńśτªℓļèδ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Âŀŀ ƒîŕ℮ťěáм mεмвěґş мџŝţ ĥǻνė ťђě şēŀē¢ţėđ ĝămз ćσñτёñт ìŋśťąĺŀéď. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ăļł ƒίŗёτèаm mєmвέŕѕ mΰŝτ ħåν℮ ŧнė śęĺè¢тёď ğąmэ çõиτеñт іņśťāļℓеδ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "GameContentNotEntitled",
                "gameStartErrorId": 36,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "All fireteam members must be entitled to the selected game content.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Všichni členové palebného týmu musí mít přístupová oprávnění k vybranému hernímu obsahu.",
                        "da-DK": "Alle kampgruppemedlemmer skal have adgang til det valgte spilindhold.",
                        "de-DE": "Alle Feuerteammitglieder benötigen die Berechtigung für die gewählten Spielinhalte.",
                        "el-GR": "Όλα τα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης πρέπει να δικαιούνται το επιλεγμένο περιεχόμενο παιχνιδιού.",
                        "es-ES": "Todos los miembros del equipo de asalto deben tener acceso al contenido del juego seleccionado.",
                        "es-MX": "Todos los miembros del equipo deben tener acceso al contenido del juego seleccionado.",
                        "fi-FI": "Kaikilla tulitiimin jäsenillä on oltava käyttöoikeus valittuun pelisisältöön.",
                        "fr-FR": "Tous les membres de l'équipe doivent avoir accès au contenu sélectionné.",
                        "hu-HU": "Minden tűzcsoport tagnak jogosultnak kell lennie a választott játéktartalomra.",
                        "it-IT": "Tutti i membri della squadra d'assalto devono avere accesso ai contenuti di gioco selezionati.",
                        "ja-JP": "すべてのファイヤーチーム メンバーが、選択したゲーム コンテンツのプレイ資格を持っている必要があります。",
                        "ko-KR": "모든 화력조 멤버가 선택된 게임 콘텐츠를 플레이할 권한이 있어야 합니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Alle gruppemedlemmer må ha tilgang til det valgte spillinnholdet.",
                        "nl-NL": "Alle vuurteamleden moeten bevoegd zijn om de geselecteerde gamecontent te spelen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Wszyscy członkowie drużyny muszą mieć dostęp do zawartości wybranej gry.",
                        "pt-BR": "Todos os membros da esquadra devem ter acesso ao conteúdo do jogo selecionado.",
                        "pt-PT": "Todos os membros da fireteam devem ter direito ao conteúdo de jogo selecionado.",
                        "ru-RU": "У всех участников отряда должен быть доступ к выбранному игровому контенту.",
                        "sv-SE": "Alla gruppmedlemmar måste ha tillgång till det valda spelinnehållet.",
                        "tr-TR": "Tüm atış timi üyelerinin seçilen oyun içeriğine yetkilerinin olması gerekir.",
                        "zh-CN": "所有火力小队成员必须有玩所选游戏内容的权限。",
                        "zh-TW": "所有火力小組成員必須有玩所選遊戲內容的權限。",
                        "qps-ploc": "∆łł ƒìґēţēâm мêмвėґš мμşť ьз ēйţĭŧℓэđ ťò ťнê ѕέłęςŧėð ģäмε çθпťēŉŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ãľℓ ƒΐŕέτēаm mêmъêřş мũşτ вę єñтĭτℓëď тσ ŧħé ѕєļеčŧеď ģдmз ¢ŏŉŧèňŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Αŀľ ƒĭѓēŧêąm мэmвєŗŝ мμŝţ ъè єйťìŧľєð τô ţђë ѕéłĕςťеδ ģąmè čōñťëπŧ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "DisallowedDeviceClassConsole",
                "gameStartErrorId": 37,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "One or more members of your fireteam is on console and is not allowed in the selected activity.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden člen vašeho palebného týmu je na konzoli a nemá povoleno se vybrané aktivity účastnit.",
                        "da-DK": "Et eller flere medlemmer af din kampgruppe spiller på konsol og har ikke adgang til den valgte aktivitet.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Mitglied deines Feuerteams spielt auf Konsole und darf an der ausgewählten Aktivität nicht teilnehmen.",
                        "el-GR": "Ένα ή περισσότερα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης σου είναι στην κονσόλα και δεν επιτρέπονται στην επιλεγμένη δραστηριότητα.",
                        "es-ES": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo de asalto están jugando en consola y no pueden participar en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "es-MX": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo están jugando en consola y no están permitidos en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yksi tulitiimisi jäsenistä pelaa konsolilla, eikä voi osallistua valittuun aktiviteettiin.",
                        "fr-FR": "Un ou plusieurs membres de l'équipe jouent sur console et ne sont pas autorisés à participer à l'activité sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod legalább egy tagja konzolon játszik, és nem engedélyezett számára a kiválasztott aktivitás.",
                        "it-IT": "Uno o più membri della tua squadra d'assalto giocano su console e non hanno accesso all'attività selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームの 1 人以上のメンバーがコンソールに参加しており、選択したアクティビティで許可されていません。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버 중 한 명 이상이 콘솔로 플레이 중이며 선택된 활동을 할 수 없습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Ett eller flere gruppemedlemmer spiller via konsoll og kan ikke delta i den valgte aktiviteten.",
                        "nl-NL": "Een of meer leden van je vuurteam spelen op de console, wat niet is toegestaan voor de geselecteerde activiteit.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden członek twojej drużyny korzysta z konsoli i nie może brać udziału w wybranej aktywności.",
                        "pt-BR": "Um ou mais membros da sua esquadra estão no console e não são permitidos na atividade selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "Um ou mais membros da tua fireteam estão na consola e isto não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "ru-RU": "Один или несколько участников вашего отряда играют на консоли и не имеют доступа к выбранному занятию.",
                        "sv-SE": "En eller fler gruppmedlemmar spelar via konsol och får inte delta i den valda aktiviteten.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin bir veya daha fazla üyesi konsolda ve bu yüzden seçilen etkinlikte yer almalarına izin verilmiyor.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中有一名或多名成员使用的是游戏主机，而且不允许参加所选的活动。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中有一名或多名成員使用的是遊戲主機，而且不允許參加所選的活動。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Óňз бř mσѓе měmъёřş óƒ ỳøùґ ƒìяєţéªм ïŝ óй ĉóňśбĺэ äиď īš йοт âℓļόщёď ìŉ ŧĥé şεĺèçťєď αстіνĩτў. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Öń℮ ǿґ mόґè мēmъěѓš øƒ γǿцŗ ƒіŕėтэâм ìś őη çőπŝõℓ℮ åйđ įѕ пöт ăŀłõшзð ĩи τħε ѕέľέ¢ŧĕď ªċţìνìŧý. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Φŉê ǿѓ мôřέ mемьėѓś ǿƒ ýōûř ƒîѓзŧ℮ăm îѕ оⁿ ćőŋśõŀє äиď ĩś ήøτ ąℓľоẁέď їñ ťћέ ŝеĺèςťēð ªçτινίтÿ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "DisallowedDeviceClassPC",
                "gameStartErrorId": 38,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "One or more members of your fireteam is on PC and is not allowed in the selected activity.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden člen vašeho palebného týmu je na PC a nemá povoleno se vybrané aktivity účastnit.",
                        "da-DK": "Et eller flere medlemmer af din kampgruppe spiller på pc og har ikke adgang til den valgte aktivitet.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Mitglied deines Feuerteams spielt auf PC und darf an der ausgewählten Aktivität nicht teilnehmen.",
                        "el-GR": "Ένα ή περισσότερα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης σου είναι στον υπολογιστή και δεν επιτρέπονται στην επιλεγμένη δραστηριότητα.",
                        "es-ES": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo de asalto están jugando en PC y no pueden participar en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "es-MX": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo están jugando en PC y no están permitidos en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yksi tulitiimisi jäsenistä pelaa PC:llä, eikä voi osallistua valittuun aktiviteettiin.",
                        "fr-FR": "Un ou plusieurs membres de l'équipe jouent sur PC et ne sont pas autorisés à participer à l'activité sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod legalább egy tagja PC-n játszik, és nem engedélyezett számára a kiválasztott aktivitás.",
                        "it-IT": "Uno o più membri della tua squadra d'assalto giocano su PC e non hanno accesso all'attività selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームの 1 人以上のメンバーが PC に接続しており、選択したアクティビティで許可されていません。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버 중 한 명 이상이 PC로 플레이 중이며 선택된 활동을 할 수 없습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Ett eller flere gruppemedlemmer spiller via PC og kan ikke delta i den valgte aktiviteten.",
                        "nl-NL": "Een of meer leden van je vuurteam spelen op de pc, wat niet is toegestaan voor de geselecteerde activiteit.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden członek twojej drużyny korzysta z komputera PC i nie może brać udziału w wybranej aktywności.",
                        "pt-BR": "Um ou mais membros da sua esquadra estão no PC e não são permitidos na atividade selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "Um ou mais membros da tua fireteam estão no PC e isto não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "ru-RU": "Один или несколько участников вашего отряда играют на ПК и не имеют доступа к выбранному занятию.",
                        "sv-SE": "En eller fler gruppmedlemmar spelar via PC och får inte delta i den valda aktiviteten.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin bir veya daha fazla üyesi bilgisayarda ve bu yüzden seçilen etkinlikte yer almalarına izin verilmiyor.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中有一名或多名成员使用的是 PC，而且不允许参加所选活动。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中有一名或多名成員使用的是 PC，而且不允許參加所選活動。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ōиĕ óŕ мθгé mëmьēřş бƒ ŷöűґ ƒϊřèτеäм ĩѕ θл ΡČ дпð ιѕ ñöт дŀĺòẃëδ іñ ťĥе şεĺè¢ťęđ áĉŧĩνïŧў. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Θлę θѓ мбŕé mёmъёґš őƒ ŷόųř ƒιяèţėǻм ϊś ǿŋ РĆ âⁿđ ίş йσт āłłбẁєđ ìň ţĥē śёľęςŧēð ąčťіνīτŷ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Όñè ŏř мοŕз мёmвêяŝ őƒ уōùг ƒіřзťëáм іś øή РĊ аηδ įŝ ŋōт ăłľǿẃēð ĭπ тђё ŝêļэċťзð αčтįνΐŧу. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "DisallowedDeviceClassXCloud",
                "gameStartErrorId": 39,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "One or more members of your fireteam is on XCloud and is not allowed in the selected activity.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden člen vašeho palebného týmu je na XCloudu a nemá povoleno se vybrané aktivity účastnit.",
                        "da-DK": "Et eller flere medlemmer af din kampgruppe er på XCloud og har ikke adgang til den valgte aktivitet.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Mitglied deines Feuerteams spielt über XCloud und darf an der ausgewählten Aktivität nicht teilnehmen.",
                        "el-GR": "Ένα ή περισσότερα μέλη της ομάδας μάχης σου είναι στο XCloud και δεν επιτρέπονται στην επιλεγμένη δραστηριότητα.",
                        "es-ES": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo de asalto están jugando a través de XCloud y no pueden participar en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "es-MX": "Uno o más miembros de tu equipo están jugando en XCloud y no están permitidos en la actividad seleccionada.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yksi tulitiimisi jäsenistä pelaa XCloudilla, eikä voi osallistua valittuun aktiviteettiin.",
                        "fr-FR": "Un ou plusieurs membres de l'équipe jouent sur XCloud et ne sont pas autorisés à participer à l'activité sélectionnée.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoportod legalább egy tagja XCloudon játszik, és nem engedélyezett számára a kiválasztott aktivitás.",
                        "it-IT": "Uno o più membri della tua squadra d'assalto giocano su XCloud e non hanno accesso all'attività selezionata.",
                        "ja-JP": "ファイヤーチームの 1 人以上のメンバーが XCloud 上にあり、選択したアクティビティで許可されていません。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버 중 한 명 이상이 XCloud로 플레이 중이며 선택된 활동을 할 수 없습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Ett eller flere gruppemedlemmer spiller via XCloud og kan ikke delta i den valgte aktiviteten.",
                        "nl-NL": "Een of meer leden van je vuurteam spelen op XCloud, wat niet is toegestaan voor de geselecteerde activiteit.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden członek twojej drużyny korzysta z usługi XCloud i nie może brać udziału w wybranej aktywności.",
                        "pt-BR": "Um ou mais membros da sua esquadra estão no XCloud e não são permitidos na atividade selecionada.",
                        "pt-PT": "Um ou mais membros da tua fireteam estão na Xcloud e isto não é permitido na atividade selecionada.",
                        "ru-RU": "Один или несколько участников вашего отряда играют через XCloud и не имеют доступа к выбранному занятию.",
                        "sv-SE": "En eller fler gruppmedlemmar spelar via XCloud och får inte delta i den valda aktiviteten.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin bir veya daha fazla üyesi XCloud’da ve bu yüzden seçilen etkinlikte yer almalarına izin verilmiyor.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中有一名或多名成员使用的是 XCloud，而且不允许参加所选活动。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中有一名或多名成員使用的是 XCloud，而且不允許參加所選活動。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Фňě οř мояз мзmьěгѕ óƒ ÿōûŗ ƒįѓёτέам íş оⁿ ЖĆłőūđ αņð ĩŝ ⁿбτ ăℓļöŵéď ϊи тĥε śëŀêċŧėď ăčтįνįŧγ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-ploca": "Óňë ŏґ mõґė mемвеřѕ оƒ ÿŏύř ƒΐгęťєåм ïŝ õή Ж€ℓόΰδ ăňð їš пôт åŀĺóωêď іи ťћē śęļěсťёđ άćтìνīтý. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ωήé ôř мöѓέ mĕмьĕґş οƒ ŷόūг ƒїŕëţ℮ам ïš ǿй Х€łоūď αņď íś иσŧ дľℓощёđ ΐη ťĥê ѕęŀєçŧèď ąсτіνΐтў. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "NoF2PPrivilege",
                "gameStartErrorId": 40,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "At least one member of your fireteam is not currently permitted to play Xbox Live multiplayer games.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Minimálně jeden člen vašeho palebného týmu nemá v současné době povoleno hrát ve službě Xbox Live hry pro více hráčů.",
                        "da-DK": "Mindst ét medlem af din kampgruppe har i øjeblikket ikke tilladelse til at spille multiplayerspil på Xbox Live.",
                        "de-DE": "Mindestens ein Mitglied deines Feuerteams darf derzeit keine Multiplayer-Spieler über Xbox Live spielen.",
                        "el-GR": "Τουλάχιστον ένα μέλος της ομάδας μάχης σου δεν επιτρέπεται προς το παρόν να παίζει παιχνίδια για πολλούς παίκτες στο Xbox Live.",
                        "es-ES": "Al menos un miembro de tu equipo de asalto no puede jugar ahora mismo partidas multijugador en Xbox Live.",
                        "es-MX": "Al menos uno de los miembros de tu equipo no puede jugar en partidas de multijugador en Xbox Live.",
                        "fi-FI": "Vähintään yhdellä tulitiimisi jäsenistä ei ole tällä hetkellä lupaa pelata Xbox Live -moninpelejä.",
                        "fr-FR": "Au moins un membre de votre équipe n'est pas autorisé à participer à des parties multijoueur Xbox Live.",
                        "hu-HU": "A tűzcsoport legalább egyik tagja jelenleg nem tud játszani az Xbox Live többszemélyes játékokkal.",
                        "it-IT": "Almeno un membro della tua squadra d'assalto al momento non può giocare partite multiplayer Xbox Live.",
                        "ja-JP": "少なくともファイヤーチーム内の 1 人が Xbox Live マルチプレイヤーのプレイを許可されていません。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조 멤버 중 적어도 한 명에게 Xbox Live 멀티 플레이어 게임을 할 권한이 없습니다.",
                        "nb-NO": "Minst ett av gruppemedlemmene har ikke tillatelse til å spille flerspillerspill via Xbox Live.",
                        "nl-NL": "Ten minste één lid van je vuurteam mag momenteel geen Xbox Live-multiplayergames spelen.",
                        "pl-PL": "Co najmniej jeden członek twojej drużyny nie może obecnie grać w gry wieloosobowe w ramach usługi Xbox Live.",
                        "pt-BR": "Pelo menos um membro da sua esquadra não tem permissão para jogar o modo multijogador no Xbox Live no momento.",
                        "pt-PT": "Pelo menos um membro na tua fireteam não está atualmente autorizado a jogar jogos multijogador no Xbox Live.",
                        "ru-RU": "Как минимум у одного из участников вашего отряда сейчас нет разрешения играть в сетевом режиме через Xbox Live.",
                        "sv-SE": "Minst en gruppmedlem har inte tillstånd att spela flerspelarspel via Xbox Live.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin en az bir üyesinin şu anda Xbox Live çok oyunculu oyunlarını oynamasına izin verilmiyor.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队中，至少有 1 位成员目前没有进行 Xbox Live 多人游戏的权限。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組中，至少有 1 位成員目前沒有進行 Xbox Live 多人遊戲的權限。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Áτ ĺêаŝτ όⁿё мёmъęѓ оƒ уöμя ƒíŕзťεäm īś ñόţ сµѓгėйţľŷ рєѓmìτŧĕď ţŏ рļàý Жъóх Łĩνє mϋŀŧîφŀáỳèŕ ĝämêş. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Åт ℓзăśτ ôńз m℮mьěŗ óƒ ÿøµѓ ƒīŕéťęåm ιś иот ćûяѓёиťℓγ ρ℮ŕмϊтŧэď τŏ рļăу χъõж Ļîν℮ мΰļţϊрľäўέŗ ģámėѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "Ǻт ŀєâŝτ оŋє mзмвëŗ ōƒ уōûя ƒίяĕŧéám įš ńõţ ¢ũѓгёńтļγ рêѓмīτť℮ď тò φľªŷ Жъσх Ŀïνĕ mùĺтіρĺαŷêŕ ġãмзѕ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            },
            {
                "gameStartError": "SkillRangeTooWideForMatchmaking",
                "gameStartErrorId": 41,
                "displayString": {
                    "status": "Ready",
                    "value": "Your fireteam's range of ranks is too wide to matchmake in this playlist, please visit halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR for more info.",
                    "translations": {
                        "cs-CZ": "Rozptyl hodností ve vašem palebném týmu je příliš velký na to, aby bylo možné vytvořit hru v tomto playlistu. Pro další informace prosím navštivte halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR.",
                        "da-DK": "Der er for stor spredning på medlemmernes rang i din kampgruppe til at matche på denne spilliste. Besøg halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR for at få flere oplysninger.",
                        "de-DE": "Die Rangunterschiede zwischen den Mitgliedern deines Feuerteams sind zu groß für die Spielersuche in dieser Spielliste. Mehr Informationen sind auf halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR zu finden.",
                        "el-GR": "Το εύρος των βαθμών της ομάδας πυρός σας είναι πολύ μεγάλo για να ταιριάζει σε αυτήν τη λίστα αναπαραγωγής. Επισκεφθείτε τη διεύθυνση halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR για περισσότερες πληροφορίες.",
                        "es-ES": "Los rangos de tu equipo de asalto son demasiado dispares para hacer matchmaking en esta lista de juego. Para más información, consulta halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR.",
                        "es-MX": "La variedad de rangos de tu equipo de asalto es demasiado amplia para el emparejamiento en esta lista de juego. Visita halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR para obtener más información.",
                        "fi-FI": "Tulitiiminne jäsenten taitotaso vaihtelee liikaa päästäksenne tämän pelitilan vastuksenhakuun. Osoitteesta halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR löydätte lisätietoja.",
                        "fr-FR": "Les trop grosses différences de grade au sein de votre équipe empêchent le matchmaking dans cette sélection. Rendez-vous sur halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR pour en savoir plus.",
                        "hu-HU": "Tűzcsoportod tagjainak rangjai nagyon széles skálán helyezkednek el a párosításhoz ezen a játéklistát. Keresd fel a halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR oldalt további részletekért.",
                        "it-IT": "La varietà di gradi presente nella tua squadra d'assalto è troppo ampia per permettere l'utilizzo del matchmaking in questa playlist. Visita halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR per maggiori informazioni.",
                        "ja-JP": "このプレイリストでマッチメイキングするには、ファイアチームのランクの範囲が広すぎます。詳細については、halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR をご覧ください。",
                        "ko-KR": "화력조의 랭킹 범위가 너무 넓어 이 플레이리스트에서 매치 메이킹을 할 수 없습니다. 자세한 사항은 halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR에서 확인하십시오.",
                        "nb-NO": "Geværlagets spredning i grader er for stor til å passe i denne spillelisten. Gå til halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR for å få vite mer.",
                        "nl-NL": "De rangen van je vuurteamleden zijn te gevarieerd voor matchmaking in deze playlist. Ga naar halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR voor meer info.",
                        "pl-PL": "Zakres rang w twojej drużynie jest zbyt szeroki, by skorzystać z matchmakingu w ramach tej playlisty. Wejdź na halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR, by uzyskać więcej informacji.",
                        "pt-BR": "Os Spartans em sua esquadra possuem uma variedade de postos alta demais para jogar esta lista de jogos, acesse halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR para saber mais.",
                        "pt-PT": "O conjunto de classificações da tua fireteam é demasiado amplo para o matchmaking nesta lista de reprodução.",
                        "ru-RU": "Для использования подбора игроков в этом списке игр у участников вашего отряда слишком большая разница по рейтингу. Подробнее на странице halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR.",
                        "sv-SE": "Din grupp har ett för brett rangspann för att matchas i den här spellistan. Besök halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR för mer information.",
                        "tr-TR": "Atış timinizin rütbe aralığı bu oyun listesinde eşleştirme yapılamayacak kadar çok geniş, lütfen daha fazla bilgi almak için halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR sayfasına bakın.",
                        "zh-CN": "您的火力小队排名范围太广，无法在这个游戏列表中进行匹配，请访问 halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR 以获取详细信息。",
                        "zh-TW": "您的火力小組排名範圍太廣，無法在這個遊戲清單中進行配對，請造訪 halowaypoint.com/FireteamCSR 以取得詳細資訊。",
                        "qps-ploc": "Ýσųя ƒїŗеŧęám'ş ґâиğĕ óƒ řáŋκŝ ίş ŧõο ẅįďé ťõ мâţċĥмάќē ιŉ тĥīś ρľãŷℓϊśţ, φľєåšέ νìŝīţ ħáļőẁãγφôίŉŧ.ĉǿм/₣îřёťęąmÇŚŘ ƒоř мοѓě ìйƒø. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-ploca": "Ỳóûŗ ƒįѓêţëªм'ş ŗãñğе őƒ ŕāпĸŝ ίѕ τŏο ώìδέ ŧō мàтčħмáκë ĩñ τħīѕ φℓάýļϊšт, ρłєǻş℮ νΐśϊт нâłǿŵåŷрòìńţ.ćòм/₣îŕęţεąmĆŠΓ ƒόґ møřè ĭŋƒô. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!",
                        "qps-plocm": "¥õūř ƒìřзтэáм'ѕ ŕαⁿġė óƒ ŕăйĸś ìš τσő щіδē τő mâтсђмąĸê īп ŧнîŝ рŀãÿŀíśţ, рĺēãŝę νϊşĩť ĥäŀöẁàурôϊňŧ.ćŏm/₣ïяэťėàm€ЅЃ ƒöř мσřê ìиƒõ. !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!! !!!"
                    }
                }
            }
        ]
    }
	</code>
</example>